During the two weeks that Nana was gone,
I took on extra work,
so I’d be busy every day,
and worked until I was
absolutely exhausted.
I did this to keep my mind off
of how lonely I was.
Yet I went to the practice sessions
at the studio without fail.
Then Nobu would always walk me home.
I hadn’t heard from Takumi at all.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
I’m thinking about going on a trip.
Hey, that sounds nice.
Don't forget my souvenir.
I’m finished.
So where do you wanna go?
Go on your own.
You might have the time, but I’m busy.
Take some time off work.
We have an important concert coming up,
so I have to practice every day.
What’s that? Are you on the pill again?
It’s your fault!
If you want a child that badly,
have some other woman
give birth to one for you.
You don’t mind
if I sleep with another woman?
You’re such a cold woman.
You just realized that now?
I’m gonna go write a song
for the cute Reira.
Oh, Shin. You’re awake.
Good morning, Ms. Ryoko.
I’ll be flying out again tomorrow.
To the States.
So I won’t be seeing you for a while.
But I’ll bring back a bunch of gifts,
so keep your hopes high.
So you’ll be going.
I’ll be lonely without you, Ms. Ryoko.
Oh, my. You’re not only good
with your technique,
but you’ve also improved
your choice of words.
Perhaps it’s due
to my great teaching skills.
I am grateful.
Thanks to you, business is thriving.
I’ve turned an angel into a devil.
Up close,
I guess you don’t look much
like her after all.
Huh? What did you say?
No. Nothing. Seconds please!
Yasu!
Long time no see.
You haven’t changed one bit.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Oh, one stout beer please.
How are you doing?
I’m glad to finally meet up with you.
That’s because you keep pestering me.
I invited Reira too,
but she’s back in her hometown.
She really wanted to come.
Is that so?
By the way, Naoki, your voice is too loud.
You’re a celebrity now,
so you’d be wise to keep a low profile.
Not to worry.
The customers here are all
from the entertainment industry.
Really?
By the way, Yasu, I heard you came
to Tokyo to go pro.
Reira was complaining that
she’s not happy with your decision.
Yeah, I guessed as much.
That’s why I don’t wanna see her.
She’ll keep teasing me about it.
Well, of course she’d tease you.
What in the world happened
to make you change your mind?
Let’s see.
You could say I feel responsible
for the band like it's my child.
What’s that supposed to mean?
You really haven’t changed, Yasu.
You need to let it all out sometimes.
Go wild for a change.
Though I suggest not becoming
as violent as Takumi.
When he loses it, he becomes a criminal.
Although he’s been quite calm as of late,
perhaps from fear of becoming
the next gossip item.
Back in junior high school,
none of the windows had
glass because of him.
Yeah, I remember that.
Speaking of Takumi,
I can’t reach him on his cell phone.
What’s he up to?
I don’t know, but…
He’s probably visiting women,
one after another.
There’s no need to worry about him.
Is that so?
Reira, what are you doing?
-Visiting my hometown.
-Oh right. Of course.
You startled me.
How long have you been here?
-Thirty minutes.
-Huh?
I’ve been here staring at you
like this for thirty minutes,
but you didn’t notice me at all, Takumi.
I'm exhausted.
No, I meant how long
have you been in town.
Anyway, if you’ve been staring at me,
the least you could do is say something!
I’ve been here for three days.
I was visiting mother’s grave just now.
But your mother is still alive.
Your mother, Takumi.
Due to work, you couldn’t be
here for the ceremony
marking seven years after her passing,
so I prayed that she may
warmly protect her careless son
from the wrath of the gods.
Well, thanks for that.
Is your father doing okay?
Maybe I should go and say hi.
Don’t bother.
He’s the same as always,
drinking from early in the day.
That’s gotta be tough
for your elder sister and her husband.
With a little brother like this
on top of it.
You know, if you’re gonna worry
about someone,
worry about your own mother!
Leaving her alone way out here
in the countryside.
But she says
she doesn’t wanna go to Tokyo.
She really likes this place.
I don’t get it.
What’s so good about this place
way out in the countryside?
Especially given the fact
she lived in New York at one point.
Isn’t that why?
Living abroad didn’t suit her at all.
I’ve been telling her Tokyo
isn’t a foreign country.
But I kinda miss New York.
It’s my birthplace after all.
Why not go there?
Though we only have two more days off.
You should’ve gone.
Hmm… But I had a number of things to do.
Besides, we all should pay our respects
to our parents once in a while.
We came so close on our tour
the other day,
but I couldn’t visit because
of our tight schedule.
What about you, Takumi?
As long as I stay in Tokyo,
I end up working.
So I thought I’d wander off
to the countryside.
Call it an escape.
But I can’t keep my mind off work,
so I’ll be returning now.
I just stopped by here for a bit.
Huh, you’re going back?
We got to meet here,
so why not have some fun together?
Give me a break.
Give me a chance to be alone
on our off days. See ya.
Oh, Reira…
We’ve got a photo shoot
for a magazine next week,
so don’t get tanned.
I’m aware of that, leader.
What is that Takumi guy doing?
His time off is coming to an end.
But I didn’t contact him either.
Why didn’t you?
You have no reason to hold back.
You should send him a bunch
of emails daily and keep his mind on you.
But I don’t wanna contact him
only to be ignored.
He may be in less of a position
to contact you
once he's back to work.
Yes. But it’s okay if that’s how it goes.
Yasu! Aren’t you worried about Hachi?
Don’t you get the urge to call Takumi
and give him an earful?
Sure. But I can’t get through
to him on his cell.
Nana! If he came to see me
because someone around him told him to,
that’s not gonna make me too happy!
I really am fine, so don’t worry!
The way I said that…
to them it probably sounds like
I’m trying to be strong about this.
But the honest truth is,
if Takumi were to never call me again,
I’d be fine with that.
Or in fact, it would be better that way.
Hachi! Buy one for me too!
Buy it yourself.
What should I get?
You know, Nana’s singing seems
to be improving day by day,
don’t you think?
Maybe because of the sit-ups.
I'm sure we'd be able to go pro, right?
Trapnest will be on their break
for two more days.
If I don’t hear from Takumi again,
I can become the poor girl
who was tricked and dumped by a nasty guy.
I can make it all Takumi’s fault
and move on to a new love.
But if he found out
about my cunning thoughts,
he’ll end up hating me.
First of all, I’d be dreaming
to think someone would
make me their girlfriend
because Takumi dumped me.
I don’t want Nobu thinking
I’m such an easy woman.
But the fact is, I am that type of woman.
A black, four-wheel drive Mercedes Benz.
Nobu!
-Thank you for walking me home.
-Huh?
I’ll be fine on my own from here on.
It's just around the corner.
I’m sorry for having you take
a longer route home
to walk me home every day.
No, I don’t mind it.
If you’re bothered by it,
I’ll have Shin or Yasu walk you home
from tomorrow…
No, it doesn’t bother me.
Nana!
If he’s gonna come at this stage,
he could’ve sent me
an email ahead of time.
Such a selfish man
who makes decisions on a whim.
Well, well. It’s you.
Where were you this late at night?
I worry, you know.
I’ve been waiting for an hour.
Ah, sorry. I was at the studio
to see Nana and her band practice.
Nana’s staying with Ren now,
so Nobu walked me home
because I'm afraid to walk alone.
Is that so?
Well, thank you very much for that.
Okay, then. Thank you, Nobu.
Good night.
I’m the worst.
Sorry for coming like this
out of the blue.
I left my place without my cell phone
and came here before returning,
so I couldn’t call you.
This is what happens
when I think cunning thoughts
and take advantage of Nobu’s kindness
by having him walk me home.
I must’ve really hurt his feelings.
What am I gonna do?
I can’t go to the studio anymore.
I won’t be able to look him in the eye!
Oh, Takumi, want me to make you something?
Are you hungry?
No.
Then do you want something to drink?
-There’s cold beer.
-Sure.
I mustn’t let my guard down.
To Takumi, I’m nothing
but a convenient woman
who will sleep with him
when he wants to do it.
It’s one thing to get involved
once or twice,
but this is the third time.
If I don’t put a stop to this,
this pathetic relationship
may continue on.
If I’m gonna end this,
I’ve gotta do it now,
before it’s too late.
I just have to tell him
to never come here again.
But…
am I able to say such a thing?
I can’t say it.
Why are you drinking on your own?
Give me some too.
I know he’s not that great a guy.
So why can’t I… end it?
Oh, welcome home, Nobu.
Don’t!
What are you watching?
Porn videos. I’m studying.
Cut it out. Not at a time like this.
Are you doing it to make fun of me?
I can’t take it anymore.
Take what?
What’s the matter?
Nothing! It’s none of your business!
Um, sorry. Please leave me alone.
Shin.
A man and a woman are
simply opposing creatures
driven toward each other by lust.
Can they be connected by love?
Sorry, I don’t know either.
The truth is, I’m just a girl
who wanted to get close
to Trapnest’s Takumi outta curiosity.
I’m not as pure as Nana thinks.
And I’m sure I’m different
from the ideal girl Nobu pictures me as.
But Takumi understands me…
me who's helplessly empty.
And I do too.
I know Takumi is a pathetic man.
Nana…
It’s strange.
He lived in a world
farthest away from mine.
But only Takumi…
will forgive me for who I am,
as if he was the sole accomplice
to my actions.
Thanks for your concerns about everything.
Takumi came by last night,
and says he’ll be with me
all day tomorrow,
until the end of his break.
But I have work. I should have
taken the day off.
What time do you think
you can make it home, Nana?
With the live concert coming up,
I don’t wanna get in the way
of your practice,
so I won’t be dropping by
the studio. Good luck.
Say hi to everyone for me. Hachiko.
Trapnest’s time off came to an end,
but Nana didn’t come home.
I simply assumed she was with Ren.
I wanted to at least drop
by the studio and see Nana.
But I didn’t because I didn’t have
the guts to see Nobu.
As usual, Takumi didn’t send me
a single email.
But surprisingly, I accepted that
with an open mind,
casually thinking he’ll eventually come
to see me again.
I couldn’t tell if that was
a feeling of trust or resignation.
Misato!
Thank you for coming all
the way out to pick me up, Ms. Komatsu.
It’s not a problem. And call me Hachiko.
That’s such a cute nickname.
We still have time before the concert,
so why don’t we go home first
so you can leave your bags?
I’ll carry one.
Thank you so much.
Is it really okay to stay
at your place again?
Mm-hmm. You can stay
for as many nights as you wish.
It’s summer vacation,
so you have free time, don’t you?
Yes.
To be honest, I would love to spend all
of my summer vacation here,
but I couldn’t possibly impose
on you for a full month.
That’s totally okay with me!
Then spend
your whole summer vacation here!
Or rather, I want you to stay!
Are you sure? I’m thrilled!
I’m just as glad about it.
-Nana’s staying with Ren…
-A train will be arriving on track one.
and shows no sign of returning.
-I was feeling all lonely living alone.
-Please stay inside the yellow line.
TRAIN IS COMING
You know, I still can’t get
over the excitement
after learning that Nana and Ren
are all lovey-dovey.
I carelessly blurted it out.
I assumed you would already know.
But I did secretly find out
when they were back in my hometown
that the two were living together.
I’ve been wondering what had happened
between them after that,
so this news is such a relief to me.
Please don’t tell anyone, okay?
Rest assured.
Please have faith in me, Ms. Hachiko.
The concert starts at seven, right?
I can’t wait to see the band members.
I wonder if they’re still rehearsing.
Actually, I haven’t seen them for a week.
But I thought you visited the studio
every day to see them practice.
Well, yeah, but…
I didn’t wanna bother them
so close to their live performance.
I see. You’re right.
Let’s hope that BLAST’s
professional debut becomes a reality.
Mm-hmm.
If I were to see Nobu today,
what expression should I make?
Nobu may never smile for me again.
That thought almost made me cry.
That other night, when Nana sang
that song that Nobu wrote,
she was wishing for something
as she sang it with such passion…
so her voice would reach me.
Right now, I realize what she was wishing.