I realized that the time had come to face
the problem I had been ignoring
by not thinking too deeply about it.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
RE: IT’S ME, REIRA
Why does being pregnant make me
so sleepy every day?
NEW MESSAGE, UNREAD EMAIL: 01
UNREAD TEXT MESSAGE: 01
SEPTEMBER 24TH
NOBU - HOW ARE YOU?
RECEIVED MAIL
SEPTEMBER 24TH 2:36 A.M.
NOBU
HOW ARE YOU?
I WANT TO HAVE A PROPER TALK
WITH YOU. IS IT POSSIBLE?
I’LL BE WAITING FOR YOUR REPLY.
NO NEW MESSAGES
Nobu!
Yasu says lunch is ready.
Spaghetti with mushrooms!
I think we can count on a tasty meal.
Yasu’s cooking is the best.
Who are you expecting a reply from?
You’ve been checking
your email all morning.
Well, you know,
because the reception is bad here.
But you usually leave your cell phone
in your room.
Shin, do something about that habit
of yours of closely observing others.
Sorry. But you’re easy to figure out
even without observing closely.
I don’t want you figuring me out!
But I can.
It’s dangerous here.
Looking at the night sky,
it’s as if you can reach the stars.
You get the feeling that
your dreams will come true.
Shin, thank you for your email.
I feel it’s been a long time
since I’ve seen that many stars.
Even if I close my eyes,
I can only imagine artificial neon lights
like in a planetarium.
Because I thought I’m no different
from such neon lights.
Your words have saved me once again, Shin.
Thank you so much.
PHEW
Thank you, Nami. You have quite the tan.
No! Yes! I mean,
I’m sorry, I’m kind of nervous!
I’ve been a big fan of Trapnest
since your debut!
Really?
Don’t question her. She’s being polite.
Honey!
You think this pattern is too flashy?
You don’t need to wear a tie.
I have to look dignified as a father.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Pleased to meet you. I’m Takumi Ichinose.
You sure are tall! H-- How tall are you?
One meter and 83 centimeters, right?
I wasn’t asking you. Fawning all over him…
I apologize that it took so long
before I could come.
These are some gifts from England.
Though, the only thing British
about them is the tea.
-Oh my, this much?
-What is it?
Wow, thanks, Brother!
I’ll follow you for the rest of my life!
How cozy!
It’s beautiful! Your father
would never buy me things like this.
You certainly seem to be well-off,
Mr. Ichinose.
Do celebrities get paid that well?
It depends on the person.
After all, your profits are determined
by your popularity.
That’s true.
Are you sure you can provide
for my daughter and her child
for the rest of their lives?
-I’m positive, sir.
-"Sir "?
He seems like an untrustworthy guy.
I may be a celebrity on the outside,
but I’m just a hard worker.
It’s difficult to continue a band
regardless of its popularity.
I’d like to be in the same band forever,
but that’s not something that
I alone can determine.
Today, I wore a wedding dress
while filming our promo video.
It’s a song about a woman
who can’t get married.
The staff just don't get it!
We filmed the entire day for a few scenes
that will only be a few seconds.
Everything we work on is like that.
The work takes a lot of effort,
but the thrill of completing something
together is like none other,
and with my friends,
I’m able to feel that I belong here.
Thinking back, that’s probably
why I was able to come this far
with my singing
no matter how tough things got.
All right, okay. We’re done.
-Done already?
-We’ve done enough.
At your current level as a singer,
it’ll be the same, no matter
how many times we record.
In other words, you’ve given it
all you’ve got for now, and it was great.
What’s that supposed to mean?
We can artificially adjust the high notes
you have trouble reaching.
Do some voice training
before the live performance,
so you don’t embarrass yourself.
Otherwise, the music magazines
will start writing nasty things about you.
Shut up! Stop laughing!
Let me sing it again!
Well then, now that we’re done
with the recording,
what do you say we go fishing?
-Yeah, that sounds like fun.
-All right!
That’s the only thing I’ve been looking
forward to doing here.
-The only thing?
-Matsuo!
Let me sing some more!
Keep it down!
You’ll scare off all the fish!
Say, why did your wife leave you?
Um…
I think the number one reason Gaia
decided to record at that training camp
was to strengthen the bond
between the band members and the staff.
The staff you’ll be working
with from now on
will be like your family,
there to support the band.
I think participating in that camp
has great meaning to it.
Let’s both do our best.
Mr. Ichinose, what about your family?
How many siblings do you have?
You have a big sister, right?
We’re not asking you.
Honey…
Would you let me talk too?
This isn’t any fun!
But you hardly know a damn thing
about my family, don't you?
-"A damn thing"?
-Excuse my language.
Oh, that’s not a problem at all!
You can use that language with me
whenever you damn please!
It’s not fine! Not at all!
And your Japanese is funny!
Nami, go buy some sake.
Yes, you do that.
And pick up the ingredients
for sukiyaki too.
Huh? No way!
Besides, what are the ingredients? Meat?
Let’s take the car
and go together, Nami. Okay?
You wanna go out
with your new handbag, don’t you?
Don’t tell me you like Nami.
Please, anyone but her.
I’m so sorry! Nana and Nami
are both such noisy girls.
Me too? Don’t group me with Nami!
Not at all. I’m enjoying this very much.
My mother was very weak,
and the rest of my family
was rather gloomy.
Perhaps because of that,
I’ve always been drawn
to energetic, happy people.
That’s why I find this so attractive.
The feeling of a loving family
like yours. This is fun.
I see.
Well, one thing I can guarantee
is Nana’s good health.
So how is your family doing now?
My mother passed away six years ago.
My sister married a local man.
They now live
with their two children and our father.
Okay, then we should give them
a visit sometime soon.
We’ll all go and pay our respects
at your mother’s grave.
-Yes, we should.
-No, it’s okay.
-Huh?
In fact, my father is
a complete alcoholic,
and lately, he can’t even manage
a proper conversation. I’m sorry.
An alcoholic. That must be tough for you.
But we still should go
and introduce ourselves.
No, it’s really all right.
He’s the type of man
that wouldn’t even attend
my sister’s wedding
or my mother’s funeral.
Besides, I have no intention
of inviting him to our wedding.
I wouldn’t want him ruining it.
If there’s something not right
about the father,
the child isn’t going to amount to much.
I’m a good example.
More importantly, about the location
of the wedding ceremony,
would you mind taking a look
at these documents?
Hey, guy. You’re not a salesman.
Honey! Don't call him "guy"!
Ren?
Ren, you’ll catch a cold
if you sleep here.
Here. Come here like a good boy.
Come on.
Reira? I’m sorry. I guess I dozed off.
Did Mr. Honjo have a bit
too much to drink?
Is he okay?
Yeah. This always happens.
-Help me carry him to the bed.
-Sure.
Shin.
Right now, I’m really
regretting having left in Japan
the lighter you purposely forgot.
I left it because I didn’t want
to risk losing or breaking it,
but I feel uneasy not having it
within reach.
Taking care of something is so difficult.
I’ll be returning to Japan on the 27th.
When will you be returning to Tokyo, Shin?
I wanna talk with you face to face.
Because I believe looking
someone in the eye
without any pretenses is
like looking at yourself.
If you look away, you lose.
And I don’t wanna lose.
FROM REN
MESSAGE FOR NANA
I GOT BACK TO JAPAN TODAY.
PLEASE GIVE ME A CALL.
-Did you read it?
-Yeah.
THE HOUSEWIFE NEXT DOOR
BY AI YAZAWA
Without delay,
the eight-day, seven-night-long recording
at the training camp finally
came to an end.
But even after returning to Tokyo,
I can’t go home while the place
is still infested with those mosquitoes.
What are you reading, Shin?
You’re into literature, I see.
An erotic novel. Mika bought it
for me at a book stand.
Is it any good, Shin?
-Not at all.
-Huh?
-No use trying to tease him, Mika.
-Oh, Mika.
-I think Shin knows more about that
-You can only touch him
-than you do.
-from the neck up.
Huh?
-But this is good study material.
-What study is that?
THE HOUSEWIFE NEXT DOOR
BY AI YAZAWA
The Housewife Next Door?
Starting today,
we’re all being thrown
into the agency’s so-called dormitory.
They just call it a dormitory.
It’s really a regular apartment building.
It’s for our agency’s talents only,
though.
Everyone gets their own room,
there’s no curfew,
and there's no nosy dorm supervisor.
But the security and facilities are
above the basic standards,
so it’s safe and comfortable!
I don’t care what it is,
as long as I can relax and get some sleep.
You’re better off not opening the window.
That’s a love hotel next door.
They’re not likely to open
their windows too often either.
What’s comfortable about this?
I don’t get any sunlight here!
You have your own toilet and shower.
Where’s the bathtub?
You’re such a complainer!
Who do you think you are?
If you wanna live the high life,
then work your way up there.
I’ll make certain that you have
a full schedule starting tomorrow.
Wait, Ginpei! Is there a phone here?
There’s one on the first floor
at the front desk!
The front desk?
At least buy a cell phone!
Work will be so inconvenient without one!
That’s not a front desk!
And the security guard’s asleep!
What’s the point of having one?
He’s bored,
which is proof of how safe it is.
I’ll pick you up
tomorrow morning at 7:00 a.m.
Don’t go wandering off outside!
There’s something wrong.
Something’s definitely wrong
about this production company.
Even the president was a weirdo.
Well, do your best.
No, I can’t judge people
by their appearances,
but this guy also looks like one of them.
-Who are you, miss?
-I’m Nana from the Black Stones!
I just introduced myself
to you moments ago!
Oh right. Did you want something?
I wanna use the phone.
Go ahead and use it. It’s free.
NO LONG PHONE CALLS
Forget it. I don’t wanna be overheard.
I’ll borrow Nobu’s phone.
Really, go ahead and use it, miss!
But say I call Ren,
what am I gonna say to him?
We’re not gonna be able to see
each other for a while anyway.
I actually would prefer
that he leave me alone
rather than have him half-heartedly
show some affection toward me.
That’s what I should say to him.
I’m finding it hard to breathe.
It must be because the air is dirty.
That’s why I hate Tokyo.
Huh? The Black Stones? I know the band!
-You do?
-Well, it’s famous, in a way!
No, not nearly as famous as you.
This is so exciting! Hey, come on in!
Huh? But…
Come on! Hurry!
Ow!
What are you doing, little man?
You seem to be having fun.
Well, I was just saying hi to my neighbor.
Nana?
She’s gorgeous! She sure is a celebrity!
It’s the real Nana!
Please give me your autograph!
-Huh? Yuri Kosaka?
-That adult film star?
You all seem to know her.
RESIDENTS RULE BOOK
What the hell kind of agency is
"Shikai Corporation"?
Why are there adult film actresses
working for the agency?
Well, she did start out as an idol.
But when her popularity dipped,
she took her clothes off.
You know a lot about her, Yasu.
And how could you make the dormitory coed?
That’s borderline outrageous!
I’m guessing it’s to accommodate
or shelter their talents
with some sort of problems.
Like Ginpei was saying,
they just call it a dormitory.
You’re right. But Ms. Yuri’s been
in so many adult films,
so she must have money.
So why is she living
in a shabby place like this?
Ms. Yuri?
-Nobu! Switch rooms with me.
-Huh?
With a starving wolf like
you living next door,
"Ms. Yuri" would be in danger!
-I’m not gonna do anything! She’s a pro!
-I don’t care! Just switch!
Why are you always so bossy?
Nobu, I couldn’t care less
if you get off on porn videos,
but I hope you haven’t forgotten our plan.
Plan?
To get Hachiko back!
We pledged to fight together!
So don’t get involved with other women!
What are you saying?
You’re misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
You were bashfully
and gleefully chatting with Yuri!
No, not that.
I’m not necessarily fighting
to get Hachi back.
And this is unrelated to that.
For me, Hachi and the band
are separate issues.
Besides, why do I have
to take care of Hachi
just so you can own her in your yard?
Honestly speaking,
I have completely given up on her,
so do whatever you wish on your own.
-But…
-What? Damn, you’re being stubborn.
Then what are we fighting for?
Huh?
That’s a stupid question.
We’re fighting
so our music will be accepted
as professional.
Hachi has nothing to do with it.
Nana?
Nobu is free to date whomever he wants.
But then,
how do I stay connected to Hachi?
I can no longer go home to that place,
and even if I did,
Hachi’s no longer there.
Hey, Yasu, how do you read this kanji?
"Itsuwari." It means "lie."
Thanks.
NOBU
Yes?
Yasu! Nana’s…
Nana!
Shin, call an ambulance! The number’s 119.
What’s the address here?
Tell Mr. Yamagishi, the security guard,
and have him call one!
Okay!
We were talking, and then all of a sudden,
she was short of breath
and seemed to be in pain,
like she was having an attack.
Nana, are you okay?
An ambulance will be here soon.
It’s okay. Don’t worry.
I won’t leave your side.
I’m not going anywhere.
I think she’s hyperventilating.
It’s so painful you think you’re dying,
but you will never die from it.
What?
It’s a living hell.
Hey, wait!
Nobu! Do you have a paper or plastic bag?
Huh? Why?
Just hurry and find one!
Hey, Hachi.
Humans are such pathetic creatures.
The harder they struggle,
the deeper they sink.
If I were to be born again,
I want to be a fish.
Ren and I, just the two of us,
would swim in a small fish tank.