FROM NANA
The moment I saw that empty room,
I felt that I had become lost
in a lonely world where only I existed.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
What? She moved?
Mm-hmm. She says she lives
a lot farther away,
so she doesn’t think she can come by much.
She asked me to give her best
to everyone here at Jackson’s.
Wait a minute.
What’s that supposed to mean?
That’s making me feel really lonely.
Who moved?
Nana. She moved to Shirogane.
Why Shirogane, all of a sudden?
Minami Aoyama, Hiroo, Azabu.
Each one of those properties
were spectacular as well.
They’re all in really expensive districts!
But I thought right from the beginning
that Nana would choose Shirogane.
Why’s that?
Because it’s the place that
young wives dream about.
Young wives?
She probably wants to be one
of the "Housewives of Shirogane."
What the…
Personally, I’m a bit relieved.
I’m looking forward to seeing Nana
in a wedding dress.
Even if she’s doing it
for her child’s sake,
I can’t understand how she could marry
a guy she doesn’t even love.
No, if she didn’t love him,
she wouldn’t do it.
-But what about Nobu?
-She probably loves them both.
That’s something
you can relate to, isn’t it?
I’m home!
Huh? You’re here, Shoji.
So you’ve finally run out of money
to drink at Jackson’s?
A toast to Nana,
who’s marrying a rich guy.
So you heard.
Although she probably wouldn’t want you
to celebrate it.
But how rich is this guy,
who can afford a million-yen rent?
No, it’s 700,000 yen.
She persuaded him to save some
of the rent money for the child.
Nana’s starting to mature.
That’s the strength of becoming
a mother, I guess.
But even 700,000 yen is plenty expensive!
-Who is this guy?
-He’s a musician.
Someone close to that guru again?
I guess. He’s Yasu’s friend, I hear.
If it’s one of Yasu’s friends,
there’s no need to worry.
But for him to have that much income
would mean, unlike BLAST,
this guy’s a professional musician, right?
Is he famous?
No, one would have to be a major star
to make that much in music.
He’s likely some carefree son
of a rich family.
Besides, why would a famous star
want to marry someone like Nana?
Also, with how excited Nana gets
when it comes to celebrities,
there’s no way she would’ve kept quiet
about it if he were even a little famous.
But maybe she’s forced to keep it
a secret because he’s a celebrity!
Huh?
-What’s his name?
-Takumi.
Takumi is so cool!
Of Trapnest?
That’s impossible! Are you dumb?
-Why are you following me?
-See ya.
Why not? I’ll leave right away!
-Just let me get a glimpse of Hachiko!
-All right.
Welcome home.
This place is nice. Is it a new building?
The rent is very reasonable
for the space, right?
It's because you have to walk
a bit from the train station.
You never use the train anyway.
This is nice. Like a hidden residence.
Is it your first time to this place, too?
Because we were confined
to the studio the whole time?
No. I came to see this place once
when I signed the contract.
Really?
I needed to check the neighborhood
and the security system,
or else I’d be worried.
Hello?
I’m home.
Ah, um… Welcome home!
She’s tripping on her words.
She’s too cute.
-You seem to be having fun, Takumi.
-Because we’re newlyweds.
But you’re not legally married yet.
Are you really serious
about getting married?
You’re still renting the place
in Akasaka too, right?
Are you planning to live separately?
Shut up. I’ll move out of
that place eventually.
Eventually?
There’s an auto-lock on each floor too.
Talk about high security.
I’m seldom at home, so this is
to ensure the safety of my wife and child.
Especially since you have
many extreme fans.
Why are they so fixated
on chasing an illusion?
-I have trouble understanding it.
-It’s because it’s an illusion!
In reality, there is no person
who would do exactly as you’d wish.
But Takumi, you are getting married
to a woman whom
you have trouble understanding, right?
I have trouble understanding that.
Nana knows that reality and illusions
are two different things.
She knows that, and she still dreams
without getting discouraged.
That’s what’s so cute about her.
Then Hachiko and I are the same!
So that makes me cute, too! Right, Takumi?
I wanna smack him.
-Yes?
-I’m home.
What am I gonna do?
I’m getting nervous.
Please don’t stay long.
Don’t intrude on our first night
as newlyweds.
But you’re not newlyweds,
and it’s not your first night together.
-Welcome home!
-Hi. Good evening.
Who is this guy?
Good evening…
NAOKI
Hachiko’s so cute!
If you’re satisfied, go home.
This place is like a castle!
What part?
You must be exhausted from your recording.
How thoughtful of you.
If it’s not inconvenient,
won’t you stay for dinner?
-Yes!
-Don’t bother.
He’ll be leaving right away.
Then I’ll have dinner ready right away.
I got carried away and prepared too much,
so it would be a great help
if you’d eat with us.
Yes.
MORNING SICKNESS COUNTERMEASURE
Wow! Thanks for the food!
Delicious!
Yeah? I’m glad.
You’re a great cook, just like I’d heard.
No wonder he’d want you as his wife.
That’s not why I decided to marry her.
If that’s what I wanted,
a housekeeper would have been fine.
But there aren’t many girls
who can cook like this.
On top of that,
it must’ve been a lot of work
to make this place so livable
so soon after moving.
Actually, I had a professional coordinator
do the interior design before I moved in.
But I found it difficult to express
the image I had in mind,
so it ended up looking a bit over the top.
I see.
We can gradually change things as we like.
Speaking of which,
what about the furniture
you were using at your last place?
-Did you throw them away?
-No. I put them all in a room for now.
-Your private room?
-No, I plan to make that the baby’s room.
I can use a lot of my furniture as is.
I even had the wallpaper changed,
and the room looks so cute now!
-I wanna see it!
-Take a look!
-So cute!
-Isn’t it?
Thank you, Mama!
A flower pattern?
There’s nothing wrong with that.
It looks really cute.
Like a princess’ room.
What if it’s a boy?
What’ll we do?
I felt so sure that it’s gonna be a girl.
Then I’m sure it will be a girl.
I don’t understand how
you could be so sure.
I’m sorry. I got carried away.
Don’t worry.
Wallpaper can be changed anytime.
And we can keep trying
until we have a girl.
Geez…
Well then… I guess I’ll be going now.
Just ask at the front desk,
and they’ll call you a taxi.
Yeah. Thanks for having me over.
And thanks for the great meal, Nana.
Please come again anytime, okay?
I’ll come when Takumi’s not around.
No way! That would be a problem!
Naoki’s really funny.
I never imagined him to be so outgoing.
I think we could get along.
That makes me happy.
Really? He made me super exhausted.
Fill up the tub for me, will you?
Oh, I did that already.
You don’t need to try
and be the perfect wife.
Let’s take a bath together and relax.
I can’t relax doing that.
Did you lose weight?
Mm-hmm. About three kilos.
Is your morning sickness that bad?
But I’ve been feeling a lot better
these past two, three days,
perhaps because of the change
in atmosphere after moving.
Besides, I was getting a bit chubby,
so it’s perfect now.
I guess so.
I’m sure you’ll get chubby again
once the morning sickness is over.
-No way!
-I’ll bet you’ll become really fat.
What’ll I do?
In fact, I tend to gain weight easily!
My mom and older sister are both chubby,
and my younger sister goes through
great effort to maintain her great figure.
-How many siblings do you have?
-Two!
-Both girls?
-Mm-hmm!
-Wow, that’s kind of scary.
-There’s nothing scary about it.
My older sister is
as kind as a bodhisattva.
Did you talk to your parents?
Yeah. I called my mom.
How much did you tell her?
That I’m pregnant, so I might get married.
What do you mean "might"?
Can’t you trust me?
-But…
-Oh well.
And what did Mommy say?
Mommy? M-- Mommy said…
Oh, really? Congratulations. You did well.
-Like that.
-What kind of mom is that?
She’s that kind of mom.
But I’ll bet your dad
is furious, isn’t he?
Not really.
Right after that call, he called me.
Rather than be angry,
he just sighed and went on
about what a foolish daughter I am.
He asked me what kind of man you are,
so I told him that you work
in the music industry.
He works at a karaoke joint?
Is it all-you-can-sing?
That’s what he said.
So I summed it up and told him
that you write music and stuff.
Summed it up?
Because if they found out
it’s Takumi of Trapnest,
my younger sister will get all excited
and tell all her friends!
I haven’t even told
Jun-chan about this yet.
Jun-chan?
She takes care of me like a mother,
even more than my real mother.
She always lectures me,
but I feel her love for me.
Maybe Jun-chan’s the one
who gave birth to me.
There’s no need to be secretive about this
to the people close to you.
I do have permission from the agency.
We’ve decided to notify the media by fax
when the marriage becomes official.
Rather than trying to hide it,
it’s better to inform them
and request them not to make a fuss about
it because I’m marrying an ordinary girl.
I’ve kept this coming Sunday open,
so tell your parents that
I’ll be coming to meet them.
I’m hoping to discuss details
such as the wedding date then.
We should make it soon,
before your belly begins to show.
FROM: NAOKI
RE: REPORT
I went to check out
Takumi and Hachiko’s new home!
Hachiko is a cute and nice girl,
and Takumi is very kind to her.
I’m sure things will go well
between the two.
There’s nothing to worry about.
Good night. Heart.
You’re disturbing my sleep!
You’ll catch a cold.
Why don’t you smoke inside?
It’s all right. Just one cigarette.
I don’t wanna be hated
by the princess in your tummy.
It was really nice taking a bath together.
It resolves the lack of communication
we’ve had.
Let’s take a bath together again, okay?
You like doing it in small spaces?
You’ve gotta tell me
these important things.
SHIN
Oh, hello. Hachi?
Mm-hmm.
Sorry for calling this late.
You have to go to work
early tomorrow too, right?
No.
I’m not calling
about anything in particular.
It’s just that I haven’t seen you
since the fireworks
and was wondering how you’re doing.
The fireworks were fun, huh?
That was the first time
I had ever lit fireworks.
We wrote wishes on tanabata, too,
this summer.
Everything was so much fun.
Let’s light fireworks with everyone again.
Do you think they still sell them
at the convenience store?
I’m sorry, Shin.
What for?
Because I’m a traitor.
I can’t look you guys in the eyes anymore.
I’ll always be on your side,
no matter what, Hachi.
Nana, where’s the hair dryer?
I’m sorry, Jun-chan. Good night.
Found it.
What’s wrong? Did Jun-chan lecture
you about something?
I just got a bit homesick.
SEPTEMBER 10
8:32 P.M. HACHI
Don’t you ever mention that name again.
Even Nobu has a thing or two
he would rather not talk about.
SEPTEMBER 10
8:32 P.M. HACHI
So that’s what’s going on.
Because I’m a traitor.
I can’t look you guys in the eyes anymore.
I believe people are bound by trust.
I’m sorry.
Please give me Yasu’s cell number.
Reira was in love with Takumi.
Looking back, I know it was
just petty jealousy…
Yet I couldn’t support her
when she needed me the most.
But can't you support her now, Yasu?
Right now, my hands are full
taking care of you guys.
Shin!
Ren, you’re here!
You…
I hate to say this
since I haven’t seen you in a while,
but I have to leave again
right away. Sorry.
Can’t you at least be a little sorry?
Nana began crying all because of you.
It was a mess!
I’m sorry. I got angry, so…
That was childish of me, wasn’t it?
No, actually it’s Nana
who was acting childish.
When I see her at the studio,
I’ll apologize to her.
Where are you going in the middle
of the night with your acoustic guitar?
Are you also a street musician? How cool.
A street musician?
The lonely hero who wanders
the streets looking for love.
That is so cool!
Bye! Let’s play mahjong again sometime!
He’s so cute, isn’t he?
And sexy too.
Don’t you get horny living with him?
Of course not!
But you’ve had enough with women,
haven’t you?
Never! I've got my whole life ahead of me.
To Nana. Sorry for being so selfish.
You probably will never forgive me,
but I will never forget the six months
we lived together.
It will be lonely not being able
to see you,
but I don’t know what to do.
So I hope that your major debut comes soon
and that you’ll be on TV a lot.
Let me see you as you continue singing.
No matter who I’m in love with,
you will always be my only hero, Nana.
There’s nobody as cool as you.
Until now… and from here on.
P.S. UNTIL YOU FIND A NEW ROOMMATE,
PLEASE LET ME CONTINUE PAYING
FOR MY SHARE OF THE APARTMENT.
I WILL LOCK THE DOOR ON MY WAY OUT.
I'LL SEE TO IT THAT REN GETS MY KEY.
Why are you so sad?
This is not a break-up letter
but a passionate love letter.
You will always be my only hero, Nana.
Go and visit Hachiko.
You do wanna see her tears of joy
when she sees you, right?
Why should I have to go see her?
That’s irrational!
That’s what a hero does.
Good evening. Street Musician here.
Huh?
MR. STREET MUSICIAN?
-Are you alone? Can I come in?
-Sure.
Um, Shin… Mr. Street Musician.
I’m sorry about the other day.
I, Shinichi Okazaki, will now sing.
Hey, Hachi… No matter how much
or how often people hurt each other…
loving someone is never a waste.
Even now, I still cherish that
love letter you gave me then.