The strawberry glasses were still
being sold at the 100 yen store.
But when I thought about how
importantly Hachi treated them
without buying any spares,
the cut on my left cheek that
I don’t even remember getting
started hurting like hell.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
That will be 105 yen.
Tonight, I’ll return home
and apologize to Hachi.
Thank you for coming.
The glass probably broke.
I can’t remember,
but I think that’s what happened.
It’s also a mystery how
I ended up at Ren’s place
when I was trying to be careful
not to cause a scandal…
but I’m just glad I didn’t wake up
in Yasu’s room.
I can’t rely on Yasu’s kindness anymore…
because Yasu isn’t mine.
Reira, I’m sorry, but I’ve gotta
get back to work right away.
Sorry.
I’ll come home as soon as I can.
Can you be here on your own until then?
I’m locking the door,
so don’t open the door for anyone.
I’m sorry, Yasu,
to call you out of the blue like this.
I couldn’t think of anyone else
I could depend on.
I ran away from the recording.
Takumi said he’s getting married,
and I couldn’t bring myself to sing.
But I didn’t know where to go.
No matter where I go,
I feel like everyone’s watching me.
I’m scared.
If people found out that I ran away
from a recording,
they’d be disappointed in me.
The staff and the fans…
They’d abandon me, saying I’m finished.
But I can’t sing now.
What am I to do?
I’m worthless unless I sing.
I just heard back from Mr. Takeda!
She didn’t go back to the hotel either!
She left with her stuff, right?
Did you try calling her cell?
Several times, but she won’t answer.
But why did she run away like that?
She was all excited earlier,
saying she’s gonna sell a million copies.
Does anyone have any clue
where else she might’ve gone?
I was transferred here recently,
so there’s still much I don’t know
about Reira’s private life.
Maybe she went to her secret lover!
Come to think of it,
does she have any close friends?
I haven’t a clue. Don’t ask me.
But Takumi, you and Reira have been
friends since you were kids, right?
So what?
Nothing.
What should we do, Takumi?
Should we proceed with recording anyway?
With all this commotion around us,
we can’t concentrate.
We can’t do it.
I guess so.
I’m sorry.
It’s okay, Mari.
Your job is to take care of Reira,
so just worry about Reira
and don't worry about anything else.
Okay.
If you understand that,
then go find her and drag her back!
I’m sorry.
Don’t cry, Mari. That guy is scary.
I’m scared of him, too.
Drinking on the job?
It’s water!
If work is that important to you,
don’t go saying something
that would upset our songstress
before the recording.
If it’s to test her professionalism,
you’re being too much of an evil coach.
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
Don’t try to act stupid!
You know Reira’s in love with you.
Don’t put it so simply!
Years of acting like I didn’t know
just went down the drain!
Acting like you don’t know
won’t solve the problem.
If you get married,
Reira might not be able
to sing anymore, you know.
If me getting married means
she’s gonna stop singing,
then we have big problems.
I have no feelings of love for her.
I can’t help it.
Well, I guess so.
But if Reira won’t sing,
Trapnest is finished.
I know that! So what do you want me to do?
If the lord showed a little more love,
the princess might wanna sing.
Are you telling me to do it with Reira?
She’s like a little sister to me!
There’s no way I could do that!
But you’re not a blood relative.
That’s not the point!
But you’ve always been the type
to do whatever it takes
to achieve your objectives.
Compared to marrying an ordinary girl
who’s only after your money,
you’ll end up with a larger castle
with a marriage of convenience to Reira.
-Castle?
-It suits you.
I never knew you were so ambitious.
I’d never do such a thing.
I’m just suggesting a way of living
for someone as greedy and brutal as you.
What’s that supposed to mean?
Don’t try to act like a good person!
You’re the man who abandoned
your woman and friends!
You even sold your soul,
all for your own success!
Although I’m the one who bought it.
My soul?
You were a punk rocker to the core.
You were coolest when you could play
whatever you wanted in a small room.
Although you still are… a pretty cool guy…
like some orthodox hero.
I wanna hear Ren Honjo’s soul shout!
But don’t you think it’s funny?
The bigger the castle gets,
the more confining it feels.
Before I knew it,
I had locked my cute little sister
in the top of a high tower…
even though I can’t love her.
That’s the greatest sin of my life.
But she only knows how to sing
and nothing else.
And I can’t turn back now.
If only there were a prince
who’d climb up that tower to hold her.
Turn off your phone at least
during recording!
But we’re not recording.
Yeah, but at least have it on silent.
Hello, darling! No, that’s okay.
The Lord is in a foul mood,
so we’re not getting any work done.
He’s right beside me.
Who is it?
The former prince. Though he’s bald.
Um, excuse me.
You’re Takumi from Trapnest, right?
I’m a huge fan of yours!
Can I shake your hand?
Thank you so much!
Who’s that, Mommy?
Someone who sings songs?
Someone who plays instruments.
Wasn’t that great?
Sorry for causing you trouble
during a busy time.
Reira will hate me again for doing this.
But for her to say
she’s worthless unless she sings?
I didn’t break up with her
so I could hear her say such things.
Do something about it.
If that’s how you feel,
then you do something about it.
Being the hated one is my exclusive right.
Yasu, you traitor!
-That baldie!
-Reira, please calm down!
It’s all right! I won’t take you back!
The recording has been postponed!
Takumi asked that you be given time off
until you’re ready to sing again.
He went and talked
to the president himself.
We’ll have to rearrange the schedule,
but at the very least,
you'll be able to take off the entire week
that was set aside for recording.
Isn’t that great?
Takumi may say some harsh things,
but he certainly thinks about you, Reira.
-You’re wrong, Mari.
-Huh?
Takumi has abandoned me.
He doesn’t need a singer
who runs away from her job!
What are you saying?
I’m sure that’s not true!
I’m sorry, Mari.
I’ll return to the studio right away,
so let everyone know.
But you couldn’t possibly sing
in this condition.
Please! Don’t take away my chance to sing!
Singing is all I’ve got.
This restaurant pisses me off.
Don’t play Trapnest songs.
Play some Enka!
You’re ruining our ramen noodles, old man!
I’m sorry! We’ll eat quickly and leave.
It’s only natural that the radio
would play what’s popular.
Besides, it’s a song Ren wrote.
You should like it.
This isn’t Ren’s.
But more importantly,
you need to see a doctor.
A doctor?
Memory loss isn’t normal at all.
I’ll come with you.
No way!
You know, you’ve been rude lately,
telling me I’m strange.
But you were saying that yourself, too.
You could have some kind of brain disease.
You should get it checked.
I’m fine. Darn. I shouldn’t have told you.
Annoying, annoying, annoying!
Thanks for the meal.
Now, I’ll listen to your whining
as I promised.
It’s all right.
If I tell you, you might just
rub salt in my wound.
I wanna hear it!
How could things have come
to this in one day?
Come to this?
Don’t you know?
What the hell have you been doing?
What about you?
Where have you been hiding
since last night?
At such an important time for Hachi!
That’s so cold of you!
As a friend,
shouldn’t you have gone straight to her
and heard what she had to say?
She would only cry and apologize to me.
She wouldn’t tell me anything.
So you went.
You two are both women.
She might’ve opened up and talked
to you about her true feelings.
But when I went back this morning,
Hachiko wouldn’t say a word to me either!
She had Takumi do all the talking.
What did he say?
It’s okay. Tell me.
Nothing will shock me anymore.
He said they’re getting married.
You are shocked! Of course you are!
It makes no sense, right?
I’m sorry, Nobu. Are you all right?
Well, ah… yeah.
I sort of knew it was over
from the way Nana was acting yesterday.
"Nana"?
After all, it’s Takumi she loves.
I knew that from the beginning.
But you called her Hachi
in front of everyone.
But I’m part of this,
so why am I out of the loop?
Am I that unreliable to her?
It’s okay to cry, Nobu!
Cry on my shoulder!
What the hell?
This is no time to be embarrassed!
It’s just between us.
But people are staring…
So what? You’re too short
to be acting cool anyway!
Don’t call me short!
At least I’m taller than you!
I know that!
I also know that you’ve got a heart
way bigger than mine!
Before I met you, I hated everyone!
I couldn’t trust anybody!
But then when I met you,
I felt for the first time that this world
isn’t all that bad!
Terashima. Thanks for these.
You are not unreliable, Nobu.
Don’t get down on yourself just
because some girl dumped you.
Your spikes are digging into my neck.
Nobu’s shoulders are
way scrawnier than Ren’s,
but they weren’t shaking.
I was offering him my shoulder
but ended up borrowing his instead.
I owe Nobu so much.
I really can’t make up with Hachi.
I’ll take the strawberry glass
to Ren’s place.
We can’t use these!
How could you stick with them
for a full month
and not get a shot of them together?
Because they’re
on completely different schedules,
and they never leave together, you see!
Don’t "you see" me!
You probably did something
to make them cautious.
All of you are idiots!
Let’s just give up on that
and write an article
using two different shots.
I’m not compromising.
You want someone else beating us
to the story?
Kurata. Fly to their hometown immediately.
Huh?
Trapnest is recording in the studio
every day this week.
Following them won’t do us any good.
In the meantime,
gather everything you can on Ren Honjo
and Nana Osaki’s backgrounds.
What a drag.
Gaia seems to be reluctant
about giving BLAST their debut,
but this’ll make
the greatest "Battle of the Bands."
I’ll create a huge festival for you
and bring you onto the same stage
as Trapnest in a heartbeat.
You should thank me, Nana Osaki.
The curtains are about to rise
on your fateful game.
Ms. Komatsu. Registered mail for you!
MS. NANA KOMATSU,
THANK YOU FOR CONSULTING WITH OUR FIRM.
WE’VE GATHERED SOME LISTINGS OF PROPERTIES
THAT FIT THE CONDITIONS
YOU NOTED THE OTHER DAY.
PLEASE REVIEW THE MATERIAL.
IF YOU WOULD LIKE…
THREE BEDROOM APARTMENT
IN MINAMI AOYAMA
MONTHLY RENT 1,000,000 YEN
You know, Hachi…
I was hostile toward Trapnest
because I was envious of Reira
for stealing Ren’s heart,
not as a woman but as a singer.
I only wanted Ren to notice me more.
I never wanted to make them my enemy.
It’s so moving, isn’t it?
This’ll sell way more than a million.
How much harder are you gonna push her
until you’re satisfied?
I have no idea what you’re talking about.
At least let me accompany her
with my guitar,
since I can’t hug her.
But ever since that day
when you were taken away from me,
I couldn’t help but feel
the need to defeat them.
I wanted you back… no matter what.