In those hectic days
when we barely had time to sleep,
I had not realized the flaw in my plan.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
So, what do you wanna do
when we get there?
Let's try some real Italian food first.
I looked up some stores we can go to.
Hey, isn’t he from Trapnest?
-Huh? Whom?
-Ren?
No, the long-haired one.
Really? Where?
So where’s Ren?
I’m sick of eating bread
for breakfast every day.
I want some miso soup.
Oh, I found
this great Japanese restaurant.
-Wanna go there tonight?
-I want some of Nana’s salty miso soup!
Ren, keep your voice down.
Ren, you’re better off forgetting
about women like that.
"Women like that"?
While we’re on the subject,
I’ll be blunt with you.
I believe Nana is the type of girl
she’s rumored to be,
and you’re really being fooled by her.
If she loved you,
she’d be more careful
about the salt content in her cooking--
Take, let me go back to Japan earlier too.
That’s not fair only Takumi got to go.
No, you still have your photoshoot.
Besides, he had his reasons.
What? Takumi’s returning early?
He’s already left. Yesterday.
What’s with that?
Why didn’t he say anything about it?
-He should’ve arrived in Japan by now.
-He’s so cold…
Mom, I’m off to check in at the hotel.
If Mr. Ichinose’s coming to see us
tomorrow anyway,
he should just stay over.
But he’ll be arriving pretty late,
so he didn’t wanna inconvenience anyone.
He shouldn’t be so formal.
He’s gonna be family.
They’re seeing each other
for the first time in two weeks.
Of course they want some time alone.
Oh, I guess you’re right.
I’m sure looking forward to tomorrow.
Talking with him over the phone,
Takumi seems like a really nice person.
Huh? When did you talk to him?
I answered the phone
when he called from overseas.
Dad is so critical
when it comes to celebrities,
saying they’re as bad as the yakuza,
but even he was praising Takumi
on his manners.
Really? But Takumi is like a yakuza.
HE’S GOT YOU FOOLED.
Is that so?
If he actually was one,
he’d take over the world.
He’s so cutthroat.
Then God must’ve given him musical talent
to keep him on the right path in life.
The world of entertainment
seems glamorous,
but I’m sure it’s pretty difficult.
It will be your job to create a home
where he can relax.
So stop slacking off and do your best.
Mm-hmm.
By the way, how’s Nana doing?
Have you been keeping in touch?
No. I heard that Nana's cell phone broke,
so I haven’t been able
to call or email her.
And she hasn’t called me.
I see. That’s a bit worrisome, isn’t it?
Yeah. But from what my other friends
are telling me,
she seems to be in extremely
high spirits and working hard.
Extremely?
That’s my Nana!
She’s a tough girl!
I was so frantic to give Hachi the chance
to see me out there singing.
It never occurred to me to ask
how she was doing…
about her child or about Takumi…
Honestly speaking, I didn’t want to know.
Although that was just me being jealous.
You haven’t touched your breakfast.
Are you feeling sick?
No…
Hey, Mari. I wonder
if Takumi met up with Stella.
Huh? I-- I don’t know.
But we’ve been so busy,
I doubt he had time to sleep around.
He raced through his schedule
for his fiancée after all.
-That’s awful.
-Huh?
Well, that might be okay for his fiancée,
but Stella has been Takumi’s lover
for a lot longer!
Ah, is that so?
She might’ve even been secretly dreaming
of marrying Takumi someday.
I feel sorry for Stella.
YOU'VE GOT MAIL
SUBJECT: IT’S ME, SHIN
-You sure are amazing, Reira.
-Huh?
To be able to see things from
so many different perspectives like that.
I was only thinking of the feelings
of Takumi’s fiancée.
Someone who can sing songs
that captivates the general public
sure is different.
You overestimate me, Mari.
Huh?
It’s just a matter of whose feelings
I can empathize with more.
I’m a selfish person
who only thinks of herself.
I have no idea how
Stella really feels at all.
How are you, Reira?
Are you getting enough rest in London?
Right now, I’m recording
at a training camp
deep in the mountains up north.
The recording is coming along well,
but we’re forced to run in the morning
and do the cleaning.
What’s that all about?
But in these five days,
perhaps because of this healthy lifestyle,
I think I’ve grown a little taller.
Or maybe I’m just imagining it.
It’s salty!
Huh?
You’re the one who wanted miso soup!
Stop complaining and eat it!
Why is everything you cook
always so salty?
Misato should’ve come along
to this training camp.
Then she could’ve cooked for us.
No, we couldn’t do that.
She should quit school
and become our manager.
-Great idea!
-She’s very considerate too.
That’s true.
In any case,
I wanted a cute girl for a manager.
Yasu!
Are you not satisfied with me?
-Not satisfied at all.
What was that?
Ginpei! You’re a man, so talk like one!
And we don’t need two baldies!
Who are you to say?
You’re a girl, so talk like one!
And my head’s not bald. It’s just shaved!
Well, I’m not naturally bald either…
Oh! Smells good in here.
Ah, Matsuo! If you haven’t eaten,
would you care to join us?
-I’ll pass.
-Eat it.
I’ve decided to eat with the staff
when it’s Nana’s turn to cook.
That’s why your wife left you, Matsuo.
Anyway, Mr. Kawano will be arriving soon,
so we’re gonna skip practice
and have a meeting instead.
Come to the studio’s conference room
when you’re done eating.
Man, it’s cold! What’s with this weather?
This is crazy. It’s still September.
What happened to global warming?
-What’s global warming?
-Read the newspaper.
These facilities belong to Gaia,
and the equipment is all spectacular,
but there’s nothing
but forest and lakes around us,
which makes life inconvenient.
But at least for now,
the press hasn’t come after us,
so it’s a lot more peaceful
than being in Tokyo.
Above all, I appreciate the clean air
and seeing the sky full of stars at night.
For some reason,
whenever I see something that sparkles,
I’m reminded of you, Reira. I wonder why.
I really don’t know.
Guerrilla gigs?
Yeah. Five locations in Tokyo,
starting on the tenth of next month.
Shinjuku, Yoyogi, Ikebukuro,
Ueno, and Shibuya.
We’ll be setting up a special stage
in spots with lots of pedestrian traffic.
Yay! Live performances!
But won’t we get in trouble
with the police?
No. Of course we’ve obtained permits
for the locations.
We’re just not announcing to the public
that we’ll be having
these live performances.
I’m sure you’re sick of dealing
with the cops, right, leader?
So, our audience is
the street pedestrians.
But we’ll have
20 part-time paid applauders.
We don’t need your hired applauders!
Oh no, you must have applauders.
Japanese crowds are
so hard to get fired up.
Stop talking, you!
Just think of them as promoters
for when a new store opens.
-It’s just a way to draw customers.
-Oh…
Oh my! So you’ll obediently listen
to what Yasu says.
You aren’t actually together, are you?
-I’ll kill you, buzzcut!
-Oh, bring it on!
-Wow, nice muscles, Ginpei!
-S-- Sorry…
That’s okay, as long as you understand.
Come to think of it,
you may not know being overseas, Reira,
but the coverage in the magazines
has gotten worse,
and now even Yasu’s being targeted.
Just like with Nana,
they’re writing garbage
about whatever they can.
His past and everything.
They’ve made him out to be
the character he looks like.
He’s got quite a presence now.
I don’t know if it’s
because they haven’t found out
or they’re purposely hiding it,
but nothing’s been written about
the fact that you two were lovers.
So don’t worry.
Hey Ren, has Naoki told you about Yasu?
What’s that baldy up to?
I guess Search published
an exposé about him.
Naoki says there are rumors about it
all over the internet.
An exposé about what?
All kinds of things.
Apparently, he hit a Search reporter
to protect his vocalist
and was taken in
for questioning by the police.
Then other magazines started saying
that Nana and Yasu are actually dating
and things like that.
That’s just not possible. It’s all lies.
In addition, Search also wrote
that Yasu’s not a real lawyer
since he doesn’t have a license
to practice law.
-Isn’t that horrible?
-That is horrible.
-Um, Reira…
-Oh, thank you.
You know, I’ve been concerned
about those rumors too.
Huh?
Is it possible Mr. Takagi never served
as a law apprentice for a firm?
What’s a law apprentice?
It would be equivalent
to a medical intern.
After passing the bar exam,
you must serve as a law apprentice
for a year and a half
before you can become a real lawyer.
You really know a lot, Mari!
-More like you don’t know anything.
-What about you?
Well, it’s not exactly common knowledge.
I’m a law school graduate.
That’s amazing! You’re not just wearing
those glasses for show.
No, there’s nothing amazing about it.
And these glasses are just for show.
Then what are you doing
being Reira’s babysitter?
What do you mean, babysitter?
You know, like changing your diapers…
She doesn’t!
-Enough about me.
-No.
I wanna know more about you.
Are you free tonight?
Why do all our members try
to seduce every woman they see?
Are you Italian?
Anyway, so that’s why
Yasu said he was a trainee.
So I guess he’s in the midst
of his so-called apprenticeship.
But it’s been a year and a half
since he graduated,
so he could already be a lawyer!
No, once you become an apprentice,
you must go where you’ve been assigned.
He would’ve had no say
as to where he’d be assigned.
If he was devoted to the band,
it would’ve been difficult.
His mentor probably
saw Mr. Takagi’s abilities
and hired him through the office
and had him do only deskwork.
-Mari, can you come here?
-Yes!
Mr. Takagi probably couldn’t give up
his dreams for the band.
The fact that he hit that reporter
shows just how much he cares
for his band members.
No matter what the public says,
I think Reira’s boyfriend
is a wonderful man.
Don’t pay attention to the rumors,
and keep your spirits high.
-Mari?
-Yes!
Boyfriend?
What does that mean?
Wasn’t Yasu’s dream to be a lawyer?
It’s always been secrets and lies.
Since the old days,
I never knew what he was thinking.
I have no intention of making
a living on music,
and I don’t plan on
ever leaving this town.
So I guess there’s nothing
we can do about it.
If the band is that important to him,
was that just an excuse
to break up with me?
No, he didn’t go that far
for the sake of the band.
This may be a problem.
I could no longer sacrifice
that much for Nana.
I wonder why.
I still love her like I always have.
Hey, Ren. If I died,
would you die with me?
When did I become such a cold person?
Reira. If you said that
you were lonely now,
I’d fly to London in a heartbeat.
I’d go anywhere.
If I could warm your heart and body
even a little,
then it would be worth it.
The way I say that,
you may get the wrong idea
and think I’m a kind person.
The truth is simply that
I don’t have anything right now
that is as important to me as you.
I don’t know about tomorrow, though…
Sorry for being so selfish.
That’s different
from being a cold person, Ren.
The longer we live,
the more weight we carry on our shoulders,
and it gets harder to do what you want…
That’s why you need someone
to carry that load with you.
Don’t you think you and your girlfriend
could do that for each other?
Welcome home!
You must be exhausted from work!
I’m really exhausted.
Souvenirs!
So many!
-Which do you want?
-Just one out of seven?
-How about this one!
-You’ve got a great nose.
-You picked the diamond…
-Huh?
…earrings. That’s a good choice.
-No, I’d rather have this one!
-That’s some tea.
-What about this?
-A pearl necklace.
Wristwatch. Shoes.
A handbag. Cashmere scarf.
Where’s the ring?
Well, that’s different from a souvenir.
You already have it.
Where?
Your left pocket.
A magic trick?
It’s that tendency to let your guard down
that lets men trick you.
I do have a list of priorities
that I cannot change.
First is work.
That makes up for more than
ninety percent of my brain.
Everything else doesn’t matter as much.
But I’d say my girl comes second.
I need her so I can relax.
I won’t be able to care for you too much,
but I won’t let you have a hard life.
Okay.
As long as I’m your number one
second priority.
I’m sorry, but you’re number two
in my second priority.
Huh?
Maybe this souvenir would best suit
my number one woman.
Shoes?
They wouldn’t fit you anyway.
She must be petite.
Sachiko…
Is it you again?
You’ve already given her a name?
And what a traditional name.
Well, whatever name’s fine with me.
Here! Then these are
for our little Sachiko.
They’re so cute! Thank you, Daddy!
So many!
But doesn’t that sound awkward?
Sachiko Ichinose.
It’s like a tongue twister.
Stop it with that ominous name.
You gave her that name!
Reira. The reason I bought
a laptop computer was
because I wanted to spend all the money
I got from you quickly,
but I didn’t wanna spend it
only on myself.
I bought the acoustic guitar
for the same reason,
but I could never become
romantic enough to sing
where my voice would not reach you.
So from now on,
I’ll send you an email from time to time
like I’m doing now.
If you feel up to it, please write back.
Goodbye for now.
We had fine weather today,
so I’m sure the sky will be
full of stars tonight.
Oh, Mr. Illegal Lawyer.
What are you working on,
hiding in the dark?
Same goes for you.
You shouldn’t be walking outside alone
in the middle of the night.
It’s dangerous.
It’s all because that raccoon told us
about the guerrilla live performances.
-I got too excited to sleep.
-Sleep while you have the chance.
Once we get back to Tokyo,
we’ll be really busy promoting our music.
-Wanna sleep with me?
-Sure. Why not.
-That was a joke.
-That wasn’t funny.
Because you’re in love with me.
You’re right.
Now that I’ve laid all my cards
on the table,
there’s no point in denying it.
Was I too obvious?
You’re damn right, baldy.
What in the world are you up to?
I’m not really up to anything,
so you stop worrying
and just focus on singing.
But Yasu…
ever since Ren and I broke up
back home two and a half years ago,
I‘ve felt closer to you than to Ren.
Even when I’m with Ren,
I’m still feeling a bit lonely.
He and I can no longer
become one like we used to.
Why is that?
I still love Ren like I always have.
Mai, Yui, Sumire, Akane.
Names using only
a single kanji character are best!
And it looks prettier with the last name,
which uses three kanji characters.
Like Takumi.
What’s wrong with Sachiko?
No way! Come on and help me think!
But I’m already kind of attached to it.
It’s decided. The name’s Sachiko!
Hey, Hachi.
With stardust spread all across it,
the night sky looks
awfully bright tonight too.
Even now, when I see something sparkling,
it reminds me of Ren.