GRADE 1, CLASS 3 NANA KOMATSU
I am straying from the subject,
but please bear with me.
Ever since I was a child,
my dream was to become a beautiful bride.
There was really nothing else
that I truly wanted to be.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
Wedding funds?
That’s right.
Listen, a wedding is a major event,
so it will cost a lot of money.
So I had been saving up money
for that special day.
It’s not easy for a parent
with three daughters, you know.
So why are you suddenly depositing
such important funds
into my account?
-Well, you eloped, didn’t you?
-Huh?
I’m home.
Hey, Nami.
-Where have you been until this hour?
-Mom!
-I was at, like, a karaoke bar.
-Mom?
Can’t you at least call
-if you’re gonna be late?
-Mom!
Hello, Nana?
Mom, what makes you think I eloped?
-Hello, Sis?
-Nami?
How are you?
How’s life in Tokyo treating you?
How are things with your boyfriend?
Nami! It’s you, isn’t it?
You’re the one giving Mom
strange ideas, aren’t you?
What? Not really.
All I said was you had gone
to Tokyo to live with a guy.
You’re wrong!
There’s no need to hide it. I envy you.
You get to have sex every day, right?
Goodness, watch your language!
Go and take a bath.
Huh? But I wanna talk some more.
-I took a bath already. Where? That hurt!
-Young girls today will talk about s-- sex
-in front of their parents?
-You kicked me!
Hello, Nana?
-Anyway, you’re legally an adult now,
-This sucks. I should’ve
-so do whatever you wish
-applied to a university
-with that money.
-…in Tokyo, too.
Just don’t get divorced
and come running home.
D-- Divorced?
Don’t cause me any more trouble
than you already have. Bye.
Mom?
This is no laughing matter!
I thought she would ask me to return home
because she was worried.
But don’t come running home?
What parent would say that?
I'm not even married yet!
Way to go, Natsuko! What a cool mother!
-Are you drunk, Nana?
-No, I’m not drunk.
Why even ask?
I’m back. I bought you cigarettes, Nana.
Yasu! Welcome back!
You’ve had a few, I see.
I love you!
I get it. So don’t jump on me.
-Wh-- What about Nobu and Shin?
-Yeah.
Nobu passed out on the sidewalk,
so Shin took him home.
I-- I see.
Nobu was drinking a lot after all.
That Shin…
Surprisingly, he doesn’t get drunk.
Is it only water to him?
Don’t fall asleep.
Give me a break.
Let's go.
Oh my, Nana.
It’s the first time I saw Nana
with her guard down and drunk like that.
How cute.
She must be really happy that Yasu came.
She even kissed him
in the midst of things.
And on top of that, telling him
"I love you"?
But it wasn’t as if Yasu was
at all surprised by it.
Those two could be dating, after all.
What are they doing with the door open?
Oh, sorry, Nana.
Having you clean up all by yourself.
Let me help you.
It’s okay. I just have to rinse.
Then give me a towel.
I’ll wipe the dishes.
Yasu is a great guy.
He doesn’t look it,
but he’s kind, considerate, and reliable,
and he doesn’t brag.
And he’s a lawyer too.
If I were to marry someone,
I’d prefer a guy like him.
What am I thinking? Yasu belongs to Nana.
Come to think of it, I have Shoji.
Oh, are you done?
Thanks for doing the dishes.
I’ll be on my way.
Huh?
Thanks for the meal.
Where are you going?
I think I’ll stay in a hotel
until I find my own place.
Shin’s at Nobu’s place,
so it’s kinda crowded there.
Why not stay here?
Huh? Thank you.
But I’ll have to decline the offer.
There’s no reason to decline!
Yeah, but it wouldn’t be right.
Good night.
Why?
I don't understand.
Although she was drunk,
Nana was being so sweet.
Why is Yasu always so stoic?
Could he have a girlfriend back home?
Playing in a band and all,
he’s probably popular with the women.
Still, even if he does have
a girlfriend back home,
she can’t be that important to him
since he left her to come here.
Shoji left me, too!
But it’s not the same with Shoji.
He’s always treated me with great care.
Besides, I’m here now
because he asked me to come.
No he didn't!
I decided on my own to come here!
Well, you eloped, didn’t you?
Just don’t get divorced
and come running home.
You’re wrong, Mom. I came here on my own.
Let’s live together, Nana.
It’s all right. Calm down.
Shoji said that to me.
If I wanted to marry,
he’d accept me as his bride anytime.
I wonder…
Living together and getting married
are somewhat different, I think.
Besides, Shoji just started
studying at the university,
so he won’t graduate
for another four years.
And he’s just as broke as I am.
A wedding is a major event,
so it will cost a lot of money.
Mom's right. I’m not interested
in a cheap wedding.
I wanna wear two types of wedding dresses.
I don’t wanna live
in low-income housing or a studio flat.
If possible, a home with a yard.
Or at least, a brand new condominium.
I have to save money!
EMPLOYMENT MAGAZINE
I'll try not to use
the 300,000 yen from Mom
and will try to keep it
in my bank account.
And I’ll save more on my own, too.
If I keep at it,
I should have saved up enough
by the time Shoji graduates
from university.
Shoji!
I’ll get that house with a yard, Shoji.
Leave it to me.
My head hurts!
Shit. I shouldn’t have agreed
to work today.
Hachi! Medicine!
Hachi! Aren’t you home?
Oh, good morning, Nana.
What’s with that outfit?
I have a job interview today.
I gave them a call,
and they told me to come right away.
How do I look? Will this do?
-Work? What kind?
-A publisher.
What?
Are you all right?
Do you have a hangover, Nana?
I’ve got some medicine for that.
A publisher?
Can someone like you
get into a place like that?
But I do meet their conditions to apply.
The ad says they're looking
for someone who can do errands.
Besides, it’s a small company
I’ve never heard of,
so I’m sure it’ll be fine.
You sure about that?
I hope this place isn’t going
bankrupt anytime soon.
Let me get you some water.
"Let me get you," she says.
She’s even changed her speech pattern
to match her outfit.
But why a publisher, suddenly?
I just happened to come across it
in the classifieds.
The salary’s good,
and I get two days off every week.
Also, since I’m living in Tokyo,
I’d like to commute to downtown.
Doesn’t working for a publisher
sound super cool?
It has the ring of a successful woman.
Ring of a successful woman?
But I am glad you’ve decided
to look for your next job.
I thought you saying you wanted
to live on your own
was all talk and no action.
But now I see you were serious.
Well, not really.
The only reason I decided to work
is simply because I want money.
But regardless of what
my true intentions are,
if I get into a good company
and work hard,
it’ll eventually give me the skills
and ability to live on my own.
That’s killing two birds with one stone.
By the way, where’s Yasu?
Yasu said he’ll be staying at a hotel
until he finds a place to live, then left.
-I tried to stop him, but…
-Is that so?
"Is that so?"
I’ll be going now.
We’ll be practicing
at the usual studio tonight.
-Can you make it, Hachi?
-Mm-hmm. I have no plans this evening.
Then come!
From tonight,
Yasu will be playing the drums,
so it’s gonna be far better
than anything you’ve heard.
Sure!
That Nana. She really is in a good mood.
Her good mood is rubbing off on me.
It's making me excited.
But yeah, now they have
all the band members they need.
All they have to do now is head
toward their dreams full force.
All right! I’ll do my best, too!
Shoji!
Hey, Junko! Long time no see.
Well, yeah. It’s the first time
I’ve run into you on campus.
Are you coming to school like you should?
That’s not nice.
I'm seriously attending classes.
Shoji. I’ll go on ahead.
Should I cover for you?
Ah, sure. Well… no.
Which is it? Make up your mind, will ya?
Use your wise judgment!
All right.
-So is that the rumored Sachiko?
-No! Ah, what’s this about a rumor?
Wow. You’re totally freaking out.
That makes you all the more suspicious.
Give me a break! That Kyosuke.
Telling Junko, of all people…
Let that guy from Kansai
cover for you in class.
In the meantime, you will give me details.
Matsuda.
Have you seen Shoji today? Is he not here?
No. We were together until a moment ago,
but we bumped into a girl he knew.
They wanted to talk, so I left.
Oh?
It's not like that.
I doubt that was his girlfriend.
Don’t worry.
Matsuda, I don’t have
special feelings for Shoji.
We’re just good friends.
What are you saying?
It’s more than obvious.
You know, at first,
I thought you two were dating.
I was really surprised
when I heard that Shoji has a girlfriend.
I didn’t know either until recently.
To be honest, I was a bit surprised.
What do you mean? Was he hiding it?
-He’s the worst!
-That’s not it!
I assumed on my own that
he didn’t have one!
Don’t cover for him. You’re so sweet.
Come on, have a seat, Sachiko.
Forget about Shoji and go out with me.
Sorry, but I’m not attending this class.
Besides, you have a girlfriend back home,
don’t you?
Shoji told me.
That guy. Going around disclosing
other people’s secrets and not his.
I’ll get you for this, Shoji.
You really are the worst!
I have lost all respect for you!
I just didn’t get a chance
to talk about it.
-I wasn’t necessarily hiding it.
-Don’t make excuses!
You were planning on two-timing them,
weren't you?
Junko! Do you think I’m capable
of doing something like that?
Of course not!
Yet you got greedy and ended up
breaking somebody's heart.
Do you think… she’s hurt?
Of course she’s hurt!
Sachiko’s in love with you, right?
But maybe I’m just hoping that she is.
She hasn’t actually told me
that she likes me.
And nothing has changed since.
We still continue seeing each other
as no more than friends.
Your intellectual level has remained
the same since junior high.
-This is nonsense!
-Junko! Don’t talk to me like that!
What should I do to make things right?
You have to put an end to this.
If you keep spending time with her,
you’ll continue hurting her
until it becomes unbearable.
But we attend the same classes,
and we work at the same workplace.
How am I supposed to put an end to it?
Actually, before you
concern yourself with Sachiko,
shouldn’t you be thinking
about Nana instead?
Huh?
So Sachiko’s more important
to you than Nana.
That’s not true!
I haven’t done anything that
needs explaining to Nana.
But Nana seems to suspect you and Sachiko.
-Huh?
-I heard her mumbling about Sachiko.
She said something about her working
for her Demon Lord or something.
Oh. You’ve got it wrong.
That’s the virtual Sachiko.
Huh? What do you mean, virtual Sachiko?
I have no idea. In fact, I’d like to know.
You know, Shoji,
I can perfectly understand that
you’re exhausted being with Nana,
and you look for comfort through Sachiko.
-Comfort?
-That’s it, Junko. That’s exactly it.
I feel comfort whenever I’m with Sachiko.
But you knew that Nana’s
an exhausting woman in that way
and still you went after her.
So don’t run away now.
Diligently stick with her!
Of course, that’s what I intend to do!
I’m committed in this relationship
enough to make Nana my wife.
Eventually, I wanna share
a grave with her.
You’re taking this too far.
You’ll never rest in peace
if you die with that believer
of the Demon Lord.
Junko! Whose side are you on?
Neither really.
You could say I’m on the side of justice.
What does she mean, justice?
She’s making fun of me.
This coming from a former delinquent.
One day, I’m gonna show everyone
pictures of you from junior high.
Why are you here?
Shoji… Thank goodness.
I was looking for you.
Here’s the book I borrowed.
I wanted to hurry and return it to you.
Thank you very much.
Oh. Anytime would’ve been fine.
You could’ve even given it to me at work.
You’re right. I’m sorry.
No, there’s no need to apologize.
So, how long have you been standing here?
I’m sorry! I didn’t mean to eavesdrop,
but given the content
of the conversation, I just froze.
Never mind that!
How long have you been here?
Of course she’s hurt!
Sachiko’s in love with you, right?
Shoji! I’m sorry. Are you all right?
Ah, yeah. Just so we’re clear,
I didn’t stumble like that to try
and make you laugh or anything.
I’m really sorry.
No, Sach… you don’t have to apologize.
I’m the one at fault.
I’m at fault! Bye!
This is bad. This is worse than bad.
What am I gonna do?
I have to think this through seriously.
If you keep spending time with her,
you’ll continue hurting her
until it becomes unbearable.
But it would be cowardly
to run away from it like this,
right, Koichi Sato?
-Huh?
-Nothing. I’m talking to myself.
What do you mean?
After calling a person by his full name.
Besides, Shoji,
I thought you had class today.
If you’re already cutting class
to come here and drink at this early hour,
I’d say your future isn’t looking
too good.
That’s right.
What am I doing here at Jackson’s?
I see. So this is what escaping
from one’s troubles is like.
Then I’m already running away.
So Sachiko’s more important
to you than Nana.
You’re wrong!
Koichi Sato, I’m going to work!
I’m gonna break ties with her!
I'll do whatever it takes
to be with Nana forever.
Ever since I first met her,
I was planning not to hang out
with her much.
So what am I doing,
feeling comforted by her?
That’s exactly what the Demon Lord wants.
It won’t happen.
I definitely won’t betray Nana.
Why are you changing into your sneakers,
Ms. Kawamura?
Because I have to run for the last train.
Right. That makes sense.
-Sorry to keep you. Let’s hurry.
-Wait, Sachiko!
I have to talk to you about something.
Don’t make such a face.
I won’t look at her face.
I’ll talk as we walk,
so will you please listen?
If we miss the last train,
I’ll pay for a taxi.
So, how am I supposed to end this?
What am I supposed to tell her? How?
She’s my friend
and not my girlfriend to start with.
So asking her to break up with me
would be odd.
Do I say we’re no longer friends?
But why should I have to say that?
Sachiko hasn’t done anything wrong.
Or rather, she’s a really great girl.
What am I doing?
Anyway, I must say something.
You know…
-Sorry. I’m really sorry.
-You’ve done nothing wrong, Shoji.
I jumped to conclusions on my own
and got carried away.
I will be careful not to interfere.
I will never interfere
in your relationship with your girlfriend.
So… please… Can’t we at least be friends?
Don’t ask me to end this.
That’s strange.
Huh?
Shoji should be done with work,
but I get his answering machine.
Did he forget to turn his phone on?
I want to hurry and tell him
that I got a new job.
He’s probably cheating on you.
Shoji wouldn’t do such a thing!
I’ll send him an email.
I wonder what kind of company would hire
a woman like you…
They must really be understaffed.
But you know, I’ll learn the job
while doing errands,
and if I am fully capable,
they’ll hire me permanently.
So I’ll do my best.
Wow. You seem awfully motivated.
If I work hard, I will get a bonus,
which will get me a step closer
to buying a house with a yard.
A house with a yard? Is that your dream?
Yup! A great big dream!
Then I’ll build you a home
with the money I get from my songs.
Huh?
But your room will be the doghouse.
If Nana was a guy,
she would be the love of my life.
Back then, I often thought that.
However, if that were the case,
I doubt we would’ve been left
with only happy memories.
Because love and pain go hand in hand.
The deeper you fall,
the more painful it gets.