Back then, I wasn’t really able
to love someone properly.
Yet I couldn’t help but want to be loved.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
What’s that supposed to mean?
You went to Nana’s place
because you were worried, right?
Then what good will lecturing her do?
But it just came out that way.
How can you say things so bluntly
to someone whose heart’s been shattered?
But I did it for Nana’s sake.
If so, you could’ve chosen a better time.
But there’s meaning in talking to her
about it now after what happened.
Welcome.
What? Hey Nobu, where’s Koichi Sato?
He caught a cold, so he’s off today.
Really? I guess, with the change
in temperature lately…
-Could we have two beers?
-Sure.
What are you doing
sneaking around like that, Shoji?
Don’t worry about me. My character
disappeared in the last episode.
You definitely didn’t disappear.
-I can see you just fine.
-That’s not possible…
-Drink with us.
-Watch it!
How naive of you.
You deserve to experience being
that character who gets hated
and despised by viewers
but still needs to make appearances.
I shouldn’t have come to Jackson’s.
What about work? Do you have the day off?
No, sir. If you must know,
I have the evenings off during
the "Golden Week" holidays.
Just talk normally.
I went to see Nana.
She really hates you,
so I suggest you don’t try to fix things
and just keep a low profile.
What do you mean by "fix things"?
Well, because Shoji says
he hates breaking up like this
and wants to talk things over with Nana.
-What does he want to talk to her about?
-Some excuses, perhaps?
No, it’s not like I wanna make excuses…
It’s just, I think
I should properly apologize to her.
Not a good idea!
If you have no intention
of getting back together with Nana,
you should clearly end this relationship!
You’ve gotta realize it’s your attitude,
trying to hold on to them both,
that hurt both Nana and Sachiko.
You still haven’t learned your lesson!
I don’t think you wanna apologize
to Nana out of kindness.
By apologizing,
you just wanna feel better about yourself.
Kyosuke, you’re being just as blunt,
you know.
Yeah? It’s ok.
My motto is to be kind to women,
strict towards men.
Nobu, I’ll leave the money here.
-You running away?
-No. You’re absolutely right.
-So on that note, I’m gonna disappear.
-Where to?
What are those flowers?
Don’t worry about it. Bye.
-Oh, Shoji!
-What?
Please, just let me leave.
That hat belongs to the store.
Thank you very much.
That was lame.
Apparently,
it’s his girlfriend’s birthday.
Sachiko’s? Oh, so that’s
what the flowers were for.
He was saying she’s working now,
but it’ll be her birthday at midnight,
so he wanted to be the first
to wish her a happy birthday.
That kid’s got a kind heart.
Well, well. He’s being all lovey-dovey
where we can’t see him.
Good for him.
That’s how it should be,
for Sachiko’s sake.
Oh, hello.
The main issue is with Nana,
especially with you lecturing her.
I just hope she’s still alive.
She’ll be fine! Tomorrow’s the day
of her roommate’s live concert.
She was really looking forward to that,
so she’ll be alive until then.
Besides, I promised her that
we’d drive her there in the evening.
But she might die after that.
Farewell.
Then that’ll probably also mean
the end of this series.
And I was so thrilled that
I started crying!
It’s the first row!
The first row at a Trapnest concert!
I get to see Takumi in person
from that close!
I feel so great I could just die!
Farewell…
But I can’t do that.
If I die, I can’t see him.
So there’s no way I can die until then.
-Thank goodness for that.
Hey, if by any chance
Nana can’t come along,
you wanna come with me, Jun-chan?
Well… even in the front row,
I’m not particularly a fan of Trapnest.
Why not go? It’s just a live concert.
That’s no fun.
That’s exactly what Nana said.
She says "I’ll come if I’m in the mood",
then learning that the concert hall’s
far away, she says, "That’s such a drag."
-Far? Where exactly is it?
-At the Idea Hall.
-Idea Hall? You mean that place back home?
-Mm-hmm!
What? Why didn’t you get
tickets to the Tokyo performance?
Because back when I ordered them,
I still wasn’t sure
if I’d be able to come to Tokyo.
On top of that,
given the popularity of Trapnest,
even fan club members have a hard time
getting tickets for the Tokyo concert.
It would be totally sad
if I couldn’t get seats.
But I was sure I could get two tickets
for the concert back home.
And I figured I’d see them better than
from seats in Tokyo’s bigger concert hall.
I’m not going! It would be such a drag.
How come? You could also visit your folks,
so you’d be killing two birds
with one stone.
I don’t wanna visit my folks!
They’d only put me to work
in those rice fields!
Fine, then. I’ll ask Nana again.
She may talk in an unfriendly tone,
but inside, she’s really kind.
I’m sure she’ll agree to come.
You know, I’d think twice
about pressuring her to go.
Why not find a guy who’s a Trapnest fan
and go with him?
Yeah.
You’ll have a new boyfriend,
and you get to go to the concert.
That’s killing two birds with one stone.
I don’t want a boyfriend.
I’m through with love.
What are we gonna do?
You take love away from Nana,
and she’s got nothing left.
I have Nana, after all.
As long as I’m with Nana,
I won’t feel lonely.
Since we’re both women, we can be
ourselves in front of each other.
There’s no need to be jealous.
We can always be together
without worrying about that kinda stuff.
In comparison, love is
tiresome, hurtful, and never lasts.
I’ve had enough of it.
What I want is not a boyfriend
but a knight who will protect me.
But I know very well that
in the real world,
such a person doesn’t exist.
-This is loud!
No way, it’s a full house!
I wanted to see them up close!
We should’ve come sooner!
What kind of event is this, anyway?
"Punk Night"?
-They’re all punk bands?
-What a dull title.
I think Nana’s band is after this one!
I’m gonna force my way to the front!
Hey, Nana, do you want a drink?
I don’t want one!
It’ll only get in the way!
Ow!
Oh, no, I can’t get through!
What is this weird vibe?
I can’t get into mood.
That singer’s not at all cool.
Thanks!
Lose some weight, man.
I guess they’re finished.
Nana’s next.
This is my chance to get closer.
Hey, wanna stick around for the next one?
"Black Stones"? Don’t know them.
"BLAST" for short? How lame.
How dare you!
Let’s go outside for a smoke.
The main guys have already performed.
Let’s go home!
Let’s go for a drink.
How come? Wait a minute,
everyone, don’t leave yet.
Hey, have you heard?
The next band is super cool!
What a cute girl.
Yes, I know! Blast is really cool!
There’s a girl who’s into them.
Especially the vocalist, Nana!
She’s so powerful for a young woman!
Really? Is the next band a girl band?
Ah, no. The vocalist is a woman,
but the drummer and guitarist
play like pros.
This is their first concert in Tokyo,
but they were quite famous
back in their hometown.
-Wanna check them out?
-Sure.
Your blonde curls are really cute.
Are they fake?
No, they’re real.
Who is this girl?
Hey, you know,
I hear the next band is pretty good.
Huh? Really?
Why not stay just for the beginning?
Hey, they’re saying that the next band’s
really great. Let’s hear them play.
They’re that great?
In that case, let’s hear them.
-Are they?
-Well, I don’t know, but…
If they don’t perform well,
this could be embarrassing.
Looks like a lot of the people
have returned.
-Um…
-They’re coming!
What am I gonna do?
I’m getting really nervous.
My heart is beating so hard
that it could tear apart.
Hey, look at them.
That band looks pretty hot.
Yeah, but a band should be credited
not for its looks but for its sound.
What’s this? The floor is shaking.
Nana!
Good evening. We’re Blast.
Back home, she had some dedicated fans.
She was like a celebrity.
I could barely stand on my own two feet.
I felt that I was being left behind.
Nana’s songs all seemed
to consist of that same message.
I feel my eyes tearing up.
That’s exactly how I’m feeling.
Don’t leave me behind, Nana.
What a surprise!
You guys are really talented!
The other performances that
came up after you all
looked like those played by children
in a school band.
Sure, your sound is great,
but how do I put this?
You guys had this great aura emitting
from you when you took that stage.
Anyway, you were awesome.
Thank you, Mr. Kyosuke, Ms. Junko.
Nobu, you can drop the "Mr."?
We’re the same age as you after all.
Really? You are?
You’re really mature, so I expected you
to be about the same age as Yasu.
It's cause Nobu acts
like a kid for his age.
You’re pretty cool
as long as you don’t talk.
That’s a good call to have you
not talk on stage.
Um, Ms. Komatsu,
do you have plates
we can use to divide this for everyone?
Oh, we don’t have enough plates.
Just serve it like that.
-Okay.
-Misato!
-What did you make?
-A vinegar dish and salad.
I figured you’d want something light
after the concert.
Far out! You sure are thoughtful, Misato.
Leave the rest to Hachiko.
Come chat with us.
-But…
-It’s fine. It’s fine.
-There aren’t enough seats. Nobu, move.
-Yes.
What about my seat?
Did you come all the way out here
just to see them perform?
-Yes.
-You look so cute in that apron.
Shin, that’s my apron!
That’s great. You already
have such dedicated fans.
But I’m surprised that you found out
about the live concert.
We got this on a last minute call
to fill in an opening.
Nana called me and told me about it.
Is that so?
I just wanted to inform her.
I never expected her to actually come.
Should I not have come?
Why would you think that?
I’m happy you came.
-Have a seat.
-Thank you!
What’s with that
"Should I not have come?" nonsense?
That sounds stupid.
Does that girl seriously like Nana?
She was crying a lot at the live show.
But they’re both women. That’s just weird.
-I never imagined I’d feel any jealousy.
-Your blonde curls are nice.
I may be the weird one.
They're really cute.
Well then, see you. Good night.
Good luck with your band!
Hey Nobu, get up. We’re leaving.
No way. I don’t feel well.
Nobu really can’t handle his alcohol.
And you’re too unaffected by alcohol.
Hey, Nana. Let’s let Nobu crash here.
Sure, as you wish.
Well… I should be going now.
Huh? Where are you going, Misato?
I’ve booked a room in a hotel
near Tokyo Station.
Really? Then why don’t I get
a taxi and take you there?
What a relief. I thought
she was planning on staying here.
Cancel the hotel room. Just stay here.
That’s right.
You came all the way here after all.
No, it’s okay. I couldn’t.
There’s no need to hesitate. Nobu!
It’s decided. You go home now.
If you stay here, Misato won’t be safe.
That’s not fair!
Then I’ll stay at Nobu’s place tonight.
I can’t sleep.
Sure I know Nana’s not the type that
would force herself on another woman,
but what if Misato’s
into that sort of thing?
Maybe they’ll get carried away.
Nana was kinda drunk.
Her being in such a good mood
is proof she’s drunk.
But how do two women do it?
I guess Nana would be on top…
Oh, no! I almost imagined it!
I’d better find myself a boyfriend!
I must be sexually frustrated,
both mentally and physically.
That’s why I’m having
these inexplicable feelings.
I really am in need of a kind man
who will take good care of me.
But it’s such a burden going through
the process of finding a boyfriend.
And falling in love is exhausting.
First of all, I get too involved
when I fall in love.
I’m so involved that
I lose sight of everything.
That’s why things don’t work out.
It was like that with Mr. Asano too…
I can’t even picture his face anymore.
And I really liked him.
And it was the same with Shoji too.
I don’t wanna think about Shoji now.
I don’t wanna remember anything.
In the meantime,
how am I gonna spend the day tomorrow?
As long as I have work,
I could distract myself.
But I don’t work
until the day after tomorrow.
On the other hand, if I think
I’ve gotta put up with Ms. Sakagami
telling me how useless I am,
I really don’t wanna go.
I wanna look for another job
and quit this one right away.
No matter how much I think about it,
I’m just not suited for that workplace.
But I wonder, is there any place
in this world I’m suited for?
I envy Nana.
GOOD MORNING! I’M GOING TO
THE AMUSEMENT PARK WITH MISATO!
I BET YOU’RE ENVIOUS! HA HA HA!
Why not ask me?
I wanna go to the amusement park, too!
Anyway, I’m going out.
I know. I’ll go shopping.
I’ll buy clothes
and make up and everything I want.
I’m going on a shopping spree.
But I don’t have any money.
I put that 300,000 yen
from my mom in a CD deposit.
Hello.
The interest rate isn’t that great.
-I shouldn’t have done it.
-Um,
-I no longer care
-if you’re looking for that color…
about the home with the yard.
M-- Miss?
Why is the city full
of couples on vacation?
I’m going home.
It’s already seven o’clock.
I hardly did anything today.
Yet I’m really hungry.
What should I do about dinner?
Oh, I know. I’ll go to Jackson’s.
The people there know me,
so I won’t be lonely even if I go alone.
But Shoji also hangs out there.
I'm changing my mind.
I’ll go to the supermarket
and buy something to cook.
I’ve gotta spend less.
Misato’s in high school,
so she has class starting tomorrow.
I’m sure she’s on the train
returning home about now.
Then Nana could be back soon.
The ground meat’s on sale.
I’ll make hamburger steak.
Why must I run into her here?
Does she live around here too?
Or maybe she’s about to go
to Shoji’s place…
and cook in that kitchen…
You’re home, Hachiko. Where’d you go?
Hello. Great timing.
I just finished preparing dinner.
Look at her. Isn’t Misato super cute?
Nana bought this for me.
Wha…
Stop taking them away.
Hachi?
Everyone’s taking away
my places of comfort.
Is this girl gonna stay here tonight, too?
This is my home, too!
So don’t just do as you please, Nana!
That moment, I was convinced
Nana would be furious.
But she had the expression
of a scolded child.
Every time I think back about it,
it hurts me.
Back then, if I were a bit more mature
and a bit more understanding
of your weaknesses,
would our future have been different?