If I saw everyone again right now…
I know that I’d depend on them
just as much as I did back then.
I’m scared of that.
That’s why I can’t move from this spot.
Hey, Nana.
The midsummer flowers will bloom
along Tamagawa again this year.
We’ll all be waiting for you in room 707.
I even made matching yukatas for us.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
Satsuki!
If you keep dawdling like that,
I’m going ahead!
Mommy!
-A butterfly! There was a butterfly!
-Huh?
It was big and black and really pretty!
It’s a famous butterfly!
I saw it in my book!
That must’ve been a black swallowtail.
A black swallowtail? It’s not a butterfly?
It is a butterfly.
But that kind is called a swallowtail.
A swallowtail?
How’s it different
from a normal butterfly?
Oh boy. Lately, talking
to Satsuki reminds me
of talking to Shin in the old days.
Why?
I guess it’s because he was
like a six-year-old.
What about me?
Shin, you look fabulous!
That looks great on you!
Really? How do I tie this thing?
I’ll tie it for you.
Then make a butterfly bow like yours.
Not allowed.
And this is not a butterfly bow.
It’s called a Hanabunko.
It’s how young girls tie their obi.
Really?
Then you can’t wear it either, Hachi!
Shut up.
Today’s the day
of the annual Tamagawa fireworks festival.
No matter how busy we are,
on this one day, we meet up in this room…
carrying the same pain inside.
Ah, that’s enough for me.
If I start drinking this early in the day,
I won’t make it to the fireworks.
But Yasu, you haven’t changed one bit.
You’re like a living fossil.
It’s not like I’d change
in just a few months.
No, you haven’t changed at all
since high school.
So I bet you’d be the same
if you lived a thousand years.
You haven’t changed much either, Nobu,
including your height.
Shut up!
Nobu.
Why don’t you go take a quick shower
and change into your yukata?
Oh, thanks! In fact,
would you mind filling the tub for me?
All right. Very well, young master.
Hey, what about Ren today?
Isn’t he coming?
He’ll be here in time for the fireworks.
He sure doesn’t hurry for anyone,
as always.
Here you go, Satsuki!
I bought you a present!
&lrm;YUMEKO
Yumeko-chan!
-What about for me?
-I have nothing!
Mommy, look! Yumeko-chan!
And she’s wearing a yukata!
RETRO DRESS-UP DOLL
So cute! Thank you, Nobu!
I love this Retro Doll series!
I didn’t buy it for you!
Isn’t that great, Satsuki?
Say thanks to the old man.
Old man?
YUMEKO SERIES 7
Thank you very much!
The flow of time cleanses the past
and heals the wounds in people’s hearts.
But there are wounds that
cannot be healed.
This room is just like it was then,
as if time had stopped.
Nana, listen. It’s about Nobu.
What about Nobu?
Nana?
What are you doing?
Citron bath salts.
They smell great, don’t you think?
You don’t need to worry so much.
I’m fine now.
It’s hot…
I put out a towel for you, young master.
Nana…
There are so many things
I wanna talk to you about now.
But in this apartment,
all I can see are memories.
-What’s this? It’s awesome!
-Super view!
If we can see them from the room,
I guess there was no need
for the disguises.
Yeah.
Hey! Where’s Hachiko? Why isn’t she here?
Maybe Takumi found out
and told her not to come.
Nah. That guy’s not one to fuss over
something like going to see fireworks.
She’ll be here eventually.
No news is proof that she’s safe.
No, it’s proof that something’s wrong!
I have to get going. Everyone’s waiting.
If I break this promise,
I will be a traitor for sure this time.
But I can’t stop crying.
Bye.
I thought I’d feel better
once we talked things over.
But now I realize that
I felt the most comfortable
when I was with Shoji.
We were good friends before we went out.
I thought that
once the break-up drama died down,
things could go back
to the way they used to be.
But now I’ve really lost him forever.
I should’ve treasured him more back then.
SHIN
What should I do?
If I see Nobu now,
there’s no way I could talk to him
and act normal.
I’ll get sad and start crying
all over again.
Those with a record
must refrain, you know.
What should I do?
But I don’t ever wanna betray them
again without saying anything.
If I can’t go,
then I have to tell them that.
Hello, Hachiko?
Nana?
Where are you?
Near Jackson’s.
I see. Well, hurry up!
The fireworks have already started.
I’m sorry. I don’t think… I can go…
Why not?
Hey, why are you crying?
Is something wrong?
I’m so…
scared of… seeing Nobu.
It’s all right. Nobu isn’t here.
You know, that guy has no guts.
He backed out at the last minute.
What a chicken.
So you’ve got nothing to worry about.
Hurry on over.
Shin and Yasu are really
looking forward to seeing you!
Don’t be so cold by telling us
you can’t come now.
I wanna see you, Hachiko. So hurry.
Okay.
Where are you going, Nobu?
I’m going home.
If she says she doesn’t wanna see me,
then I can’t stay.
She didn’t say that!
She says she’s scared to see you.
Hachi’s still in love with you!
Stop twisting things around
to how you want them to be!
No, I just know what it’s like
to be so scared
of being swept away again!
She’s marrying Takumi in two weeks.
It’s right around the corner.
But if you two fell back in love now,
Hachi would be stuck
in an impossible situation!
Of course she’s scared!
All the more reason
why I shouldn’t see her.
Can’t you just get stuck with her?
Forget it.
After all, you probably just wanted
to comfort Hachi
who had been dumped by her old boyfriend
and was being used by Takumi.
-You never really loved her.
-I do love her!
What do you know?
But now you love
that girl next door, right?
I hear that girl has
the same condition as me.
She can’t even go to work
without her medication.
So what?
She’s trying her best in spite of that!
Since long ago,
you’ve always loved helpless girls
who are stuck in some sort of situation
you had absolutely nothing to do with.
That way, you can always play
the part of the hero, right?
Nana, cut it out.
But then, the moment you feel
you’re being pulled in,
you let go of her hand.
Nobu, she’s just provoking you.
Don’t mind her.
What an easygoing form of love.
Nana can be really cruel.
She’s purposely trying to push them
into an impossible situation.
Of course Nobu would react
and get serious from the way
he was confronted.
Hachi’s gonna end up suffering even more.
Nobu is a pacifist.
He’s always tried his hardest to choose
the path that would make everyone happy.
I don’t think trying to avoid conflict
is the same as being easygoing.
I agree.
After all, it’s a battle
against his own desires.
What would you like?
Miss? How many do you want?
Three.
I’ll do everything I can
to make you happy.
I wanna see you, Hachiko.
So hurry.
If you two fell back in love now,
Hachi would be stuck
in an impossible situation.
It’s been a while
since I’ve seen fireworks.
They sure are pretty.
This is the first time I’ve ever had
food from a food stand.
-What?
It’s pretty good!
But it’s hard to eat with chopsticks.
I wonder if any of the stands have forks.
D-- Don’t spoil him! Make him practice!
Don’t grab me so suddenly!
My wig will shift!
HACHI
-Your wig!
-Hello?
-Shin?
-Yeah, what is it?
I'm at the apartment,
but no one’s answering.
Have you all gone ahead
to see the fireworks?
But the light’s on in the room.
Where are you?
Shin?
Yeah. We couldn’t wait
any longer and left. Sorry.
No, I should be the one apologizing
for being late.
I’ll head over there right now.
Where are you watching it from?
Yeah. Got it.
I’ll call again if I can’t find you.
What? You’re dressed as a girl?
Can’t you just get stuck with her?
What an easygoing form of love.
Over here!
Huh? No way! Shin? You’re so cute!
Come on! Everyone’s here.
They’re so pretty! Awesome!
They really are pretty, aren’t they?
Come on, Shin.
You’re sounding like Misato!
What a huge diamond.
You know, Nobu aside, why aren’t you
inviting me to your wedding?
You did invite Yasu and Shin.
Huh? You’d come?
Of course I would.
I’ll even sing you the punk version
of Ladybugs’ "Samba".
What’s that? What kind of song is it?
I’ll buy you the CD
so you can arrange it
and play the guitar part.
You be happy, no matter what, okay?
Nobu stepped aside so that you’d be happy.
So if you end up unhappy,
it was for nothing.
Well, with Takumi as your husband,
I’m sure he’s gonna make you cry
from time to time.
But you’re the fool who fell
in love with him,
so that can’t be helped.
And don’t get discouraged when he cheats
on you now and then, all right?
Just smack him around
until you feel better.
Yeah. You’re right.
Thank you, Nana.
That day, the riverside was packed
with people,
and I never saw Shoji and his girlfriend.
I felt that the curtain had finally
come down on our relationship.
There was such a big crowd
that you could easily lose sight
of the people you were with.
So I wanted to hold Nana’s hand…
But I was worried she’d think
I’m insensitive
if I innocently grabbed her hand,
which was as warm as Nobu’s.
The wind blowing on my fingertips
was freezing cold.
Come to think of it,
summer ended long ago, didn’t it?
Did you guys have fun at the fireworks?
Get ready to continue working hard!
Huh?
Hey, Nana.
That summer you longed for
more than anyone,
the one we couldn’t get back,
is right here.
I’ll always be waiting.
For ten years… twenty years… fifty years…
Hey, Nana…