On the wall discolored by the sun,
the poster mark remained.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
You’re an only child, Nobu?
Yeah. My parents must be crying about now.
Or rather, they must be really pissed off.
I see. I guess you were supposed
to take over your family inn, huh?
How big is it?
A SPOILED CHILD
You only remember things like that, huh?
What’s going on in this head?
But when BLAST officially debuts,
I’ll bet they’ll be so thrilled
they’ll forgive you right away.
So you’ve gotta do your best.
Yeah.
I’ll do my best for your sake too, Hachi.
I told you, don’t call me Hachi.
But if I call you "Nana,"
I can’t help but picture
the face of that cat-eyed queen.
Cat-eyed?
I’ve been calling her that
since the tenth grade,
so it’s become second nature now.
So BLAST has been around
since you were in the tenth grade?
No, we started the band during the summer
when I was in eleventh grade,
but Nana and I were classmates
in high school.
Really?
Hey, how was Nana in high school?
She never laughed, she didn’t talk much,
and she had this evil look in her eyes.
-She was totally isolated.
-No way.
I was so sure she was
really popular in school!
What a shock.
No, she was so gloomy.
She’s really pretty,
so even though she was quiet,
she did stand out in school.
But you could never tell
what she was thinking,
so everyone was too scared
to get close to her.
But when you think about it
in a normal sense,
it must've been lonely for her,
having no friends.
So I tried blitzing her
with my non-stop talking,
but then she just ignored me,
which left me feeling lonely.
So then,
the music-crazed youngster Nobu figured,
"If I can’t communicate with her
through words, I’ll do it through music."
So I made her borrow my CDs.
Ten of them, I think.
I tried to give her
different genres of music,
thinking there was bound
to be one she’d like.
Then she finally talked to me.
Terashima.
Thanks for these.
If you get some more good ones,
can I borrow them?
She smiled.
Ms. Osaki spoke?
-So she can speak after all.
-Wait, Osaki.
What’s your favorite genre?
Which one of those did you like?
What was it?
The noisiest one
with the kinda erotic name.
-The Sex Pistols?
-Yeah, that one.
My favorite’s punk, too!
We have the same taste!
How annoying.
I was so happy.
It was like
being liked back by your crush.
To me, that just sounds
like you were in love with her.
Maybe a little.
You fool! I hate you!
But that happened in the past!
Besides, once we became friends,
I realized that I wasn’t seeing her
as a woman.
Otherwise, I would never have
introduced her to Ren, right?
So you were the one
who brought the two together?
Yeah.
Nana had this dangerous, warped way
of thinking that no one could deal with.
I thought maybe Ren would be an exception
and could do something about it.
For the young Nobu,
Ren was an invincible hero.
It was a big success, huh?
-But not quite what I expected.
-What do you mean?
I realized little by little
that Ren wasn’t the strong person
I thought he was.
Perhaps Ren was saved just
as much as Nana was in this encounter.
You know, when I was younger,
for no good reason, I thought that
guys had to protect their girls.
So I always acted tough
in front of my girlfriend.
But that may have been a big mistake.
Huh? Why was that a mistake?
So you want to be supported
by these frail arms?
Yes. Totally.
It’s impossible.
Ever since I fell in love
with you, Hachiko,
I realized just how much
of a weak, shameless man I really am.
What do you mean?
Weren’t you gonna do anything
to make me happy?
Sure I will. As long as you’re always
by my side supporting me.
With you by my side,
I feel that I can do anything.
Sure.
Nobu loves to be pampered.
That’s a problem.
I’m the one who wants to be pampered.
But what is this feeling?
It feels really sweet.
I wanna be kind to him.
I wanna be by his side.
I wanna be of help to him.
I wanna hug him.
I wanna be able to do
everything he desires.
Until now, I’ve only thought
of being treated that way by men.
That may have been a big mistake.
Good morning.
Nana, you’re back here again.
What about Ren?
He’s busy with work right now,
so he’s hardly ever home.
You left Misato all alone.
Who were you with if it wasn’t Takumi?
Wh-- Where’s Misato?
She’s still sleeping.
I’d better explain everything to her.
But how am I gonna explain
so that she’d understand?
It happened immediately
after I broke it off with Takumi.
It actually overlapped a little.
I’ll think about it thoroughly today.
I’m working today,
so I’d better get changed and hurry off.
Oh, by the way…
Were you able to find
Nobu’s workplace yesterday?
Yeah, thanks. I had to see him
about something urgent.
You two really get along, don’t you?
That guy’s always been
a genuine, honest sort of guy,
so you two share the same values.
Well, from the rest of the world,
you’re like two little dogs barking
for attention,
which is kind of annoying.
I’m sure Nana will understand me.
She had to be lonely having no friends.
Because Nana for sure knows
a lot more great things
about Nobu than I do.
-Nana…
-Huh?
You know, I… Nobu…
It seems like I’m head over heels
in love with Nobu.
Isn’t it natural?
Nana didn’t ask me any questions.
And if I said anything more,
it would’ve sounded
like an excuse, so I didn’t.
There’s no need for me
to explain anything.
I just need to treasure Nobu. That’s all.
And Nana will always be watching over us.
Hey, look, Kyosuke did this.
This is incredibly well done.
That’s Mr. Kyosuke for you.
There’s no need to add the "Mr."
He’s the same age as you, after all.
But he just seems older than me.
Mr. Kyosuke’s somewhat like
a father to you.
Let’s leave it at older brother.
Look, that one over in that section.
That’s Jun-chan’s painting.
It's incredible! In many ways.
It’s impossible to comprehend, Jun-chan.
What is it? Can you explain it to me?
I’m the one who needs an explanation.
Huh? Nana and Nobu?
Yeah. All lovey-dovey.
So much that it’s sickening.
What’s that supposed to mean?
But I thought she preferred Yasu.
Maybe he didn't pay any attention to her.
But she could've told us sooner.
Why’d she hide it?
I think the guy she was hiding
from us was another guy.
I’ll bet he broke her heart.
In any case, she was really hurt
about what happened with her ex-boyfriend.
Maybe Nobu was kind to her then,
and she went along with it.
Yeah. But it was like
she had completely forgotten
about her ex-boyfriend
a little while back.
That’s true. I guess it just shows
that Nana’s ex wasn’t
all that important to her after all.
So you’re saying that
there are a lot of guys out there
who are better than her ex.
Oh, Mr. Ex-Boyfriend,
here’s your Jackson Burger.
Cut it out with all the "ex-boyfriend"!
Oh my, I didn’t notice you there, Shoji.
I’m sorry.
You’re the one who invited me to come!
But we always find you here
whether we call you or not.
Even though you live farther away
since you moved.
Huh? When did that happen?
Didn’t you tell me that
it wasn’t gonna happen
because you didn’t have money?
Shoji left his apartment
and moved to Sachiko’s place.
He made us help him move
although we were really busy.
So inconsiderate.
Hey, I never asked you to,
but you barged in
because you were curious.
Sachiko lives one train stop away
from you, right?
Yeah.
I’ll continue coming here from now on too,
so don’t worry, Koichi Sato.
-You don’t have to come.
-What?
Nana no longer comes here
because you continue to hang out here.
I’m sorry.
Tell Nana now that she has a boyfriend
that she’s all lovey-dovey with,
she can come here again
without thinking about her ex.
I do wanna see her new boyfriend.
Nobu hasn't been here before?
I believe he lives close by.
With his band and work,
I doubt he has the time
to sit back and enjoy a drink.
That guru hasn’t been here either,
has she?
Guru?
-Nana’s roommate.
-Oh…
Is her boyfriend good looking?
Average, I’d say.
But give him a guitar, and he changes.
He becomes this super cool dude.
He’s a mysterious guy.
I guess so.
He’s normally this helpless guy,
much like her ex-boyfriend.
Now that you mention it,
don’t you think that Nobu
and the ex-boyfriend are kinda similar?
Oh yeah, like the way they’re idiots
when they speak.
You think so? I think
her new boyfriend is conceited.
-Have you met him?
-No, I haven’t.
This is according to what
Nana told me about him.
Apparently, he’s the heir
to a Japanese inn,
but he threw that all away to pursue
his dream and came to Tokyo.
That alone would be enough
to have Nana fall for him.
He said something like this
to the guru in a serious tone.
"I’m happy as long
as I can play the guitar…
and have you sing to it."
Not something you can just blurt out
in a straight face.
That’s why you wouldn’t do it.
That’s so cold!
You're no good
because you can't heat things up.
You’re rather the type who acts cold
in order to hide your shyness.
However, I understand now.
I fully understand why Nana fell for Nobu.
That man surely knows how to please her.
He’ll normally be this good friend
who she can talk to about anything,
but when the time’s right,
he’ll say what a woman wants to hear.
He’s the ideal type as far
as Nana’s concerned.
I guess there's more to it than just
Nana going along with the flow.
This may turn out well.
What do you think, Shoji?
What do I think? I’m glad.
I wish for Nana’s happiness
with all my heart.
Are you lonely?
Koichi Sato! One more Jackson Burger.
I’m taking one to Sachiko.
-Welcome home, Shoji.
-A present for you.
You were at Jackson’s again? Thanks.
I’m sorry that it’s not
a Louis Vuitton bag.
I’m hopeless, aren’t I?
Actually, I prefer the Jackson Burger.
I wonder if we were too mean.
I don’t think so.
We needed to put him in his place.
We sure did that, didn’t we?
In his position,
Shoji’s not about to blurt out
that he’s lonely under any circumstance,
but he’s gotta be feeling lonely.
Men can be so selfish.
Although it would be annoying
if he didn't feel lonely at all.
Shoji did love Nana, after all.
He just loved Sachiko more.
But you know,
don’t you feel that’s because
Sachiko loved Shoji more than Nana?
You think so?
But didn’t Nana love Shoji enough
that she couldn’t live without him?
No.
Of course, there’s no way
of comparing the weight of love
Nana and Sachiko had for Shoji.
Just, Shoji probably felt more love
from Sachiko.
Maybe it’s a matter of how
they expressed their feelings.
Nana’s is very one-sided,
so it’s difficult to grasp exactly
what she feels.
Yeah. Come to think of it,
while Shoji went out with Nana,
he would often come to our place
to get drunk and complain about her.
"Nana doesn’t love me for who I am.
She only loves the me that loves her."
"You’re right!" I thought,
and I sympathized with him.
Well, although that likely
wasn’t Nana’s intention,
that’s how it looked like to others.
So when she found out that
he was cheating on her
and was quick to discard him,
saying she no longer wanted him,
that must’ve been a big blow to Shoji.
It was the type of shock
where he’s thinking,
"So that was the truth all along."
But Nana’s actions were more
because she doesn’t take pain well,
and so when she gets hurt,
the first thing she does is try to escape.
I think you're right.
She’ll quickly run away
and quickly put a lid on it.
She tries not to face her partner.
There's always that thing about her
that makes her seem like
she's having a conversation with herself,
even when she's talking to someone else.
But lately, she no longer comes crying
to you like she used to.
Maybe she is able to face her partner now.
Let’s hope that’s the case.
So if and when Nobu cheats on her,
I sure hope she shows enough passion
to go crying to him and not let him go.
Then if I cheat on you,
will you come crying to me
and not let me go?
No, I’ll beat you to death.
-I’m relieved, Junko.
-Why?
THERE’S STILL HOPE FOR US
It's all about how you
express your feelings, right?
NANA
This is the call center.
Please call again
without hiding your phone number.
So she suddenly doesn’t accept calls
from unidentified numbers! Why?
"I hate Takumi."
Ren, the next page.
Welcome back, Ren! I have some big news!
Nobu and Hachiko are together!
Huh? Then she’s going out with two guys?
Way to go, Hachiko.
What are you saying?
There’s no way Hachiko could manage
two guys at once.
She broke up with Takumi, right?
Really? Well, she has good reason
to dump that guy.
-All he thinks about is sex.
-The same with you!
Just call her without hiding your number.
There's even less of a chance
she'll pick up if she knows it’s me.
-Oh, right.
-Hachiko? I thought you two broke up.
Not really. She’s just pissed off at me.
By the way, where the hell is the crew?
They’re late! What do they take us for?
Takumi. We still have ten minutes.
I’M STAYING OUT OF THIS
Stop reading erotic comics.
I just happened to be reading that scene!
Is Hachiko not enough to satisfy you?
No, I am more than satisfied.
Is she that good?
When I talk to you,
I don’t feel like I’m talking to a woman.
But I’m glad, Nobu.
You succeeded in making Hachiko yours.
-I am very grateful to you.
-Huh?
I know that you were rooting for me.
I got this really warm feeling
of friendship from you.
So annoying. It wasn’t for your sake.
Of course! It was for Hachi then!
You thought that, of all people,
I could make Hachiko happy, right?
I sure will make her happy!
It’s not like that.
I hate to say this, but I just used you.
As a way to get revenge against Takumi?
-It’s not that.
-Then what?
So that Hachiko can run freely
without a leash in my yard.
So keep an eye on her,
so that she doesn’t ever escape
to some other place.
Nobu!
Nana!
I guess a person’s true nature
will never change.
She’s still the same girl
with the same warped way of thinking.
I'd thought she became
softer because of Ren.
But Nana’s desire to possess
is abnormally strong,
even with regards to Ren.
I mean, with that padlock and all.
Huh? But that’s because she’s
a fan of Sid Vicious.
It’s just a copy of that.
It’s nothing more.
I think there is.
And she’s even got a tattoo
that’s a symbol of Ren’s name on her body.
No matter how much she loves him,
don’t you find that scary for her
to go that far?
And then for Ren to gladly accept that
and continue wearing that
for two years after they broke up?
I find him quite eccentric as well.
But Hachi talks of them
as the ideal couple.
Perhaps I’m the one who has
a warped way of thinking.
So you’re saying Nana’s met her soulmate?
Oh, I love such stories.
Keiko? Oh boy. She can be a real sadist.
Huh? Real sadist?
I won’t be coming back tonight.
Why not have Hachi come over again?
I am really happy that you
and Hachi are together.
But weren’t you supporting us
because you wanted to keep her
in your yard as your pet?
You talked of me getting her back
as if she were a dog.
But you’re wrong.
I just wanted you to show me the answer.
The answer?
"Men and women are
simply opposing creatures
driven toward each other by lust.
"Can they be connected by love?"
But you two connected, didn’t you?
Well, you’re already having sex,
but that’s natural
between two people who love each other.
So love does tie you together, right?
Try it yourself if you wanna find out.
It’s impossible for me.
We will first have them
sign a temporary contract,
and once details of their first CD release
have been determined,
we’ll switch to an official contract.
I will do my best to make sure we switch
to the official contract right away,
but it doesn’t always go as I wish…
Never mind the details.
Anyway, I just need to put
my signature and seal
on this temporary contract, right?
Yes, well…
I entrust him to you.
Still, I’m a little worried
about the world of show business.
I have children too,
so I understand your worries
about your precious son…
No, that’s not it.
With show business,
the media tries to dig up everything
about a person’s private life, right?
I don’t want anything happening
that’ll end up affecting
my elder son and me.
Well, we thought it best to keep
his real name and profile a secret
and try to say he's eighteen.
That would be--
You can do anything you wish
as long as you keep
his true identity a secret.
I don’t want the world to know
about the embarrassment of my family.
Also, could you mail me
the official contract?
I can’t be wasting time
on something like this.
OKAZAKI
-Now, if you’ll excuse me…
-Mr. Okazaki.
He may not be your flesh and blood,
but you did raise that child
for fifteen years.
Don’t you have any feelings
of love for that child?
Unfortunately, I have never felt love
for Shinichi.
Not even once.
Even though I tried my best.
Ms. Hachiko, we’re almost out of paint.
-Is it okay if I open a new one?
-Sure.
Sorry for having you help
with this, Misato.
No, this is a lot of fun.
Painting the walls white makes
the whole room brighter. This is great.
All I wanna do is seal off my memories.
Why do I feel like some criminal
destroying evidence?
Am I still making another one
of my mistakes?
Hey, Nana…
Mistakes we made
and the scars we have won't just disappear
by simply covering them up.
So I'm still calling your name, Nana…
no matter how much it hurts…
until you answer me.