That night, Nana took Misato by the hand
and left the flat without saying a word.
She didn’t return until morning.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
-Yes.
-It’s me.
What is it, so early in the morning?
Same goes for you.
What’s up with that outfit?
Are you going to work already?
No, I came back from work
and continued working.
Work? But it was a public holiday.
Law firms can be really busy, huh?
When do you get any sleep?
I was gonna take a nap
before going back to work.
I’m coming in.
What are you doing here?
I was hanging out with Misato
in her hotel room,
but a single bed just
isn’t big enough for two people.
That girl’s still here? What about school?
She says her school is full of floozies
and she has no real friends,
so she doesn’t wanna go.
But her parents must be worried.
That girl looks like the princess type
from a wealthy family after all.
Actually, I hear they don’t really care.
It’s like what Shin was saying.
Maybe she’ll end up
running away from home.
Shin… He’s becoming quite a handful.
I just hope he doesn’t get in trouble.
He’s taken on
a different appearance lately.
Talk about appearance, Yasu.
I’ve been thinking for some time now…
you look scarier without your sunglasses.
Shut up.
Usually, it’s the other way around.
Either way, it’s not the look of a lawyer.
Nana… If you’re gonna sleep,
go sleep at your own place.
Wanna sleep with me?
What are you saying? Don’t mess with me.
Then I’m leaving.
Wait.
You wanted to talk to me
about something, didn’t you?
What happened?
Sorry for coming without a reason.
Good night.
Nana!
I return to work today,
so I’d better get some sleep.
Or so I thought,
but I couldn’t get any sleep.
Nana!
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean to say the things I said.
Just, some things happened,
and I was irritated,
and I guess I took it out on you.
I’m really sorry.
Are you mad at me?
I’m not mad, really.
Just like you said, I got carried away
and did as I wanted.
Then why didn’t you come home
until morning?
Nana, you don’t carry a cell phone,
so I didn’t know what to do.
I kept thinking about it
and couldn’t get any sleep!
Am I your boyfriend or something?
You’re more important to me
than a boyfriend.
By the way, what happened to Misato?
Did she go home?
No. She’s at the hotel sleeping.
She said that she might go home
after she checks out at noon today.
-Is that so? What should I do?
-About what?
She must think I’m such a bitch.
She didn’t do anything wrong.
She was having so much fun,
and I ruined it all.
I want to apologize.
Say, does she have a cell phone?
Yeah, she does.
Give me her number. I’ll give her a call.
Sure, but she’s likely still asleep,
so wait until after noon.
-Mm-hmm!
-Hold on a moment.
I have it written down somewhere.
Hey, Nana. What time
can you make it home today?
Give me some space!
Can we have dinner together?
That’s fine with me,
but it’ll be like nine o'clock tonight.
Then I’ll cook something
to make it up to you.
-Here.
-Thanks.
I’m off!
RECIPE OF THE DAY
RICE HAMBURGER STEAK
What should I cook for dinner?
I ended up not making
hamburger steak last night,
so maybe I'll make that.
I wonder what that girl made for Shoji.
What are you looking at, Ms. Komatsu?
The office computer is not
for personal use.
Y-- You’re mistaken, Ms. Sakagami.
I was thinking about a new project.
What do you think
about having a segment on cooking?
The readers of our magazine
aren’t all women!
But in this day and age, men need
to know more about cooking too.
Don’t talk back to me. Besides,
you don’t have the experience
to be talking about new projects.
All you need to do is complete
the tasks you’ve been given.
What’s with her?
She’s treating me like some servant.
Though in a way, I am one…
Where are you going, Ms. Komatsu?
I’m going for lunch!
I wanna hurry and quit this job.
But I need to find my next job
before I do that,
or else Nana will tell me to move out.
But we just made up.
That’s right! I have to call Misato.
Hello.
Oh, hello, Misato? It’s Nana Komatsu.
Ms. Komatsu? I’m really sorry.
I was being such a nuisance.
No, I’m the one who needs to apologize.
-Huh?
-I called to apologize about yesterday.
I’m really sorry.
I was not my usual self yesterday.
Um, come visit us again anytime, okay?
Nana and the other band members
would be glad to see you.
I’ll keep you informed
about their upcoming live concerts.
Sure! Thank you very much.
Where are you now, Misato?
Oh, I’m on the train, on my way home.
I see. Sorry for not seeing you off.
No, that’s okay. I’m grateful as it is.
Being able to have dinner
with the Blast band members
and the chance to talk with Nana…
I’m so happy I could die.
It’s like I’m still in some dream.
You’re exaggerating.
No, really. I’ve been a Blast fan
since the very beginning,
but nothing like this has ever happened.
It really is like a dream to me.
I see. When you say
since the very beginning, when was that?
It was with the first set of members,
back when Ren was in the band.
So almost four years ago?
First members, when Ren was in the band?
No way, it can’t be this Ren.
It was a shock when Ren left Blast,
but don’t you think Shin,
the new bassist, plays just like Ren does?
So at the live concert, it was like
a revival of the Blast of old times.
I was really thrilled.
Name a guitarist you respect.
Ren Honjo!
Oh, which reminds me,
I’ll be going to Trapnest's concert
in my hometown soon.
I’m so happy that I’ll have the chance
to see Ren perform in person again.
That’s the flower of the lotus, isn’t it?
Why did you choose the lotus?
Actually, it’s the ren.
Ren…
No way.
I need to calm down.
I need to calm down and think.
Trapnest’s Ren is Blast’s former bassist?
Judging from what Misato said,
there’s no mistake about that.
But why? Not one of them
said a word about it,
not even when Shin and I
were talking about Ren.
Then were they keeping it a secret?
Furthermore, if that tattoo
on Nana’s arm signifies Ren…
Are Nana and Ren lovers?
They make a great couple! That’s so cool!
I get it! Ren is a popular celebrity.
And that’s why they’re keeping
their relationship a secret.
From that perspective, everything
makes more sense now, I think.
Yasu’s stoic behavior.
The fact that Nana
avoids talking about herself.
Nana often goes out at night saying
she’s going to work,
but she’s in fact out to secretly see Ren.
She goes out wearing Vivienne Westwood
when she says she’s going
to work after all.
Maybe that’s what’s happening.
I’ll bet it is.
What am I gonna do? I wanna know more!
So much that I couldn’t possibly
keep my mind on work.
I have to find out the truth.
But Nana said she won’t be back
until around nine,
and she doesn’t carry a cell phone.
What am I gonna do?
Still that’s no reason
to come to my place.
Please tell me, Nobu.
You know a lot about this, don’t you?
I assure you, I won’t sell
the story to the press.
No, I’d never imagine you as a woman
who would do such a thing, Hachi.
Don’t call me Hachi!
Shin! That’ll stunt your growth!
And why are you so calm?
You’ve always respected Ren, right?
Because I already knew.
Why? Did you by chance become
a member of Blast
knowing you’d be taking Ren’s place?
What do you mean?
You had this all planned out?
No. Nobu got drunk and told me.
I did?
I figured you might not remember.
No way! When?
Right after I became a member of Blast.
Shin, if you knew, why didn’t you
tell me anything about it?
Because everyone avoids talking about Ren,
to the point that it’s obvious,
so I figured I’d be better off
pretending I never heard anything.
I’m the worst.
You are such a grown-up, Shin.
If it was me, I would never be able
to pretend I didn’t know anything.
I tend to get all worked up about it,
like I’m doing now.
That’s what’s so cute about you, Hachi.
Cute?
Don’t mess around!
I wasn’t really messing around.
It’s been a while
since someone said I’m cute.
Hey, Shin, what exactly have I told you?
I’ll tell you everything I know.
Because I might’ve told you lies,
since I was drunk, you know?
Ren was Blast’s bassist.
He and Nana were lovers,
and they lived together,
but two years ago,
he was offered the chance
to become Trapnest’s guitarist.
He came to Tokyo alone,
and no one’s heard from him since.
So I told you everything.
Wait! No one’s heard from him since?
Then what about him and Nana?
They had a tearful breakup, right?
That’s right. And there’s nothing left
for me to tell you.
Tearful?
But just because Ren came to Tokyo,
that doesn’t mean they had to break up.
You’re right. You had
a long-distance relationship
with your boyfriend, Hachi,
and it has lasted.
Well, yeah…
Actually, that came to an end
after I came here.
-You broke up with your boyfriend?
-It came to an end?
You’re kidding!
But we just went to his workplace
the other day.
Yeah, but… somehow, after that…
Never mind about me.
I’ll bitch to you about the whole thing
over some drinks another time.
No. I’m done with alcohol.
Is it something to bitch about?
Did he cheat on you?
Bingo.
A-- Anyway, right now, we’re talking
about why Nana and Ren broke up.
I suggest you talk to Nana directly
about their reasons for breaking up.
No, that wouldn’t be good!
Why’s that?
Listen, everyone’s got
a couple of painful memories
they’d rather not share with anyone.
Is it that painful of a memory?
But if they broke up in tears,
that would mean they were
doing great until then, right?
That’s right, but how can I say it…
I don’t hate Ren,
and I don’t wanna badmouth him,
but Ren decided to leave Blast
and join Trapnest
without talking it over
with Nana or myself.
Only Yasu knew about it.
So at that time, I really felt betrayed,
and it came as a great shock.
As a fellow musician, my pride took a hit,
and I felt frustrated.
But both Nana and I
acknowledged Ren’s talents,
and we respected that.
We could predict that this would be
better for Ren’s sake,
and of course, that proved to be true.
I believe this was the best outcome.
But Nana…
Back then, she could’ve gone
with him if she desired.
But rather than choose happiness
as a woman,
she chose to protect her pride.
I think that’s the reason why she’s
so insistent on succeeding as a musician,
no matter what.
She has her heart set on someday reaching
the level of success
Ren… Trapnest is enjoying.
Shin, surpass Ren.
Sometimes, it pains me
to see her like that.
To be honest,
I'm not sure whether or not
Nana still has feelings for Ren,
but both Yasu and I feel awkward
talking about Ren in front of her.
We weren’t necessarily keeping it
a secret from you guys.
So both of you, there’s no need
for you to act like
you don’t know anything,
but I don’t want you asking her
about this just to satisfy your curiosity.
I understand.
But I must’ve mentioned
Ren many times in front on Nana.
Ms. Komatsu! It’s already three o’clock!
-Then I was hurting Nana’s pride
-How far did you go for lunch?
-every time I mentioned Trapnest.
-My goodness!
-Although I knew nothing about this,
-Your stance toward your work
-I feel bad about it.
-is not right! You’re practically
-I’m gonna stop asking her
-stealing your salary
-to come to the live concert with me.
-from the company! Excuse me!
-Naturally, she won’t wanna go
-Are you listening, Ms. Komatsu?
to a Trapnest live concert.
It’s okay
as long as you’re feeling remorse.
I went a bit too far.
Just be careful
this doesn’t happen again, okay?
That’s right.
In order not to hurt her again,
I’ll cautiously but casually bring up
the subject of Ren.
-Did Yasu come?
-Huh?
This is Yasu’s, right?
There’s no other guy
who would smoke those odd cigarettes
with that distinctive smell.
So they do have a distinctive smell?
I always thought it had
a nice, sweet scent.
Really?
But these aren’t Yasu’s. They’re Shin’s.
I confiscated them from him.
Huh? What is it with Shin?
There’s no sense in me holding onto them,
so go ahead and smoke them, Nana.
No, I don’t care for these.
Leave them here,
and Yasu will smoke them when he’s here.
Wait a minute. When did you see Shin?
I bumped into him
when I was coming home from work.
Oh?
What am I doing lying to her?
I should just tell her the truth.
There’s something fishy here.
Don’t go after Shin.
To him, a working woman is
a woman to get money from,
even if that woman is you.
It’s nothing like that.
Then that’s fine.
By the way, did you call Misato?
It was with the first set of members,
back when Ren was in the band.
Yeah.
I wonder if she got back all right.
Mm-hmm. She said she was
on the train on her way home.
I’m glad to hear that.
You know, Nana, about Ren of Trapnest…
This is about the live concert, right?
Sure. I’ll go.
Huh? Why?
I told you I’d go if I felt like it.
So what made you feel like going?
No reason. Just felt like it.
But…
What? If you have plans
with someone else, that’s fine with me.
N-- No, let’s go together.
I’d be super happy to go with you, Nana.
Why? Does she want to see Ren after all?
Maybe she still has feelings for Ren.
I want to ask her,
but I mustn’t be hasty about it.
Even if I ask, Nana’s not likely
to be direct with me.
She won’t give me an honest answer.
She’ll get embarrassed and say
she’s changed her mind
about going to the live concert with me.
I wonder if I should ask her
after the live concert.
This is a golden opportunity for them
to get back together.
If I don’t watch it, I could ruin things.
We have first row seats.
The concert hall is small.
Ren will surely notice Nana there.
The girl he had a tearful break up with
will suddenly be standing before him.
Ren won’t be able to resist
getting closer to her!
They will silently look
in each other’s eyes.
Nana’s eyes will be filled with tears.
Without a second thought,
Ren will jump down from the stage
and embrace Nana.
Beautiful!
I should keep quiet,
so Nana doesn’t change her mind.
At least until the concert. I’ll do it.
I’ll act as if don’t know anything.
I am an adult after all.
For the sake of an exciting reunion.
Sure. I’ll go along with your story.
I acted like I didn’t know
until now anyway.
Thank you, Shin!
But I envy you.
First row seats, right?
I’d like to come too.
Yeah, I’m sure you would. I’m sorry.
But I wonder if the reunion will be
as exciting as you’re thinking, Hachi.
Well, I agree maybe imagining him
jumping off the stage is a stretch.
Still, I wonder
if Ren still thinks about Nana.
They haven’t been in touch
for two years, right?
Yeah. I wonder about that.
To start with, that guy…
"To start with that guy," what?
Rumor has it he’s a real womanizer.
Really?
Well, but that’s something from his past.
As far as Nana was concerned,
he was very faithful to her.
Oh, and that necklace
Ren’s always wearing?
Nana gave that to him.
No way, really?
That’s a totally good sign
he still has feelings for her!
But maybe he just likes it,
and there’s no real reason
behind him wearing it.
That can’t be.
It definitely means something to him.
Hey, Yasu, don’t you agree?
Yeah, I do.
I knew it!
What’s the matter?
Come on, everyone, practice time.
Let’s give it our best today too.
That dampens the mood.
That was two weeks
before the live concert.
As my heart pounded
worrying about the possibility
of Nana changing her mind,
my imagination just kept escalating.
If Nana and Ren got back together,
would that mean members of Trapnest
could come visit us at our place?
Then maybe I could become
all lovey-dovey with Takumi.
What am I gonna do?
What’s the matter, Ms. Komatsu?
Yes.
It’s me.
You again?
What do you want this late at night?
The morning of the live concert, Nana,
you were sitting by that window,
the same as always.
But there was a different scent
in the room,
the scent of Black Stone,
those cigarettes I confiscated from Shin
that you said you don’t care for.