I knew that Ren wanted a child.
I also knew that having a child
wouldn’t stop me from singing.
I think I just didn’t have the confidence
to become a mother.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
REN - FROM 1:00 A.M.
PLEASE RECORD "HUTCH" FOR ME.
You’re here again?
You’re the one who called me over!
Did you videotape it?
You keep making such dumb excuses
to get me to come over every day!
What do you mean dumb excuses?
We were both orphans, too.
Watch it, and you’re sure to be in tears.
Cry on your own! I’m going to sleep.
Good morning.
How are you feeling today, Ms. Hachiko?
Fine. Sorry if I made you worry.
I think it’s just
the summer heat getting to me,
but I’ll go see a doctor just in case.
I’d better get well soon,
or I won’t be able to go to work, right?
That’s a good idea! I’ll come with you!
What are you saying?
You need to stay here
and finish your homework today.
Please don’t remind me!
Now, stay focused.
I’ll help you when I get back.
Thank you so much.
Also, please don’t tell Nana or the others
that I’m not feeling well, okay?
It’s an important time for them
with their debut coming up,
so I don’t want them worrying about me.
But I’ll be returning home tomorrow.
Will you be all right on your own?
You should at least talk with Ms. Nana
and have her look after you.
Thanks, but I’ll be all right.
OBSTETRICS AND GYNECOLOGY
NAKAZATO CLINIC
Ms. Komatsu. Ms. Nana Komatsu.
Your urine test came back positive.
When was your last period?
July 16th. It lasted about five days.
Should you be pregnant,
are you planning on keeping it?
We’ll begin with a pelvic examination.
The next room please.
Please come in, Ms. Komatsu.
Please take off your underwear
and sit on the examination table.
-You may keep your skirt on.
-Ah, yes.
I don't deal well
with inconveniences like that.
Ms. Komatsu, please relax.
I’ll be waiting faithfully.
You are pregnant.
This small black circle you see
is the sack that contains your baby.
And the little dot you see
inside is your baby.
Now, we count the first week
from the day of your last period
as week zero,
so you're in the middle
of your sixth week.
If you’re planning on keeping your child,
come for another check-up in two weeks.
If you wish to have an abortion,
the sooner the better,
for your body’s sake.
Would you like to take home the photo?
Yes.
What? He grew up abroad? Where?
I didn’t get around to asking him.
So you didn’t know either.
Did you know about it?
No. I heard about it from Misato as well
and was surprised at first.
But thinking back, for one,
he didn’t know
about the Tanabata festivities.
This explains some things
I thought were odd about him.
Yeah, I guess so.
But if his parents are Japanese,
I’d think they would’ve at least
told him about Tanabata.
Are you ready to order?
-Have you decided, Ms. Hachiko?
-Yeah.
I’ll have the grapefruit juice.
-Aren’t you eating?
-I’m not hungry.
Really? Also two mixed sandwiches
and two café au laits.
All right.
Ms. Nana, would it be possible for you
to return to your home
for a while starting tonight?
The truth is, Ms. Hachiko
hasn’t been feeling well lately.
Really? Is that why you look like
you're under the weather?
Oh, but it’s just the summer heat.
I’m all right.
The doctor said so, too.
It's bad enough that
you had to see a doctor?
That’s definitely not all right!
But the doctor said I’m fine,
so it’s all right.
That’s not the issue here.
All right, Misato. I’ll return home
starting tonight, so don’t worry.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Oh, going back to what
I was saying about Shin…
I assumed he was half-Japanese.
So without thinking, I told him
I wasn't convinced that
his parents were both Japanese.
Then he told me
he wasn't convinced either,
that his parents
shouldn’t have given birth to him.
Ms. Hachiko and I were discussing that.
That sort of thinking is like him
denying his own existence.
I’ll come back to get you, Nana, okay?
I’ll be back soon.
No. Denying his parents
and denying his own existence
are two different issues.
Shin’s not a kid anymore.
He should be capable of figuring out
why he deserves to exist.
You think so?
If we put our minds to it,
we're all capable of determining
our own fates.
Right now,
his purpose in life is to work hard
toward the band’s debut.
You’re right! A purpose in life!
-Here you are.
-Me too.
Ever since I found my purpose in life,
to become a diehard BLAST fan,
my life has been nothing but roses.
Roses?
Well then, Ms. Nana, Ms. Hachiko…
I am really grateful for your hospitality.
Please give my regards
to the band members.
Take care, Misato.
Come stay with us again anytime.
We’ll definitely become
Japan’s number one band…
for the sake of your purpose in life, too.
What are you crying for?
You made her cry on purpose.
Come on, Nana!
Misato, you would always come
to our shows alone,
ever since you were in junior high school.
I was always worried about that.
Back home, you probably
don’t get along with your parents
or have any close friends.
But for you to say out loud
what others may consider foolish,
like your purpose in life,
you have no idea how much it means to me.
Please understand that, Misato.
Now, regarding the situation
with Shin’s family…
Am I the only one who believes
Shin was probably a child
that resulted
from his mother’s affair abroad,
leading to his family falling apart?
I wonder. It certainly seems possible.
But why did she have the baby?
It's such a gamble not knowing
who the father is.
Even if the guy she was having
the affair with was using protection,
you can never really be sure, can you?
When people get carried away
with passion and lose reason,
you’re not always as careful
as you should be.
Regardless, whatever the situation,
there’s no doubt that Shin’s parents
are irresponsible.
If they can't raise a child properly,
they shouldn’t have given birth to him.
No, I haven’t seen her since I was four.
She ran off with a guy.
There are too many mothers in this world
who think giving birth is a joke.
I don’t think she thought it was a joke.
Maybe there was a reason
she couldn't raise him right.
Maybe there were circumstances
beyond her control.
It’s only natural that an expectant mother
would wanna give birth
and raise her child.
Why is it only natural?
Well, you see…
I can’t really explain it.
Like, maternal instinct?
Is something wrong?
No. I’ve been so busy,
I thought I’d come to get them when I can,
in case I’m not able
to come when I need to.
Then should I write you
a two-month prescription?
What’s the matter?
Um, this may be
a strange thing to ask, but…
I’m not so sure what people mean
when they talk about maternal instinct.
Is it something every woman normally has?
I believe so.
It’s a female instinct after all.
However, just because all women
have it within them
doesn’t mean all women use it.
I think that applies to anything.
I believe it’s something within a woman
that is awakened
by the woman’s situation and needs.
Then, if for example,
I was expecting Ren’s baby right now,
would I wanna give birth
even though I’d know
it would be nothing but trouble
just before my professional debut?
And not for Ren’s sake,
but due to my instinct?
That’s just not possible.
My stomach hurts.
Why does your stomach hurt
like this every day?
Do you hate to practice that much?
I hate you, Nana!
Hachi would be a lot kinder to me!
I wanna see Hachi!
Why won’t she come to the studio?
Because she doesn’t wanna bother us.
This isn’t some playground after all.
But Mr. Kawano said it’s okay.
He may have said so,
but still, you'd normally
feel uncomfortable coming.
That’s not fair, Nobu,
keeping Hachi all to yourself.
I haven’t seen her since the day
of the fireworks either!
Huh? Why?
We have band practice
until late every night,
and we both work during the day.
We have no time to meet.
But she'd come see you
every night until recently.
She won’t come even if I ask.
She’s probably having her period.
CONVINCED
You went together with Nana
to see Misato off today, right?
You should’ve insisted
on having her come today.
No, she wasn’t looking too well.
What do you mean she wasn’t looking well?
It’s just summer heat fatigue.
I guess that's what the doctor said, too.
She'll be fine.
It's bad enough she had to see a doctor?
Bye.
If you wanna become number one,
be prepared to not take a break
even to be by your parents’ deathbed.
I don't like this strict band…
Hey, Shin! Where are you going?
I told you, my stomach hurts!
Does he really wanna do this?
At least let him go to the bathroom
when he has to.
You seriously lack the sense
of kindness to others!
And you guys lack the sense
to be suspicious of others.
Or maybe Shin's body reacts funny
when the nicotine level gets low,
and he gets a stomachache.
I enjoyed commuting to that
cheap studio we used before a lot more.
I could smoke, and Hachi was there, too.
Like I said, Mr. Kawano…
It’s ludicrous to try
and make a top-selling band
outta some punk band.
I know it’s a dream you’ve had
for a long time,
but during these tough times,
you’ve gotta realize that the company’s
not about to invest in a risky, new band.
But there aren’t any competitors
in the same genre.
If they do well, this’ll be big.
And the sheer presence of Nana,
the vocalist, is simply breathtaking.
Sure, overall,
they’re a visually attractive band,
but punks in bondage outfits
are so outdated.
BONDAGE
Actually, I think it’s a fresh look
for teenagers.
I used to dress like that
when I was young.
I was leaner, too.
Well, we could always hire a stylist
and get their fashion up to date.
I wouldn’t want that!
But the main problem is their sound.
It’s not bad, but it’s too ordinary.
They may be popular performing live,
but on a CD, their music
will lack any true impact.
But that’s where you
as the director need to show your skills.
If we can’t get a decent budget
to promote them,
I can’t find the motivation.
I wish you’d give this up already.
If they’re not able to raise
a child properly,
they shouldn’t have given birth to him.
There are too many mothers in this world
who think giving birth is a joke.
YOU HAVE ONE NEW MESSAGE
FROM NOBU - I’M ON MY WAY HOME.
WE JUST FINISHED PRACTICE.
I HEAR YOU’RE NOT FEELING WELL.
IF YOU’RE STILL AWAKE,
GIVE ME A CALL, AND I’LL COME BY.
If you wish to have an abortion,
the sooner the better.
I’ll return home starting tonight,
so don’t worry.
Nana?
It’s me.
Nana, open up.
Please open the door.
Oh, shoot! Someone’s coming!
Don’t believe a thing I say.
What are you doing here? Go home!
At times like this,
what’s the best thing to do
if I don’t wanna leave?
Hey, this isn’t funny.
Hey, are you all right?
Do you wanna see a doctor?
-Morning sickness?
-I won’t keep it, so don’t worry!
There’s no need for you
to feel responsible, Takumi.
I’m the foolish one.
And of course,
this child could be my boyfriend’s.
Go home. And don’t come back again.
Is your boyfriend Nobu?
All right. I get it.
Takumi?
CONTACTS
What are you doing?
My cell phone? Hey…
NAO - NAKAGAWA - NAKAMURA - NANA - NAMI
Takumi…
NOBU
Don’t tell Nobu!
Garlic is the best
for summer heat fatigue.
Are you thinking of coming with me?
She didn’t call you,
so she must be sleeping.
Let me at least see her sleeping face.
Telepathy!
I got it, so answer already!
You’re so annoying!
-Hello!
-Oh, Nobu? It’s Takumi.
What is it?
-Hey, can you hear me?
-Yes.
Nana’s pregnant.
I don’t know if it’s yours or mine,
but regardless, if Nana wants to keep it,
I intend on becoming its guardian
and raising it as my own.
What do you think?
You know, Hachi…
I still believe life
is what we make of it.
But I’m now able to recognize that
not everyone can be strong all the time.
Because of that,
I’ve become that much kinder
than I was back then.