I felt like such a fool
for not noticing until now.
For example, the number of piercings
they each had and the way they talked.
Nana and Ren were so much alike.
It gave me a sense
of the deep history they had together.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
"What is that padlock
you’re always wearing?"
"I can’t take it off
because I lost the key," he says.
I wonder. Maybe Nana has
the key to Ren’s padlock.
Ever since I found out that Ren
of Trapnest is Nana’s ex-boyfriend,
I took out all the music magazines
and fan-club notices I had kept
and read them thoroughly, over and over.
I was stunned to realize
how I had just been skimming
through the articles until now.
I’m clearly the type who only cares
to read what I’m interested in.
In fact, right now, my mind is
full of Nana and Ren,
and I can barely think of anything else…
even though I’m purposely making
an effort not to think of anything else.
The other thing is,
if I find a new boyfriend,
I’m sure I’ll stop thinking about Shoji.
It would be nice
for such a day to come soon.
Hey, are you ready?
Shall we get going?
Mm-hmm.
Hey… hey, Nana.
Aren’t you getting changed?
Why?
Are you going to the concert
dressed like that?
It’s part of our overnight journey.
The more comfortable the outfit,
the better, right?
Say, aren’t these nice?
Y-- Yes, but we’ve been looking forward
to this concert,
so shouldn’t we dress up a bit?
You’re meeting Ren
for the first time in two years!
You’re the one who’s been
looking forward to this.
Why should I also have to dress up?
It’s only a Trapnest concert.
First of all,
if she wears those sunglasses,
Ren might not recognize her.
Is she doing this on purpose?
Damn, there are a ton of things
I want to ask and say to her.
Is this ok?
However, right now, my top priority
is getting Nana to the concert.
I should be careful
not to be too demanding.
Want another sugar for yours?
I won’t be using any.
-N-- No, I’m fine.
-Okay.
The distance between Nana and Ren
is getting closer and closer.
-I can’t wait to see them.
-Huh?
Your family.
Especially Natsuko. I’m a big fan of hers.
I’m not too comfortable
about having you meet them.
My parents are no more
than your typical countryside folks.
My younger sister still
wears that dark makeup…
And my elder sister…
Nana!
She’s gained even more weight.
They’re identical.
Sorry for making you go through
the trouble of picking us up.
"Go through the trouble"?
Don’t mention it. My workplace is
closed today, so I was available.
In this area, you can't
get anywhere without a car.
By the way, Nao,
could you drive us to the concert?
Sure. Where is it?
At the Idea Hall.
I wanna be there around six.
Then we should leave at around 5:30 p.m.
Yes! Thank you! I love you, Nao!
Nana, look! It’s my old specialty college!
It brings back memories.
Brings back memories?
But you commuted there
until only a year ago, right?
Oh right. But it feels like ten years ago.
What are you saying?
Art school, right? Was it fun?
Mm-hmm. I knew I didn’t have
much talent in that area,
but every day was so much fun.
With Jun-chan and Kyosuke and…
We hung out together, every day.
Oh, Nana. You know, Nami was telling me…
Are you really living with your boyfriend?
It’s that guy, right?
The guy who often came by the house
while you were in art school… Shoji.
-No!
-I believe you’re misunderstanding.
I am Nana’s roommate.
Oh? Really?
You know, why don’t you all come
and visit us sometime?
If you see, you’ll understand.
What? That Nami, going around
spreading rumors again.
She’s gotta be more careful.
I’m glad Nana’s with me.
This place has too many memories
for me to visit alone.
We’re back! Mom! Nana’s here!
Wow, what a grand house!
You’re quite the princess.
Not really. This is normal.
Land is really cheap around here.
Welcome home, Nana!
-How tan!
-Did you get me a gift?
Like a Louis Vuitton bag?
Tokyo is not a foreign country, you know!
Hey! Nami, behave yourself
in front of our guest.
Hello, I’m Nana’s mother.
You may find it hard to relax here,
but please make yourself at home.
Pleased to meet you. I’m Nana Osaki.
Thank you for the hospitality.
Nana?
That’s right. We have the same name.
But Nana’s name is written
in katakana characters.
Isn’t she totally pretty?
It’s amazing how different two people
with the same name can be.
Mom!
I pity you, my daughter.
Way to go, Natsuko!
You’re laughing too much, Nami!
Nami, I found out
you’re talking nonsense again.
Apparently, Nana lives with Nana.
-What?
Why? What about your boyfriend?
Again, you’re misunderstanding!
Are you serious? That’s no fun.
Then why didn’t you tell us
in the first place?
You’re a source of constant worry.
I told you,
-but you wouldn’t listen, Mom.
-So you’re living with my daughter.
I can only imagine how much trouble
she’s causing. I’m really sorry.
No, Nana is honest, cheerful and kind.
Living with her encourages me.
As I imagined,
I can see she’s been brought up
in a very warm family environment.
You certainly know
the right things to say.
-Ouch!
-You still have time, right?
-Why don’t I make some tea?
-Nana…
Here are some Japanese sweets…
-Nana, you’re such a good actress.
-Huh?
"Nana is honest, cheerful and kind?"
I really believe that.
She encourages me.
By the way, where’s your dad?
Does he work Saturdays too?
Ah, yeah. He’ll be back in the evening.
Then I can meet him.
I’m looking forward to it.
He’s not a father worth
getting your hopes up for.
Or rather, I’m sorry.
My family can be so noisy.
I’m embarrassed.
No, I’m really enjoying it.
Natsuko’s better than I imagined.
Meeting her was such a thrill.
What’s so great about her?
She’s just a normal lady.
No, that’s a quality you don’t see much.
She is the ideal mother.
Really? Then what about your mom, Nana?
What kind of person is she?
I bet she's pretty and cool.
I wonder. I can barely remember.
What do you mean?
You’ve only been away from
your hometown for less than half a year.
No, I haven’t seen her since I was four.
Huh? Why not?
She ran off with a guy.
She could even be dead now.
Not that I care.
Then, Nana, it was just
you and your father?
Do you have any siblings?
No.
Actually, I never had a father
to start with.
I was raised by my mother’s mother.
But my grandma died when I was 15.
That’s why I find this so attractive.
The atmosphere of belonging
to a loving family like yours.
Since I never had one, this is fun.
Attractive? But Nana…
To me, this is normal.
Sorry… for talking about a gloomy subject.
No, I was just a bit surprised.
Sorry for asking you so many questions
without giving it much thought.
But I’m glad.
Oh, no, that came out wrong! Sorry.
I’m not glad about what happened.
-That part really shocked me!
-Calm down.
Nana. You've never talked to me
about yourself until now,
so I would wonder why that is.
It made me sad wondering about it.
So I’m glad you shared that with me.
I see. Sorry.
It never occurred to me
that you might be feeling like that.
I never had a close female friend
until now,
so I don’t know how
to spend time together.
I’m not good at talking about myself.
So I end up not talking about things.
But just ask me, and I’ll tell you
anything you want, okay?
So stop feeling sad.
What’s so funny?
Because Nana, why are you
always acting like a cool guy?
You’re more like a boyfriend to me
than a female friend.
You just took my breath away right now.
No, I can’t have you
feel that way about me.
You’ll really tell me anything
I want, right?
-Yeah.
-And promise to be frank with me.
Yeah.
Do you still love Ren?
You knew.
I’m sorry.
Acting as if I didn’t know. But…
You brought me here knowing, right?
Thank you.
Nana.
Nana, I wanna buy a poster
and stuff. What about you?
I’ll have a smoke and then go to my seat.
Show me your poster later.
Do you still love Ren?
Nana ended up not answering that question.
However, I could tell
even without her telling me.
The word love…
If you were able to say
that word with ease,
you would’ve already
gone to see him long ago.
We’re smack in front of the guitarist.
You have the best seat in the house, Nana!
The stage is much closer
to the seats than I expected.
What’ll I do? I’m already
on the verge of crying.
Though there’s no reason for me to cry.
But rather than choose
happiness as a woman,
she chose to protect her pride.
Nana.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the event is about to begin.
If you are yet to be seated,
please promptly make your way
to your seats.
Now that we have our band members,
all we need is a band name.
What will it be?
Why don’t we keep the band name
we had before?
There’s nothing wrong with Brute.
That’s so lame. Sounds too barbaric.
You’re the one who came up with the name.
Yes, but I want to start fresh.
We finally have a pretty girl on vocals,
so we can’t have
anything barbaric, can we?
Right.
Then what about Olive? Popeye’s girl.
Does Olive match your image? I think not.
Same goes for you. And me.
Nana, stop laughing and help us think.
Anything you come up with is fine with me.
Hey, are you serious
about being the vocalist of the band?
Anything is fine with me.
Can you say you’re enjoying life,
the way you take on everything
with that slanted attitude?
I never said, "Anything is fine with me."
Then give it some thought.
Give some input into the band.
This coming from the most
self-centered member of the band.
What about this? This is nice.
"Black Stone".
Don’t just pick the first thing you see.
But it’s cool.
I’ve never seen anything like it.
Are those any good?
They have a strong scent.
Yeah, they’re good.
They’re actually cigars.
I made a trade
with a tobacco shop owner for them.
-A trade?
-Yuck! What’s this? Such a weird taste!
-Really?
But not bad. Black Stone.
BLAST for short. That’s easy to say.
Yeah, that’s nice. "BLAST".
He took my cigarette.
-Yuck!
-What the…
You know, BLAST also
means a strong gust of wind.
Really?
That’s great! That’s kinda cool that
we shorten the name,
and it also means something!
Should we go with that then?
We’re a band of four,
so let’s go with "Black Stones".
It’s an odd name,
but we’re an odd band, so it kinda fits.
Agreed! Hurray for BLAST!
Okay, it’s decided.
So, leader,
how about a celebration speech?
They really went with it.
Well then, band members,
an order from your leader.
From this day on, we’ll all
smoke this brand of cigarettes.
-Smoke them yourself!
Reira!
Why… am I crying?
But my heart’s filled with emotion.
Nana…
That night, I had repeatedly prayed
so hard that the destiny waiting
for Nana after this
would be one of happiness.
That time, I wanted to continue
holding that hand
that I didn't know I was holding.
Always, forever.