I figured if they could not
become pro after this,
there’s something seriously wrong
with this world.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
That day was BLAST’s third time
on the stage in the big city.
It was at the same venue as usual.
They performed the opening act
for 40 minutes.
BLAST is really popular!
The line was all the way
to the convenience store.
Misato told me excitedly
as she returned from buying some juice.
She had passed the line of people waiting
since before the concert hall opened,
hoping to get seats close to the front.
That was the right decision to come early.
You might wanna tell
Junko and Kyosuke to hurry.
But Jun-chan was a bit pissed off
at the concert the other day,
being pushed around by the crowd.
She said she would watch
from the back today.
Don’t push! I’m dying here!
Ouch!
Huh? Why? That life-risking feeling
is what makes it so special!
It never gets that heated
at the concerts back home.
I was so excited that I almost passed out.
Almost passed out?
It was only their third concert,
but they opened the hall earlier than
scheduled because of the long line,
and in a blink of an eye,
the place was packed.
Awesome! Awesome! Super awesome!
Jun-chan and Kyosuke might not
be able to get in.
What? Tickets are sold out?
Wow. Incredible.
We’re all standing anyway.
Can’t you squeeze in just two more?
But we’re already way past capacity.
I beg you.
Our friends are performing at seven.
Your friends? Are you on the guest list?
-I dunno.
-Your names?
Saotome and Takakura.
That’s fine. Go ahead.
If you don’t mind standing
in the hallway way up in the back.
-Hey, do you have tickets?
-No.
Then give up. The show is sold out.
-What?
No way! We came all the way out
to Tokyo just to come to this concert!
See? I told you we should’ve left earlier.
It’s your fault for insisting
on attending those classes!
But the teacher said he wouldn’t
let me graduate high school
unless I attended those classes!
Well, that’s your fault
for not studying hard enough!
I beg of you, please let us in!
Impossible! Any more people
and we’d be facing safety issues!
Some concert isn’t worth
losing your life over!
-It sure is!
-Like I said, it’s impossible.
Nana! Nana!
Crying isn’t gonna help.
Listen… Let these girls go in
instead of us.
The enthusiasm of the crowd increased
with each concert.
I started feeling dizzy from it.
Oh, I’m sorry.
It’s okay.
Excuse me.
But thank goodness we got in, Akiko.
Fortunately, our expensive
plane tickets didn't go to waste.
Say, the people of Tokyo
are surprisingly kind.
I wish we could get down there.
But even the stairway is packed
with people, so I guess it’s impossible.
But this is nice.
We can see better from here,
and we don’t have to risk our lives.
Anyway, what’s up with all
these people right from the beginning?
Impressive, huh?
It’s because they’re good.
This makes me feel lonely,
in a strange way.
With this popularity,
Nana may have forgotten about us.
But she sent us a postcard to notify us
of her upcoming concert.
That was a good call to hand her
that paper with your address on it.
You know, next time,
I say we skip school and work
and come to all the concerts,
even if we have to hitchhike!
I agree! Even if we need to camp out!
That’ll give us the strength
to work hard with other stuff.
At seven o’clock sharp,
the starting time of the concert,
the first one to appear on stage…
was Nana.
Absorbed in the cheers that got louder
with each concert,
I felt that I was disappearing
into the crowd.
Good evening. We’re BLAST.
Damn it, it’s begun!
Hey, I can hear it. They sure play loud!
I wanna go in!
BLAST should play in a bigger place!
Do you know what the population
of Tokyo is?
We should have purchased
tickets ahead of time.
We’ll wait and catch them
on their way out.
-Who do you wanna see?
-Yasu.
He has great technique.
No way! Yasu’s mine!
I’m guessing since it’s summer vacation,
so many people have come out here
from the suburbs,
causing this situation.
Even so, this level
of enthusiasm is crazy.
What is this?
What do you wanna do?
Wanna go for a coffee
until the concert’s over?
Sure. We’ve come all the way here.
Let’s stick around and meet up
with Nana later.
But with so many followers,
they should be able to go pro
without any problem.
That’s it! Their followers!
Misato’s one, and Nana has a bit
of that towards her roommate.
Yeah, you’re right.
Maybe the reason she no longer
talks about the Demon Lord
is not because she’s matured,
but because she’s switched over
to the BLAST religion.
Bottom line, she needs something
to depend on.
Well, at least she’s more positive now
than back when she’d blame everything
on the Demon Lord.
Besides, BLAST is really cool.
I can see why they have
such devoted followers.
Their presence on stage is
out of the ordinary.
You’re right. Especially that vocalist.
You know, I was thinking.
You know how with musicians,
talent alone doesn’t guarantee success?
Of course you’ve gotta
be above a certain level
if you’re gonna go pro.
But from that point on, it’s not really
about how good or bad you are.
Charisma.
GAIA RECORD CO. LTD.
PRODUCER TAKAFUMI KAWANO
Your band has that.
Your musical performance
and songs are exceptional.
It was a wonderful show.
I’ve been in this business
for a long time,
but I haven’t been so moved
to this extent for ages.
There’s a lot for us to discuss.
Rather than just talk things over here,
why don’t I…
take you out for sushi?
Yay! Sushi!
Shin.
What? You didn’t go meet them backstage?
No. They were seeing a guy
from a record company.
It would be distracting
to have outsiders there
while they’re discussing business.
We’ll be seeing everyone
at home later, anyway.
Oh, an after party?
Then we’re going straight
to your place, Nana?
Mm-hmm… I figured tonight will be
a night to celebrate,
so I prepared lots of food.
So please come.
Sorry, Nana.
We’re kind of busy now.
We’ve gotta get home right away.
Huh? Why? It’s summer vacation.
We have a group exhibition
starting next week.
Six of us have rented a gallery,
us and some friends from the Art College.
We’re super busy for the exhibition.
Is that so? A group exhibition?
Like a true art student.
I feel sorry that
you couldn’t see the concert
after coming out here during
such a busy time.
It’s not as bad as those who came
all the way to Tokyo from a different city
and weren’t able to get in.
Indeed.
Here. It’s a pamphlet with information
on our group exhibition.
Come by if you have time.
ART COLLEGE
OIL PAINTING 2
Friends studying the same thing.
Jun-chan and Kyosuke are working
diligently in their own world.
I feel an even stronger sense
that they’re leaving me behind.
Ms. Hachiko, your cell phone’s ringing.
Hello, Nana here.
Oh, Nana?
Good job with the concert.
We’re back home.
We got a ride home.
What about you guys, Nana?
What time can you get here?
Sorry. It doesn’t look like
we’re gonna be able to make it.
We’ve been invited to have dinner
with the guy from Gaia.
I imagine we’ll be pretty late.
Did you already make preparations
for our after-party?
No, not yet! We just got home!
I’m really sorry.
Not to worry.
It’s okay, don’t worry about us. Go.
This kinda stuff happens often.
I’m working tomorrow evening,
but I’ll stop by during the day.
Oh, but I have work
from the morning tomorrow.
What about Misato? Let me talk to her.
It’s Nana.
Hello?
Yes. Nana, it was an awesome performance.
Huh?
Oh? Is that so?
No, let’s hope they bring up
the subject of a contract.
Huh? Tomorrow?
What about me?
Yes, I’ll be waiting for you at home.
Hey, Nana, what about me?
Nana, Mr. Kawano’s
called for a taxi. Let's go.
They’re waiting in the street…
Oops. Sorry, you’re on the phone.
Sorry, Misato, I have to go now.
Say bye to Hachiko for me, okay?
Huh? Oh, go ahead.
Feel free to stay in my room.
The room’s not locked.
Mm-hmm. Bye.
Was that Misato? What about Hachi?
She said not to worry and go.
Misato and Hachiko should come
and join us for sushi.
You idiot. Let’s go.
Idiot?
Good job.
Oh!
Nana!
I live, encouraged by the songs you sing.
It’s only natural for Nana
to treat Misato,
who pursues Nana with passion
and makes the effort to come
all the way to Tokyo for every concert,
more importantly than she treats me.
It’s only natural for Nana to place
a higher priority on talks
with a record label than any promise
she made with me.
And it’s also only natural that
she would choose to be with Ren
than live with me.
It all makes sense.
But if that’s the case…
she no longer needs me.
It’s such a shame, Ms. Hachiko,
after making all this food.
Huh?
Oh, right!
It can’t be helped,
given the circumstances.
Don’t feel pressured into eating more
than you want, Misato.
But everything’s so delicious.
It would be hard not to overeat.
You’re a very good cook,
Ms. Hachiko. I’m impressed.
Misato is such a nice girl.
She is so much in love with Nana
yet will never show hostile sentiments
to those around her.
And she was honestly happy
about Nana and Ren.
She’s a really cute, good girl,
which exhausts me all the more
with my tendency to be cynical.
I wonder if we can get along
for a full month.
2. INBOX
3. OUTBOX
4. DRAFTS
5. SIGNATURE
TAKUMI
A FRIEND WILL BE STAYING WITH ME
DURING SUMMER VACATION,
SO DON'T COME BY MY PLACE, OKAY?
NANA
This is like telling him that I can’t
see him until summer vacation is over.
Well, I guess that’s fine.
Since being with him,
I’ve never been sure whether
or not I’ll ever see him again anyway.
I ended up not seeing Nobu again as well.
And while he was on stage,
I purposely tried not to look over to him.
Nana…
This isn’t good. What should I do?
I’m feeling so lonely.
Is your friend a woman?
Of course!
Really? Then that’s fine. Good night.
Yes.
Takumi…
I wanna see you.
Oh, Ms. Hachiko,
thank you for letting me take a bath.
I’m sorry, Misato.
I’m going out for a bit.
Huh? At this hour? Did something happen?
No. It’s nothing important,
but I won’t be coming home tonight.
I’ll be going straight to work
from there tomorrow.
I’ll leave my keys with you,
so leave them
in the mailbox downstairs when you go out.
Sorry to leave you alone.
But I just couldn’t make it
through the night tonight.
Bye, Takumi. I’ll come pick you up
tomorrow morning at ten.
Don’t you dare leave your room until then.
Yes. Thank you, Take.
Drop by my place and bring me
a change of clothes, okay?
Sure.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Reira.
-Take.
-Huh?
Get a room for me too.
I’m feeling carsick.
The price on the meter
is getting pretty high.
By the time I get there, it could be
as high as my wages for tomorrow.
ROOM 2015. JUST SO YOU KNOW,
IT’S NOT A SUITE.
THOSE ARE SPECIAL
FOR FIRST AND LAST STAYS ONLY.
Which means this isn’t
the last time, right?
Nobu, you were more popular
than me tonight.
-Thank you very much, Mr. Kawano.
-I don't understand.
The meal was exceptional.
How about another drink
somewhere around here?
No thank you.
I have to go to work tomorrow.
Right, you’re working
at a law firm, right?
What are you gonna do about that?
I’ll give it some serious thought
along with this issue about our contract.
I see. I’m hoping for a positive reply.
TAXI STOP
Yasu, I’m gonna take a taxi
with Nobu and Shin.
Hachiko said she’s working
from the morning tomorrow,
so I’ll drop by to see her tonight.
Yeah, that would be good.
Send her my apologies
for not being able to make it
to the after-party.
Mr. Kawano is such
a laid-back type of man, don’t you think?
At this rate, it’s gonna take us
one hundred years before our debut.
Does a man like that really understand
the likes of rock and punk?
Sure, he said that he was moved, but…
Still, he gave us money for the cab,
so I’m sure he’s a good man.
I’m not sure if that determines
whether or not he’s a good man.
Let’s split the change.
Excuse me! Stop here!
What is it?
Work? Where do you get all that energy?
Say hi to Hachi for me, Nobu.
-Are you planning on coming too?
-I’m not.
I give up. There are lots
of women out there.
And I’m pretty popular with the girls.
At least grow your hair, Nobuo.
I’ll get no pleasure winning
her over in that department!
Actually, I don’t think
it’ll look good on you.
Then don’t say it!
I’m back.
Sorry for waking you.
I forgot my key at my friend’s place.
REN'S PLACE?
No, it's fine. I was still awake.
What about Hachi? Has she gone to bed?
Ah…
Ms. Hachiko went out a short while ago.
Huh? Where could she have gone
at this hour?
I’m not sure,
but she suddenly left in a flurry,
saying she wouldn’t be returning tonight.
I might’ve done something
to upset her again.
No, it’s not that. I’m sure it’s a guy.
I’ll bet she went to see her boyfriend.
-Don’t worry.
-Huh?
-Is the beer cold?
-Yes.
So Ms. Hachiko has a boyfriend?
Why? Does it surprise you?
Yes!
"Yes," she says.
Because to me, it seemed that
Ms. Hachiko thinks only of you, Nana.
There’s no way.
But I think only of you, Nana.
Making remarks like that as
if it were impossible hurts my feelings.
I’m sorry.
What’s this?
Oh, it’s a microwave.
Well, I can tell that
by looking at it, but…
She said she got a loan to buy it.
Apparently, that was the only place
she could put it.
If she had that kind of money,
why not get an air conditioner?
Geez, that Hachi.
Say, what’s with this mountain
of leftovers in the fridge?
That… Actually, Ms. Hachiko figured
tonight would be a night to celebrate,
and she had already prepared this
before I arrived here.
Did you already make preparations
for our after-party?
No, not yet. Don’t worry about us and go.
I’m sorry.
No, you couldn’t help it, Nana.
Um, so how did it go
with the record company?
Hey, Nana…
For instance, if we were lovers,
would we have been able to fill
the gap between us with a hug?
Or… does everyone endure this loneliness?
It’s not that I wanted
to keep you all to myself, Nana.
I just wanted to be needed by you.