In the summer when I was 16,
I changed my brand of cigarettes
to Seven Stars
because Ren smoked them.
I increased my number
of piercings to match his
and I wore matching boots.
We slept in the same bed,
and we dreamt the same dream.
Still, Ren left me behind.
Perhaps, somewhere deep in my heart,
I had not forgiven him for that…
the same way that
I couldn’t forgive my mother.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
I’m so weak willed.
This is already my fifth one.
I could only manage to quit
for three months.
But I need something to relax me.
I wonder what happened to Nobu after that.
I came down hard on him,
saying some merciless things.
I’ll apologize to him
when I see him at work.
But… will he come?
06:42 AM
I’m so sleepy.
I’m not in the mood to go to work.
But I have to make a living.
It does help to not have to pay
for the studio,
but how much longer will it take
for things to start moving
towards our debut?
I wonder if Hachi’s asleep.
Takumi has recording,
so he would’ve left by now.
Welcome home.
Don’t ignore me!
Come here and have a seat.
I have something important
to discuss with you.
I’ve gotta get changed and go to work.
Then come out after you get changed.
It won’t take much time.
And put out that cigarette, okay?
It’s bad for the baby.
Calm down.
I've decided to watch over Hachi gently
no matter what she decides to do.
You want something to drink?
We’ve decided to get married.
Get married?
So, I’ve gotta first talk this over
with my agent
on how we should proceed with this,
but I wanna hurry
and find a new place for her.
This place has no elevator,
which is hard on a pregnant woman.
And she has a tendency to be careless,
so it has to be a place with security.
So, I’m sorry but…
could you find a new roommate?
What the hell?
Why are things jumping forward so quickly?
I wasn’t even aware
that you were pregnant.
And what about Nobu?
Why are you keeping quiet?
I don’t get it.
But sure, that’s not fair to you
having her move out so suddenly,
so I’ll pay half the rent
until you find a new roommate.
I don’t need your money!
Really? But we created
these circumstances.
Actually, the timing’s perfect.
I was planning on moving in
with Ren anyway.
If that’s the case,
we’ll just stop renting this place.
No, wait…
I wanted to talk to you about that too.
You need to think
about Ren’s situation a bit.
-Huh?
-About your relationship.
If everything from your past
until now comes to light,
it's the kind of thing
the tabloids go after.
So what? If Trapnest is gonna fail
because of some scandal,
then it’s not much
of a band to begin with.
No, in fact, I’m more worried
about us receiving more attention.
When a band becomes as popular as ours,
the public gradually shows more interest
in things other than the band’s music.
It can't be helped.
And we can take advantage of it, too.
But honestly, I’d hate for us to be judged
because of stuff unrelated to our music.
So I want to avoid the chance
of scandal encouraging that.
As someone involved in the music business,
I’m sure you'd understand.
How are you okay with getting married?
Me getting married won’t attract
much attention from the public.
I’m not nearly as recognized as Ren.
Besides, I don't think
you wanna draw attention
in that way before your debut.
Of course not! I couldn't stand it.
Then you need to be more cautious
with your actions.
I’m not telling you not to see him.
I get it. I’ll be more careful.
I'm glad you get it.
I tried to talk to Ren about this,
but he refuses to listen to me,
so it was bothering me.
That’s all I have to talk about.
I should be heading back.
What’s with her?
She’s like Takumi’s faithful dog.
I won’t be able to come
during our recording…
but when we’re done,
we’ll go and meet your parents.
So don’t worry unnecessarily
and get lots of rest.
But I don’t feel that ill that
I need to stay in bed.
While you’re away,
I’ll go see a real estate agent.
What kind of place
should I be looking for?
You’re even hastier than I am.
Are you that eager to play newlyweds?
I was just thinking you’re really busy,
so I wanted to help in any way that I can.
You wanna move out fast
because you’re finding it hard
to face Nana, right?
She seems to be very good friends
with Nobu,
so it's gotta be uncomfortable.
And she doesn’t hide the fact
that she’s upset about this.
FROM: REIRA
SUBJECT: GOOD MORNING.
I’M DONE WITH THE LYRICS.
IT’S AN INNOCENT LOVE STORY.
FROM LOVELY REIRA
I’ll talk to someone at my agency
about finding a place
and have him list up a few options.
You can go view those places
when you’re better
and decide on a place you like.
You’re not looking as pale.
Are you feeling less nauseous?
Mm-hmm. Thanks. I feel much better.
Takumi…
Shouldn’t you be going to your recording?
I still have plenty of time.
But this may not be good for the baby.
It’ll be fine. It’ll be fine.
Nana will hear us.
Don’t worry.
Just keep your voice down,
and she’ll never notice.
But she’s already pretty angry!
I need you to tame my anger first!
I can't stand the thought
of some other guy doing it with you.
Don’t you worry about a thing
and just focus on pleasing me.
The bed we got
from Mizukoshi’s store was old,
and the bedsprings would squeak.
It’s driving me crazy.
You’re a lot more important
to me than a boyfriend, Nana.
You liar!
It seems like I’m head over heels
in love with Nobu.
You traitor!
Could you find a new roommate?
Tell me that yourself, Nana!
If you don't want it,
I don't want it either.
I wanna use the same things you do.
Why don’t you use the strawberry glass?
Because there are only two of them.
What if I break one?
But if you don’t use them,
what’s the point of having them?
Yeah, but still, it’s too sad
if one of a set breaks.
You can use it, but be sure
to be careful, okay?
It’s too sad if one of a set breaks.
-Nana?
-Don't mind her.
Good…
They're together.
I’m not sad anymore.
Huh?
When did you get here?
A ring of oath.
Our red string. We can't see it now.
No promises either.
What part of this is
an innocent love story?
It seems to me more like
a song about infidelity.
-Huh?
-Huh? But there's no ring of oath, right?
Yes, but you could interpret this
as the other guy having
a ring on his finger.
Huh?
You know, you’ve been acting
awfully suspicious lately, Reira.
Are you having an affair?
That’s not what it means!
But songs about infidelity
sell pretty well!
But it’s not like that, Mari!
This is about pure love!
A love that binds people together
but one where you don’t even kiss!
-Speaking of ring of oath, Take…
-Hm?
I’m getting married.
-Huh?
-It’s all right, isn’t it?
-You're getting married?
What are you saying
all of a sudden, Takumi?
And to say it here?
I trust the staff members here.
-I-- I need an explanation!
-Huh?
You getting married is even less likely
than this single selling
ten million copies!
My woman’s pregnant.
Hachiko?
You sure know a lot.
It’s not like you, Takumi.
It’s not like you!
It's not Nobu's baby?
Why would you fall
for Hachiko’s tactics so easily like that?
Tactics?
Hachiko’s objectives are to earn
the status of being the wife
of a popular musician and your money!
She may have even lured you
into doing it when she was ovulating!
TAKUMI
Takumi, I wanna see you!
No, I doubt it was something
she did on purpose.
But her objectives may be as you say.
Are you fine with a loveless relationship?
Love comes later.
People love themselves more
than anyone else.
They end up loving those who
can fulfill the most of their desires.
-In a way, that’s true.
-Huh?
Why not? Let them get married, Take.
Why don’t we see where a relationship
between a bastard
and a fad follower will take them?
This could be fun.
Easy for you to say.
Anyway, we must discuss this
with the president.
Until we do, please,
everyone, keep this a secret.
What a pain.
Let me do as I wish! It’s my marriage!
Well then, let’s get started
with the recording.
Huh? Where’s Reira?
She was here until a moment ago.
I’m sure she’ll be right back.
We record the vocals later anyway.
We can do it without temporary vocals.
-Mari, could you please go look for her?
-Yes.
ERIC CLAPTON
ENGLISH SONGS
What? Reira’s your real name?
Mm-hmm. Well, almost.
It’s spelled L-A-Y-L-A.
You know the Eric Clapton song, "Layla"?
Yeah. It's a famous song.
My father loved that song,
so he named me after it.
Even now when I’m alone in my room,
I play that CD, and I don’t feel alone.
Lovely Layla.
The Japanese title is
a bit embarrassing…
That’ll be 5,500 yen.
I’ll be in touch.
ABC MUSIC STORE
INCOMING CALL
LAYLA
Yes?
Hello?
-Shin…
-What’s the matter?
Where are you now, Reira?
What about the recording?
Did something happen?
Reira, are you all right?
Please do me a favor.
I’m sorry.
Just tell me what it is. I’ll do anything.
I don’t need any more money.
-Yasu…
-Huh?
What?
Please give me Yasu’s cell number.
-Hello…
-Nana?
What the hell are you doing?
-You had me worried!
-Nobu?
I called you multiple times
since this morning,
but you don’t pick up!
I panicked last night
and said some mean things.
But I'm the one this is happening to
and went to work today,
so how dare you take the day off!
I’m starting to hate myself
for being so damn serious.
MISSED CALL
NOBU
-Ah, sorry.
-Never mind.
I’m used to your merciless oppression,
and I covered for you at work.
Where are you now?
At Ren’s… place?
I’m guessing Ren’s not there
because of work, right?
I’m done with work today.
Wanna grab a bite
before going to the studio?
Nobu…
My treat! You've gotta
let me spill out my sad story!
I’m thinking, there really is
something wrong with me.
I already know that, from long ago!
I can’t remember why I’m here.
Am I still only half awake?
The last thing I remember
was the strawberry glass
about to roll off the table.
Those matching glasses were
the first things
we bought together…
Was I able to catch that glass…
before it fell?
You know, Hachi…
I was too small of a person
to be able to accept everything about you.
I was like a cheap glass.
It's just that I preferred the pain
of breaking into pieces
to the loneliness I felt
from losing everything.
LOVELY LAYLA
I was just too fragile.
It’s not your fault.