MAY BLAST MAKE THEIR PROFESSIONAL DEBUT
Back then, the one thing I had plenty of
was my countless number of wishes.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
It’s July 7th?
SATURDAY, JULY 7TH 2001
A bad omen.
What is?
Actually, Nana hasn’t talked like that
lately, has she?
Before, she would blame everything
on the Demon Lord.
Perhaps she’s becoming more of an adult.
Let's hope so.
Kyosuke, do you want your eggs
sunny-side up or scrambled?
Sunny-side up.
Come to think of it…
Nana doesn’t come by our place
as often as she used to.
I don’t think I’ve seen her
in quite some time.
How’s she doing?
Oh, right. You couldn’t make it
to her roommate’s live concert either
because of work.
Well, she’s doing okay,
but there was something odd about her.
Yeah. You mean that scent
of a new guy in her life?
Although she denies it.
Has she found a job?
Ouch!
Judging by the fact
she’s said nothing about it, I doubt it.
She said something about wanting
to work in sales at a fancy shop.
But it’s been at least a month
since she was fired
from her previous job, right?
How’s she getting by?
She seems to be managing.
She said she’s been taking on
temporary jobs to get by.
But it’s not like there are
that many temporary jobs.
Hmm… She’s registered at a temp agency
specializing in demonstrators.
What exactly does a demonstrator do?
This is the new product, Raffine Beer.
Please give it a try.
This demonstrator takes part
in campaigns to promote food items
which are new to the market.
You’ll find them in the food section
of department stores,
preparing anything
from sausages to sliced fruits.
In other words, I’m a food salesgirl
offering food samples.
I get called for a sales blitz
that lasts for two, three days.
I get paid over ten thousand yen a day,
so I took the job to help me out
with living expenses for the time being.
But it’s actually a lot more fun
than I expected.
Anything involving food
would seem fun to you, Hachiko.
N-- No way! That’s not why.
How should I put it…
the interaction with the customers…
-Hey, Nobu, about this part…
-Listen to me!
What is it?
I’m convinced that working in sales
really suits me.
For instance, I’m really good at that
"free smile" deal.
Then you should find a job
at a fast food joint.
If the uniform’s cute, then I’d love that.
This latest gig from the beer company
requires me to wear
a campaign girl-type mini-skirt outfit,
which I look pretty good in.
I would’ve loved to see that.
That old pervert’s saying something.
The Milky Way’s not visible.
I was so looking forward to seeing it.
Hey, Nobu!
About meeting up tomorrow,
Yasu’s asking if we could meet there.
Sure! Since I’ll get off work just in time
for the opening anyway!
Tomorrow…
July 8th?
He says it’s okay!
That’s right. Tomorrow is
Trapnest’s last performance.
-The three of you are going, right?
-Mm-hmm.
Those VIP seats.
Are they in a special section?
Not really. They’re center seats
on the second floor balcony.
I hear you get a great view,
but since you’re surrounded by those
associated with the band
and journalists,
the section is pretty much dead.
What? That sounds so boring.
But we’re not exactly fans,
so I’m rather thankful that I won’t
be sitting between screaming voices.
You should’ve had Ren
get you a seat too, Hachi.
It might not be too late.
Why don’t I ask him?
No, I already saw them back home,
so it's fine.
Besides, I’m a bit busy tomorrow anyway.
You’ve got it wrong!
You have to write a wish
and hang it from a bamboo branch.
A wish?
Do you seriously not know?
-What?
-What’s the matter?
Well, Shin says he’s never seen
Tanabata decorations.
Can you believe it? He just asked me,
"What is a tanzaku?"
Like I asked before, what kind of life
have you been living?
Didn’t you do that kind of stuff
in kindergarten?
I wanna write a wish on a tanzaku too.
Then wanna come over to write some?
We still have some tanzaku left.
All right!
She made Tanabata decorations?
I told her not to, since it’s
embarrassing at her age, but…
&lrm;Just a sec…
All right.
Defeat Trapnest?
Nobu, that’s not a wish!
That’s a resolution!
Yeah, I guess.
I’ll write a wish for Nobu.
"I want to become taller. Nobu."
None of your business!
Besides, you’re shorter than me!
But I’m still growing.
Sorry to say this,
but I’ll surpass your height in no time.
I think I’ll wish for that.
I wish that we can get an air conditioner.
I wish that I get back the car I sold.
I want a veranda
where I can decorate bamboo branches.
I want money.
You guys, can’t you write down
some real dreams?
But this room is so damn hot!
Indeed.
My dreams will wither in this heat.
Nana! The tanzakus are being blown away.
That day, the clear skies of Tokyo
filled up with clouds in the evening,
and we never got to see the Milky Way.
However, we ended up staying up
all night chatting.
I already knew that wishing alone
won’t make dreams come true,
but I did feel that each time
a dream came true,
I would become that much happier.
MAY HACHIKO FIND A BOYFRIEND
(LONG-HAIRED) NANA
Today, we will once again bring you
a wide range of special melodies,
from the latest hit songs
to nostalgic songs from the past.
We will kick off with a video clip
of a group who will be performing
the finale to their first nationwide tour
tonight. Trapnest.
Once the tour is over…
I’ll come to see you.
When I do, would you mind
cooking for me again?
He will come. He won’t come.
He will come.
He won’t come.
Oh, no! Nobody in today’s age uses
flowers to make predictions anymore!
I may be insane!
I shouldn’t have to use flowers!
I know the answer!
There’s no way he’s coming.
He didn’t even reply to my email.
He’s probably forgotten all about me.
But just in case…
Even if Takumi doesn’t come,
I’m sure Ren will come.
There’s no big difference in cooking
for three people or four people.
I don’t know what time they’ll show up,
so it has to be food that’s tasty
even after it’s cooled.
These tomatoes are really delicious.
Where did you get them from?
This many veggies? Thank you, Jun-chan.
The two of us can’t eat all this.
They just arrived,
so they’re really fresh.
Today's my lucky day!
Well then, thank you so much, Jun-chan.
Come by again.
-Kyosuke said he’d love to see you.
-Mm-hmm.
But look at all the stuff you bought.
Are you expecting someone?
N-- Not really. N-- No one’s coming.
It’s probably for the best
for him not to come.
Then I can easily give up on him.
Besides, if Takumi comes over,
I will have to explain everything to Nana.
There’s no way I could hide
things any longer.
But if that happens, there’d
no longer be a reason to hide things.
If Takumi is the kind of guy who would
come to see me as he promised,
I would feel less guilty
about the situation.
Hey, Hachiko! Who’s gonna eat all this?
There’s easily enough food
for five people!
I guess I got a bit carried away.
But I figured he'd be hungry
after the live performance.
I wonder what time Ren will be here.
Huh? He’s coming? Did he say he is?
What? I don’t know,
but I assumed he’d be coming. Isn’t he?
I doubt he is.
He never made any such promise.
-Why not?
-What do you mean, why not?
His tour ends today,
so wouldn’t he come to see you
first thing after the concert’s over?
He hasn’t seen you in a month!
He will definitely come!
But tonight they’re partying until late
to celebrate the end of the tour.
It’s not likely
he’ll be able to come here.
Partying until late…
I see.
But he may come after that.
No. If Ren comes over and stays the night,
you’d feel obligated to be hospitable.
So we decided that from now on,
whenever we wanna meet,
I’ll go to Ren’s place.
He’s not gonna suddenly show up
late at night without my knowledge.
No way. I was faintly hoping that…
Hoping that Ren would come to see Nana,
and Takumi would tag along
with his casual
"Maybe I’ll come along too" attitude.
H-- Hey…
I don’t care even if it would be
a casual spur of the moment decision.
I just hoped he would come.
Don’t let it get you down.
If you wanna see Ren,
I’ll ask him to drop by sometime.
He did say he has free time
starting tomorrow.
Oh, if you’d like I’ll have him
invite Takumi again, and…
No, it’s all right! Don’t worry about me!
B-- But…
Well, anyway, I don’t think
he’ll be able to come today.
I’m sorry, considering
all the food you prepared.
It’s okay. It really is.
Really, don’t worry about it.
I’ll just put everything in the fridge.
It’ll last a few days.
What am I doing?
I got carried away all by myself again.
Hey, wait! I’m hungry.
Do you mind if I eat what I can now?
Sure. Of course you can.
I’ll get some plates.
This looks really delicious.
Ren doesn’t know what he’s missing,
losing out on this great feast.
Delicious!
However, seeing the way
you’re acting, you actually wanted
to go to the final concert
with everyone tonight, didn’t you?
I should’ve asked Ren about it.
I’m really bad at noticing
that sort of stuff. Sorry.
That’s not true.
Never mind me.
I bet you wanted to go, didn’t you?
You can be really stubborn.
It’s not really about being stubborn.
If I saw the performance,
I’d end up comparing myself
and get depressed.
As shameful as that is…
This is great too. Looks like
we’ll be enjoying great food for a while.
I’m the one who’s lousy
at noticing things about others.
I’m sorry for forcing
those words out of you.
Thank you very much!
Today’s performance is now over.
People are asked to follow
the guidance of the staff
and promptly leave the premises.
I’m going home.
Huh? You’re not going?
But our pass allows us to go backstage.
I have work to do.
Never mind that. Just come for a bit.
Sorry. Give Ren my regards.
What about Reira?
Tell her "Good job."
That’s it?
TRAPNEST'S BACKSTAGE ROOM
Huh? Where’s Yasu? Isn’t he with you?
He left, saying he had work to do.
He sends his regards to Ren.
-Huh? What about me?
-No way!
I was really looking forward
to seeing him.
I guess it wasn’t mutual, Naoki.
I was also looking forward
to seeing him. So it wasn’t mutual?
This is so painful.
Reira, you realize it’s hard to come up
with a comeback phrase in your case.
It wasn’t mutual? This is so painful.
Not to mention there are writers
around us taking notes.
Take, it’s not a laughing matter.
Yasu asked me to tell you
that you did a good job.
Wow, what a pretty boy!
-Come play with me.
-Hey!
Sure, but I’m expensive.
One hundred thousand yen per night
for the "works".
Shin!
You’re cute too. How much?
Ren, save me. What’s up with this person?
I think I'll go home.
Come on. We’re partying. Come join us.
We’ve got a second and third party
lined up, so we’ll be at it until morning.
Yay! I’m coming, I’m coming.
Yay, come, come.
Yeah, I’m coming, I’m coming.
Gin and tonic.
Are you sure, Nobu?
We’re only at the second party.
Shouldn’t you slow down with the drinking?
I can’t blend in with this atmosphere
unless I’m drunk.
Such a pure-hearted guy!
I wonder why Yasu went out
with such a weird woman.
Weird woman?
The mysteries of Yasu keep building.
I can’t let you talk like that, Nobu.
How dare you talk
about our princess like that.
Takumi… Sorry to bother you,
but could you please autograph these?
What. What’s this? You're making me work,
even in this place?
Sorry.
I got autographs from the others
during breaks at rehearsals,
but you seemed busy, so I was
gonna ask you later then forgot.
It’s a request
from a very important sponsor.
Okay, okay. If it’s so important,
then you shouldn’t forget.
Sorry.
Pull yourself together, manager.
So you’re signing them? Good for you.
I’m a mature man after all.
You’re the one who does
the musical arrangements
for all the Trapnest songs, right Takumi?
That’s right.
And you also produced
your latest album, right?
Well, yeah.
So that’s why it’s
so much better than the first one.
Oh? You’re cute. How about
for two hundred thousand yen?
But you’re seriously great.
How do you manage to make
such fancy music
out of Ren’s dark, twisted songs?
Excuse me for writing dark, twisted songs.
Shochu!
But it’s all possible
because of Ren’s songs.
How do you manage
to get on everyone’s good side?
By the way, Takumi,
could you sign an autograph for me, too?
Sure. But do you have autograph paper?
No, I don’t. Just give me one of those.
But these are for our important sponsors.
What do I care?
He’s just like Nana.
To whom?
-Hachiko.
-Huh?
Ren, if it’s for Hachi,
why not do the favor of having him
write out her full name?
What is her full name?
Hachi… Where have I heard that before?
You met her a while ago, Takumi.
At the mahjong tournament. Nana Komatsu.
Oh, yes, Nana.
She may no longer want
an autograph from me.
Huh? But she said she wanted one.
-When?
-The day of the mahjong game.
Then there’s no need.
We did it the next day.
Where did Take go?
Wait. What do you mean, "You did it"?
What? You want me to explain it to you?
She’s my girl’s best friend.
It’s one thing to fool around with women,
but you’ve gone too far.
-Know your limits.
-Don’t get all worked up.
It’s not as if I forced myself onto her.
She agreed to it.
She was wagging her tail
looking all pleased.
Hey, you!
Take, it’s nothing.
They’re just fooling around.
If you wanna fight, let’s take it outside.
It’s a party for all the tour staff.
Don’t spoil it.
-Nobu…
-I’m going home.
You’re going home?
Takumi…
Good job.
The autographs!
Are you all right, Takumi?
-Shin is so awesome!
-Don’t laugh, Reira.
Don’t get all upset, Takumi.
You’re the one at fault.
I was just telling the truth!
What’s wrong with that?
You think you did
absolutely nothing wrong?
I’m going home too.
You can’t leave, Takumi.
We’ve still got the third party to go to.
Continue without me.
Takumi, the autographs…
I’ll redo them tomorrow
and send them to you.
Thanks to this, I just remembered
something important that I must do.
What? A woman thing again?
When you see Nobu, tell him that
he cannot reach my level
even in a hundred years.
He doesn’t have the guts
to make a woman his, so stop fussing.
I agree with the second half.
I’ll give him the message.
What is it at this time of night?
Hey, Hachi…
Hey, Nana…
Why are having a dream come true
and achieving happiness
two different things?
I still don’t get it, even now.
MAY HACHIKO FIND A BOYFRIEND
(LONG-HAIRED) NANA