The contract money Gaia transferred
into our accounts,
the expected monthly salaries
from the agency,
and estimated royalties
we’ll be receiving from CD sales…
Our band is no longer
some humble amateur band.
I figured I could easily support
Hachi and her baby now.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
We played mahjong till dawn
in the recreation room
on the second floor…
Ron.
And we took Yuri to her room since
-she could no longer walk on her own.
-I’m all right. I’m all right.
-Don’t you touch her!
-Right.
Good night! Let’s do this again soon!
After listening closely to confirm that
she was retiring to bed,
I got into bed myself.
Even if it were casual,
if they end up doing it,
Nobu would get emotionally involved.
That’s the kind of guy Nobu is.
Right now, I want him
to think only of Hachi.
I still want him to love only Hachi.
But I wanna stop saying
such selfish things.
God… Buddha… Demon Lord…
Please make Nobu and Hachiko
get back together.
It’s past eight o'clock.
You’d better get up, or you’ll be late.
Sure… Huh? What about my alarm?
-It went off.
-Sorry!
Do you find it noisy every morning?
Or do you find me noisy?
Yeah. Thanks to you, I’ve been
able to sleep really well lately.
-Was she being sarcastic?
-Maybe.
You’re alone on the fourth floor,
aren’t you?
You’re not planning to move here, are you?
Think why I fled from Room 603
after just one night.
Then what about the third floor?
Does anyone live there?
I’ve never seen anyone from there.
More importantly,
what are you gonna do today, Nobu?
Are you going to the fireworks festival?
-Yeah.
-You’re gonna get Hachi back!
-Huh? Well…
-You coward.
Hey! That’s something
I should decide after I see her!
If she seems happy,
then that’s good enough for me.
I don’t wanna get her back
if it’s gonna interfere
with her happiness.
But… if she seems sad,
then I couldn’t leave her like that.
No!
You seriously think
you can just cancel your interview
at the last minute for personal reasons?
I never said anything about canceling it!
I’m just asking you to move it
to another day!
Absolutely not!
Besides, I can’t let you loose
in a big crowd like that.
Don’t worry about that.
Mika and Masaru said they’d help,
so our disguises will be perfect.
Oh my! You think you can get away using
a professional hair stylist and
makeup artist for your personal business?
But when we called and asked,
they both found it amusing
and were looking forward to it.
I wonder what kind of interesting outfits
they have planned for us.
Regardless, I won’t allow it!
All right.
If you won’t allow it,
I’ll just have to skip work.
What did you say?
I’m so disappointed in you, Nana.
You’ve got a bad attitude,
and you’re a lousy singer,
but at least I valued you
for your enthusiasm toward your work.
I’m lousy?
Well, that’s why, Ginpei,
I wish you’d understand that
for Nana to be insisting so much,
this has gotta be something
really important to her.
Yasu… I understand.
For you to say so, it’s gotta be something
really important.
What the hell?
I’ll discuss it with the reporter.
He’s really in love with him?
Oh, sure, that’s fine.
We still have time
before the proofing deadline.
Monday? Not a problem at all.
Then I’ll try to finish this game
and return to work before then.
What’d he say?
He was extremely troubled by it
but has agreed to somehow adjust
his schedule to accommodate us.
All right!
I’m sorry for the trouble, Ginpei.
-It’s okay.
-This is great! Isn’t it, Nobu?
I do have a heart, you know.
-That’s good news, isn’t it, Nana?
-Hey, come on! Aren’t you happy?
Y-- Yeah…
Our band is becoming
more and more like a family.
You can’t smoke!
-Ginpei’s like the strong mama,
-Why just me?
-Yasu’s the dependable oldest son,
-If you quit, Shin might quit too.
Nobu’s the kind-hearted second son,
and Shin’s the bratty baby of the family.
It’s because I’m protected by this family
that I can get away with being
so selfish and spoiled.
But then who’s the dad?
If it’s the president, that would make
us some gangster family.
BLACK STONES CLAN
I guess I’ll settle on the raccoon guy.
At least he’s better than the fox guy.
That’s not bad.
I’ve always wanted to be part
of a big family like the ones on TV.
Now if Hachi would marry Nobu,
it would be perfect.
OBSTETRICS GYNECOLOGY
NAKAZATO CLINIC
You’re now fourteen weeks along.
The baby is growing well.
I’ve got a pretty good idea
ò the gender of the baby.
Huh?
Would you like to know now?
Or would you like to keep it a surprise
for when the baby’s born?
I do want to know,
but perhaps it would be
more exciting to wait?
What should I do…
It’s still an educated guess
at this point.
Yes.
It’s good that your morning sickness
subsided fairly quickly,
but I am concerned
about your rapid weight gain.
If you gain too much,
it can be dangerous in many ways,
so try to focus on eating proper portions
of nutritionally balanced foods, okay?
Actually, appearance wise,
I don’t wanna gain weight either.
I ate too much at lunch.
I’ll avoid the food stands
at the fireworks festival.
Did you say something, Sachiko?
Huh? You want a Jackson Burger?
No, no. I have a bad feeling
about that place.
Maybe I shouldn’t go
to the fireworks festival after all.
Well, I’m sure it’ll be really crowded,
so your chances of seeing her are minimal.
But what if I run into her?
Myself aside, I’d feel bad for Sachiko.
Her evening of fun would be ruined.
I think it’d be worse not to take her
for those reasons.
That’s why I’m in a bind!
-Damn you, Junko!
-Welcome!
It’s been so long, Koichi Sato!
Nana…
My bad feelings have come true.
I’ve been led here by the Demon Lord.
If you had a revelation, then don’t come!
But Sachiko said she was hungry.
A Jackson Burger and fresh orange juice.
Sure.
Sachiko?
The baby in my tummy. Four months now.
Why’d you name it that?
-You’re scaring me!
-Don’t ask me!
I didn’t wanna name her that either!
Then don’t!
But my husband has
his heart set on Sachiko.
By "husband," you mean Takumi of Trapnest?
-Jun-chan, you blabbermouth!
-So it is!
Huh?
No, it’s okay. I won’t tell anyone.
I swear to the Demon Lord himself.
Sure, I promise. I promise, so…
-Can I get Reira’s autograph?
-You were a fan?
I thought I’d display it
in the alcove at my parents’ place
and make it an heirloom.
I’m sure my grandma would appreciate it
and put her hands together every day.
Well, I guess so then.
I’ll ask for you, but Reira’s really busy,
so I can’t promise anything.
You’re friends with her?
Well, sort of.
That’s amazing, Nana!
Until recently,
you were just a country girl.
I’m gonna call you
a celebrity from now on.
Stop it. I’m just
your average pregnant woman.
Okay, now you’ve got some attitude.
But seeing you now,
I guess running around doing
as you wish is a great skill in a way.
These days, being firm and modest
isn’t enough to get you
on the winning team.
I’ve learned something new.
Congratulations, celebrity!
Keep climbing that social ladder!
Hey, Take.
It looks like Ren’s decided to marry Nana.
Huh? Marry her?
So you persuaded him, Takumi?
No, he brought up the subject himself.
And he doesn’t seem to have
any ulterior motives.
That’s good.
-What are you talking about?
-That’s the best.
He’s out buying the ring right now.
We should arrange for him to meet her,
so he can give it to her.
You’re right.
With that ring, I’m sure
even Nana will accept it with joy.
We don’t have to worry anymore.
You know, that’s a really big diamond.
A worthless guy like me could never afford
to buy something like that in my lifetime.
I’m happy for you, celebrity,
that you didn’t settle with me.
You make it sound
like I’m some evil woman who dumped you.
But it’s true!
You had me running in circles for you,
and then in the end,
it’s, "I don’t want him!"
-Was I your toy?
-You’re the one who cheated on me!
Sorry.
So you think that apologizing now
will make it all right?
I’m sorry, but it’s in the past, isn’t it?
I’m surprised you can be
so casual about it!
I’m just trying to say what
you wanna hear.
You kept saying how much you loved me,
but it turned out that was all a lie!
I don’t remember ever
actually saying that to you.
I could hear it!
I know! And there’s no way that was a lie!
You know very well
that I’m terrible at lying.
That’s why when I cheated on you,
you found out right away,
and I confessed.
Right away? While we’re at it,
tell me everything.
Why did you cheat on me?
I just gave in to temptation.
Maybe it was the Demon Lord.
But you were dating them both
for a good two weeks.
Hey, Master! If you’re keeping track
of your customers’ criminal records,
you’ll get taken out someday.
Two weeks…
That’s all? What a boring man.
Celebrity!
You’ve changed my opinion of you.
You were keeping
Ren’s best interests in mind.
Huh?
Why, of course. I think
about his interests far more than you do.
I seriously worry about him, too!
But if he marries Nana
and she stays with him forever,
it’ll cure his bad habits.
-Oh, that’s what you’re talking about.
-Huh?
It’s okay.
He can quit whenever he wants to.
Ren just has no desire to.
You think so?
I think Ren wants to quit if he can.
Then he should quit.
But even you said you’d quit smoking
for the baby’s sake,
yet you haven’t been able to!
Nicotine creates a chemical dependency
in your body,
so quitting is not that easy.
But Ren’s psychological dependency
is also an addiction!
Keep your voice down.
If word gets out about him,
the band’s activities will be suspended.
I’m concerned about it too.
Don’t get so worked up about it.
Be concerned for the sake of Ren,
not for that of the band.
That’s not my role.
Is that why you’re letting him
get married?
He’s a burden to you,
so you want Nana to take on that role?
That’s not it. That’s a different story.
Yes?
Ah, Mr. Narita.
Good afternoon.
MITSURU NARITA (46) PRESIDENT
How does it look? I dyed it blonde.
At your age? That’s ridiculous!
Reira, even if he does look ridiculous,
that’s no way to talk to the president!
What brings you here today?
We’ll be meeting with the agency
-about Reira’s commercial appearance.
-Sexual harassment!
We don’t need you here!
Right, for the cosmetics.
That’s great, Reira.
You’ll be admired even more
-by young girls across the country.
-I only wanna do jobs
that require singing!
Stop being selfish.
They’ll be using our song
for the commercial.
Takumi, I heard about Ren.
The sooner we have
a press conference, the better.
We should try
and move things along quickly.
Bye!
BLAH
Takumi! Why does even the president
suddenly want
Ren and Nana to get married?
He’s the one who suggested it
in the first place!
He wanted Ren to announce to the press
that he would protect Nana!
Why now?
He said he doesn’t want Ren to look like
he was being used by a woman.
He thinks that by publicly declaring
that they are lovers,
the public will be left
with the impression
that BLAST became popular thanks to us.
-That’s ridiculous!
-Well, he’s not very smart.
Simply saying "we’re getting married"
is more persuasive
and leaves a favorable impression.
Then Narita will be satisfied,
and we can put this silly party to rest.
So you want them to get married
for your own protection?
Actually, you disgust me!
What does the way you feel about me
have anything to do with Ren’s problems?
We’re talking business here!
That’s what I hate about you women!
Then I’ll point this out strictly
from a business point of view.
The core of our fan base is young women.
With that in mind, I don’t think having
you and Ren getting married
one after the other is such a great plan.
If you seriously think all fans
support us for our music only,
you’re delusional.
I get it. Then it would be better
if just Ren got married, right?
Why is Sachiko working
while you’re wandering around?
We work different shifts.
You’ve gotta work more,
so she can take it easy!
But we split the bills fifty-fifty.
That’s one very reliable housewife.
I’d say girls like you
who not only spend a lot
but rely on the earnings of others
to pay for it are a lot less common.
I’m glad you found a guy
with deep pockets.
Hey, not that you’d know it,
but I’ve grown up a lot recently.
I know.
Jun-chan, you blabbermouth…
So Nana, who are you going
to the fireworks with?
That’s a secret!
We celebrities have many secrets
that we cannot tell the commoners.
So even if we run into each other,
don’t talk to me, okay?
And I’ll do the same.
&lrm;POST OFFICE
I really am sorry.
It’s okay. I had many faults too.
But thinking back,
none of your selfish whims were that bad.
I might annoy you by saying this,
but I still enjoy talking with you.
I’m glad I could see you.
So I won’t see you anymore.
Those with a record
must refrain, you know.
Bye.
Get going!
You go first. Where are you meeting?
It’s a secret. I still have time,
so I think I’ll wander around a bit.
You sure like wandering,
even though you get lost easily.
I don’t get lost anymore! Hurry up and go!
Oh, by the way, when is she due? Sachiko.
The end of April.
It’s not possible that she’ll be late
and arrive on May 5th, is it?
Why? It’s perfectly possible.
If she were born on that day,
Children’s Day,
it would be nice
because everyone would remember the day!
Are you sure it’s not
the Demon Lord’s child?
How dare you say something so ominous!
Children of the Demon Lord
can only be born on July 7th.
Let’s hope so.
Well then, take care of yourself.
Give birth to a healthy human baby!
-Hachiko’s late, isn’t she?
-No, it’s only 5:30 p.m.
She doesn’t have a key,
so she won’t be here until six o’clock.
What? She doesn’t have a key?
Yasu, you’re too funny!
I can’t continue a conversation like this!
Mika and Masaru put
all that effort into it,
so you shouldn’t be screwing around.
You’re the one who put it on me.
You even paid for it.
With Yasu, placing wigs on him is so easy!
Shin, quit talking like Misato.
You’re seriously cute like that.
That long hair looks
surprisingly good on you.
I’ll bet Hachi will fall in love
with you all over again.
But I don’t want her to fall in love
with me for that reason.
It makes you look a bit like Shoji.
Though you’re shorter.
I thought so, too. Petite Shoji?
Yeah, he does look like him.
Although Nobu’s shorter.
Who is this Shoji?
And just how tall is he?
Shoji!
What’s wrong? Your eyes are red.
Huh? My contact lenses are giving
me problems.
But you have twenty-twenty vision.
Maybe I’m just far-sighted.
The further away something is,
the better I can see it.
But once it gets close,
I lose sight of it.
That could be the same with everyone.
Let’s hold hands all night tonight,
so we don’t lose each other in the crowd,
especially since you’re tiny.
Hey, Hachi…
They say you don’t realize
how much you care for someone
until after they’re gone.
But I think it’s when you come
face to face with that person once more
that you truly recognize
your feelings for them.
If I saw everyone again right now…
I know that I’d depend on them
just as much as I did back then.
I’m scared of that.
That’s why I can’t move from this spot.