Although it’s already May,
the wind at night still feels very cold.
This is no different from my hometown
in the mountains.
I had thought that Tokyo
was a warmer place.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
Well, this may still be Tokyo,
but we’re way out in the suburbs.
Or rather, don’t you think
the weather’s gone nuts?
One day it’s hot like summer,
and then the next day, it gets cold enough
to convince you we’ve gone back to winter.
Is the weather gonna get even crazier?
I’m getting worried.
I’m a lot more worried about you,
Shin, the way you’re headed
on a direct path to destruction!
Why?
Oh, the phone.
Hello. Oh, Mayumi?
Mm-hmm, no problem. Where are you now?
Roppongi? I’m out
in the suburbs right now.
Then do you mind if I use a taxi? Really?
All right!
Yeah. I’ll be on my way now.
I’m sorry, but something came up,
so I’ll be going now.
Okay. Be careful.
-Although…
-Shin.
You’re free to choose whatever life
you wish to live,
but don’t you do anything that
will give the band a bad name!
Nana!
Shin’s only fifteen,
so you could be a little kinder
rather than push him away like that.
What would you do if he goes astray
and joins some biker gang?
Hey, Shin. I don’t know why you left home,
but I’m sure you were going
through something difficult
to make that decision, right?
Did your stepmother tease you?
-Stepmother?
-It’s all right!
You don’t have to tell me if it's painful.
But, Shin, please understand one thing.
If you underestimate women,
you’ll get hurt in the end.
Okay. I’ll be careful.
TAXI
-Oh boy.
-Not!
You haven’t fixed anything.
Besides, how is giving some advice
gonna help him?
Advice? You’re wrong.
I was giving him a warning.
I’m going home.
I have to start work
in the morning tomorrow.
Nana!
Don’t be so cold hearted and stay with me.
How do you expect me
to kill time alone here?
Are you serious about waiting here
until Shoji gets off work?
-It’ll probably be another hour, at least.
-But…
There’s no need to wait.
He said he’d drop by our place later.
But still! Jun-chan told me
I should show him that I care for him.
Whatever. Then let’s go
wait for him inside.
No!
Since he said not to wait for him,
openly waiting for him in full view
would only have the opposite effect.
Then like I said, let’s go home.
If he thinks I went home only to find that
I had been waiting for him,
don’t you think that would
touch his heart?
That’s just silly.
You have no clue how
a young girl in love feels, Nana!
I don’t understand!
I hate cunning women like that.
If you just say you’re waiting for Shoji
because you love him, then sure,
I have no problem staying here with you.
Well of course, that’s
the first and foremost reason…
Then all that other stuff is unnecessary.
Just wag your tail and wait.
I hate cunning women like that.
Nana! It’s okay! You’ll catch a cold.
I’m not that weak.
Besides, I don’t feel cold.
No way. It’s really cold today.
Compared to the cold weather
I experienced in my hometown,
Tokyo is like a tropical island.
The place I lived is covered
in snow half of the year.
So that’s what your hometown’s like.
I’d like to go there someday,
the place where you grew up.
-Thanks. It’s warm.
-Yeah.
You know how Shoji said he had
something he needed to talk to me about?
He had such a serious look.
It got me thinking.
So I’d probably be unsettled
and restless if we went home.
Sorry for having you stick around.
I couldn’t say anything else.
I just continued listening
to the tune Nana was quietly humming.
Nana’s eyes were so clear.
She seemed to fit in better
with snowy mountains
than in this city where
you can barely see the stars.
The truth is I am a very cunning woman.
I was no longer the pure woman
who would continue waiting for Shoji
while expecting nothing in return.
But I pretended to be
because I didn’t want Nana to dislike me.
Good night! I’m going on ahead!
Sachiko…
You know, I…
I’m gonna break up with her. Hey!
They’re finally finished.
Someone’s coming out.
Really?
Sachiko!
What?
This girl…
I’m sorry!
Sachiko? Of all the names…
What are you doing?
What’s with this woman?
-She’s my girlfriend.
-Huh?
Are you telling me that
you have two girlfriends?
You sure have it good!
This can’t be. This can’t be happening.
I need to talk to you about something.
There’s gotta be some sort of mistake.
I’m sorry!
There’s no way Shoji
would do something like this.
Don’t!
-Sachiko! It’s okay, stay back!
-Don’t be violent with Shoji!
Shut up! I won’t be satisfied
until I beat him up!
-Stop it!
-Stay out of this!
This has nothing to do with you!
You’re the one
who has nothing to do with this!
She’s right.
If you want to hit someone, then hit me!
-H-- Hey!
-I was the one who had a crush on him!
I knew he had a girlfriend
and still couldn't stop myself!
I won’t hide or run away,
so hit me to your heart’s content!
-You sure have guts.
-Cut it out.
Hachiko!
Why are you just standing there?
This is your fight!
Do something!
If you don’t fight,
you’ve accepted defeat!
He’s your man, isn’t he?
Fight to get him back!
I don’t want him.
I don’t even want to see his face.
I wasn't mature enough
to forgive his betrayal.
And I had too much pride to cling
onto someone who just hurt me.
I lose.
The next day, like a sick person,
I spent all day
not being able to get out of bed.
I tried not to think about anything.
I wanted to focus my mind
on something else to distract me,
but I didn’t feel like doing anything.
I repeatedly dreamt about Shoji.
Coming.
Who is it?
Ren?
What a surprise. It was a dream.
What is it with me,
dreaming of celebrities at times like this
when I’m supposed to be heartbroken?
But why Ren?
Could this have had something
to do with it?
But I'd rather dream of Takumi…
It really is the doorbell! Is it Takumi?
Or could it be Naoki? Maybe Reira?
Yes, coming!
Thank goodness! You’re alive!
Oh, it’s you. Hey, Jun-chan.
Come on! How many times
must I ring the doorbell?
You had me worried that
you slit your wrists or something.
Give me a break.
My wrists?
I see. So you heard about last night.
Slitting my wrists…
That may be better
than jumping off a bridge.
-Oh, Nana must've called you.
-Huh?
She’s working today, so she’s worried
about leaving me here alone all day.
No. Your roommate isn’t the type
to think of doing such a thing.
Huh?
Shoji called me a short while ago.
He’s worried about you.
The hell with him.
If he cannot come himself,
I don’t want him worrying about me!
You’re right.
Sorry, it was stupid of me to tell you.
But you know, Nana,
this is hard on Shoji too.
You know very well the type of guy he is.
-Are you taking his side, Jun-chan?
-No, this isn’t about taking sides.
He was cheating on me all along!
It wasn’t the whole time!
And don’t say that he cheated on you.
There you go again!
You are taking his side!
Maybe I am.
To me, Shoji is a good friend,
just as important as you, Nana.
I can’t always be taking your side
about everything.
Honestly, I have a problem
with your tendency
to be quick to play the victim.
It’s true. Shoji is at fault
for going after another woman
before clearing things with you first.
But before we focus on that,
you’ve gotta acknowledge
you’re also to blame for this, Nana.
I know that.
But I did the best I could, Jun-chan.
I even found a job,
so that I could make it on my own.
But that’s something you did
for your own sake.
From a while back, you would always
think only about yourself.
You showed very little care for Shoji.
Love is a relationship that
two people build for each other.
If you cannot care for your partner,
the relationship isn’t gonna work out.
I’m back.
You could at least turn on the light.
I know you’re depressed, but come on.
Nana! Welcome back. No way.
I didn’t realize how late it was.
You must be hungry.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t prepare dinner tonight.
I figured, so I bought us
dinner on the way home.
Let’s eat.
Are these tears of joy?
I’ve always thought this.
You always put yourself first,
but at the same time,
you’re so caring to others.
Caring?
And what’s this about me
putting myself first?
On the other hand, look at me!
I've only been thinking about myself!
It never occurred to me that you’d be
coming home on an empty stomach!
You don’t need to worry about that.
But a friendship is a relationship
two people build for each other.
Why are you suddenly
bringing up the obvious?
Let me at least make you some tea.
By the way,
there’s a letter for you from Natsuko.
Mom sent me a letter?
Bottom line, Natsuko has
a knack for sensing these things.
The way she contacts you without fail
when you’re in a bind.
It's because she is your mother.
NATSUKO KOMATSU
If she asks me to come home now,
I would be tempted to accept.
THIS REGISTERED LETTER CAME FOR YOU.
WOULD YOU AT LEAST GIVE THEM
NOTICE OF YOUR CHANGE OF ADDRESS?
Is that all?
Where are my words of consolation?
What’s the matter, Hachiko?
Are you all right?
This won’t do! Scissors.
Where did I put them? Never mind.
A paper-knife will do.
A paper-knife!
Don’t do it! Shoji’s not
the only man in the world!
I know that! But more importantly,
the tickets arrived!
-Huh?
-Tickets to the Trapnest concert.
I bought two tickets. Wanna go?
Nana…
no matter how unbearable life may seem,
good things will happen
as long as we’re alive.
They’re front row seats.
GATES OPEN 5:30 PM
PERFORMANCE 6:30 PM
RESERVED SEATING 5,250 YEN (TAX INCLUDED)
FLOOR 1, CENTRAL AISLE, ROW 1, SEAT 27
Now that I think back, during those days,
it was as if luck had eluded me
on a daily basis.
I never had much luck
with the lottery either.
Those tickets were something
God had set aside for Nana.