The biggest reason I chose that job
was because,
unlike working in sales,
I get weekends off.
I felt that I would then be able
to spend more time with Shoji,
who’s busy with school
and work during the week.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
RAMEN SEIROKU
Kyosuke, have you ever been
unfaithful to your partner?
You did it? With Sachiko?
The defendant shall
just answer the question!
The defendant would be you.
-I’ve never been unfaithful to my partner.
-You liar!
During our senior year,
you’re the dumbass who fooled around
with several girls at the same time!
-Was I?
-Don’t play stupid with me!
I know it all! There’s that college girl
you met at the club,
the nurse from the hospital when you had
your motorcycle accident,
and Tamura's sister from class six.
You have a pretty good memory.
I didn’t know you were that jealous.
Anyway!
There’s no way a cruel man
with such a past record
would not cheat on his partner!
Are you that desperate
for a partner in crime?
But that really brings back memories.
Those days were the peak of my popularity.
Lately, my popularity
with the girls has plummeted.
Then if you were popular,
you’d fool around, right?
I wouldn’t.
Why not? Because you’re afraid of Junko?
Well sure, it’s natural to be
afraid of Junko,
being a former delinquent in school
and all.
Because I’m afraid of losing Junko.
Check please.
Right away.
There’s a woman there
who totally pisses me off!
What do you call them?
You know, like, a spinster?
"Ms. Komatsu, you can’t even
make a decent cup of tea.
You’ll never make a good wife."
She’s the one who can’t find a husband,
that thirty-eight year old bitch,
Sakagami!
What’s wrong, Shoji?
You seem to be under the weather today.
Well, you know, I wish you
wouldn’t say stuff like "bitch".
Did you pick that up
from your foul-mouthed roommate?
But she really pisses me off!
It’s only a small publishing company,
but they have a ton of little side jobs!
They talk down to me,
I’ve gotta work overtime,
and I even had to come in
both days this weekend
because of the approaching deadline!
So much for weekends off.
I hate it. I wanna quit!
-Then quit.
-Don’t say it so casually!
You just said you wanted to quit.
But it’s not that easy. I haven’t even
worked there for a week yet,
and if I quit, there’s no guarantee that
I’d find another job right away.
And I can’t make a living unless I work.
Then you have no choice.
Well, it’s easy for you, Shoji.
Bottom line,
you’re a carefree college student,
and your parents pay for your basic needs.
If you hadn’t bought that computer
and kept track of your expenses,
you’d have no problem getting by, right?
That was awful. Why did I say that?
Why can’t I be a nice, cute girl
in front of Shoji?
Unless he asks me to go home with him,
we won’t be able to make up.
Wanna come up?
Nana’s probably still at work.
No, it’s okay. You have to get up
early tomorrow for work, right?
Good night.
You’re mad at me,
so don’t try to force a smile.
Unless you’re direct with me,
how am I supposed to apologize?
Ms. Komatsu! How long is it taking
you to sort those postcards?
You really are slow!
Yes, sorry, Ms. Sakagami.
-In a way,
-Oh, why did
-this woman is a breath of fresh air
-the editor-in-chief hire
-the way she’s direct about everything
-such a useless girl?
although she still pisses me off.
The publishing company
I started working at is located
on a floor of a multi-tenant building
in the heart of the big city.
It's a small company that publishes
information magazines targeted
at young men and women
in their late teens and early twenties.
THE BEST 20 PLACES FOR
THE GOLDEN WEEK HOLIDAY!
Since I’m the same age group
as those targeted,
I came into this job thinking this
would be the perfect workplace for me.
But my job here consists of…
cleaning, serving tea, making copies,
delivering manuscripts, and so on…
None of this has anything
to do with the magazine itself,
just simple jobs that anyone can do,
and so much of it with no end in sight.
Ow, my feet hurt…
From tomorrow, I’m wearing lower heels.
-Editor-in-chief.
-Yes?
Here are the illustration manuscripts
from Mr. Noguchi.
Oh, thank you for your hard work.
Nana, how about a drink tonight?
Not a good idea!
The editor-in-chief is on the verge
of sexual harassment.
-The company employees are…
-Could you speak a little slower, please?
-…mostly older men past their prime.
-A little slower, please?
Nana, dear,
make me some coffee.
The few young ones are all like that guy.
At least comb your hair,
25-year-old Honda!
Ms. Komatsu!
Can’t you even make copies properly?
They’re all crooked!
I’m so sorry.
And the trains are so crowded.
What in the world is there
to look forward to
as I make my way to the workplace daily?
I’m so exhausted!
Why is there no elevator
in this seven story building?
Why? Why is it?
This must be why the rent is so cheap.
I’m home.
Hachiko!
Wh-- What is it? Your smile is too bright.
A live show! A live show!
They had an opening
in an upcoming event at Shimokita,
and they’re letting us
fill that spot and play.
-Huh?
-It’s for thirty minutes on May 5th!
Yay!
Don’t cry, Hachiko!
We’re gonna party today!
Hey, did you hear?
On May 5th, Children’s Day,
they’re gonna decorate the kids’ meals
with little carp kites.
Look at this. Cute, don’t you think?
Wow, this is really well made!
This is great.
-You want it?
-Yeah, sort of.
But you can’t have it.
I got it as a birthday present
from our boss.
Huh? It was your birthday?
Why didn’t you tell me?
No, not yet.
My birthday is on Children’s Day.
I told him it’s a shame
I won’t see them being served
because I won’t be working that day,
so then he gave this to me,
saying it’s a birthday present.
Oh, so that’s why.
I’m off in the evening that day,
so why don’t we spend the evening
together to celebrate?
Really?
What do you want for your present?
A chimaki, maybe?
I love chimakis.
Shoji, your cell phone.
Oh, sorry. I forgot to turn it off.
You should answer it.
-Ah, but…
-It’s from your girlfriend, right?
If you keep ignoring her calls,
she’s gonna become suspicious.
-I’ll step outside.
-Ah, then I’ll go out…
Damn, what am I doing? Pathetic.
-Hello?
-Oh, Shoji! You’re awake!
Guess what? The date for Nana's
band's first live show has been decided!
Ah, r-- really? That’s great.
It’s at 8:00 p.m. on May 5th.
Can you make it?
The 5th?
Sorry. I can’t make it on the 5th.
-What? You can’t? You have work?
-Yeah.
No way. Can’t you do something about it?
No. You know, it gets extra busy
on national holidays, so I’ve gotta work.
I’m really sorry.
We’ll do it some other time.
Sure.
On Children’s Day,
let’s scatter some beans.
You’re thinking
of the Setsubun festivities, Shoji.
Stop looking. It’s so distracting.
Well, I was thinking,
"Wow, what a good looking woman,"
then I noticed it was you.
Huh? You won’t get anything
from seducing me.
I don’t really need anything,
as long as I have you by my side.
What’s gotten into you?
Do you have food poisoning?
I forgot to tell you,
the eggs in the fridge are old.
You know, I’ve been wondering
why people have a change of heart.
But the more I think about that,
the tougher it is to take.
Oh?
I had forgotten all about Tamura
from class six until Shoji brought her up.
Tamura from class six?
Unlike the other girls I went out with,
I really loved her.
And it really hurt when I found out
she was only playing with me.
What bittersweet teen years.
You know, there’s nothing
we can do about Shoji.
What do you mean?
Don’t tell me, he did it with Sachiko?
You know, I didn’t think
he was the kind of guy
who was capable of cheating,
due to multiple reasons.
As far as I know, neither did I!
He’s not just fooling around either.
He’s serious about the other girl.
He’s seriously fallen in love
with Sachiko.
He’s no longer able
to think rationally or morally.
There’s nothing we can do.
What’s he gonna do about Nana?
I wonder. It’s not as if anything’s
happened for him to dislike Nana.
I’m sure he continues
to have feelings for her.
But he’s gotta make things clear,
or else he’ll end up hurting
both Nana and Sachiko.
You’re right, but that’s
based on your values.
I don’t know much about Sachiko,
but what would be best for Nana?
As long as she doesn’t find out about it,
Shoji may be necessary for her,
even if he is seeing someone else.
Over time, Shoji’s feelings
for the other girl may cool.
You can’t expect me
to agree with that logic.
But just imagine for a minute.
Imagine Nana
after she gets ditched by Shoji.
Frightening, don’t you think?
She might even slit her wrists.
I just hope Shoji is doing
everything possible
to make sure Nana doesn’t find out!
Can’t be sure. It’s really frightening.
Hello, Nana here. Oh, Jun-chan?
It’s been a while. What’s up?
Ah, Nana?
You’re in the middle of work now,
aren’t you? Is it okay to talk?
Mm-hmm. No problem. We met our deadline,
so things are pretty peaceful here.
Hey, about that email you sent me
regarding your roommate’s live show.
Yeah, right! It’s next Saturday!
Can you come?
Mm-hmm. I’ll go with Kyosuke.
So tell me how to get there.
The three of us can go together then.
Huh? The three of us? What about Shoji?
Shoji said he had to work
and couldn’t come.
Huh?
Hey, Jun-chan, don’t you think Shoji
has been acting a little weird lately?
-What do you mean?
-I just have this feeling.
You think so?
He hasn’t really changed at all.
But I get the feeling
he’s been avoiding me.
That’s not true! You’re imagining it!
But it seems that Shoji’s
seriously growing tired of me.
Well, you know, you mustn’t
make excuses about how busy you are.
As hard as it may be,
try making the time to see him.
Show him that you really care,
and I’m sure he’ll reconsider
his feelings for…
I mean his attitude towards you!
Oh, I see. You’re right.
I’ll show him that I care.
Yeah, I’ll do my best.
Thanks, I’ll call you later.
Come on, Ms. Sakagami.
What are you doing here wasting time?
Please get back to work.
Why do I have to take the fall for Shoji?
This is all wrong.
But what else can I do?
Thank you very much!
Shoji!
I came.
Sorry for coming here without any notice.
Nice to meet you. I’m the bassist, Shin.
Hachi wouldn’t shut up
about wanting to see you.
We came all the way here,
so you’re paying.
Um… Then allow me
to show you to your table.
Please do.
This way, please.
No way. I’d rather sit
at that window seat over there.
Why should it matter where we sit?
Welcome.
Huh? Where’d Shoji go?
I’m sure he went
to get us water or something.
Would you sit down already?
Your boyfriend is so cool, Nana.
And that uniform really suits him.
Doesn’t it? Though he’s kinda lame
when he speaks.
Now how many times have I heard that?
-What are you doing, Ms. Kawamura?
-Excuse me! I’m very sorry!
You could hurt yourself
if you pick it up with your bare hands.
I’ll go get a broom.
You’re bleeding! Are you okay?
Your handkerchief. I’m sorry.
Don’t worry about it.
-You can have it, so never mind.
-But…
What’s important now is
for you to treat that cut.
-I’m sorry!
-Huh?
Ms. Kawamura. Why are you crying?
Get a hold of yourself!
I’ll take care of things here.
You go to the back.
I’m terribly sorry
for all the trouble, miss.
No, please do not worry about me.
You’re so kind, Hachiko.
My impression of you has just improved.
Actually, I used to work at
a family restaurant like this in the past,
so when I see something like that,
it’s like seeing myself.
Oh. I can just see you making
far worse blunders.
Huh? What’s that supposed to mean?
Come on!
I’ve run away again.
What am I doing hiding like this?
I should’ve predicted this much.
Well, Nana might not realize,
but Sachiko could very well realize.
Nana can be pretty loud, too.
Please, let Nana be nice and quiet.
I really am pathetic. I could just puke
thinking about how detestable a guy I am.
Sachiko.
Let’s put an end to this, Shoji.
She’s cute, kind,
and such a wonderful girlfriend.
What just happened between you and her?
It’s all right.
I doubt she has caught onto anything.
Let’s put an end to this,
before she ends up getting hurt.
I’m sorry, Shoji.
If I hadn’t gone after you like I did,
none of this would’ve happened.
That’s not true.
But at this rate,
I’ll just be more of a bother to you.
That’s not true!
This’ll continue hurting me, too.
No one can end up happy in this situation.
Make sure you take good care of her.
I guess it’s kinda hard to eat
with a pierced lip.
Serves you right.
Shin, you seem to be getting
more piercings by the day.
Now you even have one there.
What have you done to your beautiful face?
-I’m sure kissing is harder with that.
-No, I had no problem with that.
Shin! Who’d you kiss? Was it Nobu?
-Huh? Is Nobu into that sort of stuff?
-Is he?
Ah, no. But I thought this guy might be.
I’m straight.
Hey, Shin. Do you plan to continue living
at Nobu’s place like you are now?
Actually, I haven’t been
to Nobu’s place much lately.
I don’t wanna be a burden.
-So you’ve returned home.
-Nope.
Then where are you staying?
At some women's places.
What!
I move from place to place.
No way!
I’m still fifteen, I look like this,
and I still can’t find a steady job,
but I realized that if I live this way,
I won’t have any money problems.
Surprisingly, life can be pretty easy.
Shin… You’re a natural born bastard.
Bastard?
One day, you’re gonna get killed
by a woman.
Shin, I'm so sad.
Nana.
Come on, Shoji. Where had you run off to?
Do you have any plans after this?
No. I have four straight days off
from work starting tomorrow.
I'll wait for you to get off work.
-You don’t have to wait.
-Huh?
Can I go to your place later?
I need to talk to you about something.
If Nana hadn’t been with me that evening,
I probably would’ve thrown myself
into Tama River and sunk to the bottom.
I really think so.