I'm still calling your name, Nana…
no matter how much it hurts…
until you answer me.
I’m sorry I couldn't keep my promise.
You may not remember this,
but I was serious about building
that nice house with a big yard.
It would be on a hill
where we could see the ocean,
complete with a state-of-the-art
system kitchen and basement studio.
In your closet would be
a whole line of clothes
of the latest fashion,
so that you’d have a smile
on your face every time you came home,
even with your tendency
to have your heart broken by men.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
One way ticket to Tokyo.
The trains are running late
because of the snow.
Anything will do
as long as it gets me there.
EXIT
SMOKING AREA
You didn’t have to come see me off.
I called in sick and took the day off
to come see you off,
so you could be nicer.
Did you come alone? What about Nobu?
He’s probably home crying about now.
After all, you only told him yesterday.
Put yourself in the position
of those who are left behind.
Sorry. I struggled to find
the right time to tell you guys.
Although we knew that this day
would come eventually.
-What is it?
-Your birthday present.
This piece of paper?
REN
Don’t get me wrong!
I’m not going to Tokyo to see him!
I know. That has nothing to do with this.
You don’t understand.
You don’t understand anything.
The train on platform one for Tokyo…
-If you understand my feelings…
-will be departing momentarily.
-then come with me…
-All passengers not aboard are asked…
-Yasu!
-to please board the train now.
Why can’t I say these few words?
Because… you’ve chosen your path in life.
And Nobu has a great future ahead of him.
I can’t say it.
So you have to wish for it yourself.
Nana.
Don’t go.
It’ll be lonely without you.
Stop messing with me! Then come with me!
I guess negotiations break off there.
Oh well, good luck.
Yasu! There are law firms in Tokyo, too!
You can sing in this town, too.
But…
there is no big stage like
the Tokyo Dome or the Budokan here.
Think of it as a foolish dream
if you want.
But one day,
I will definitely perform on a big stage.
I’ll perform
under an incredible number of spotlights
among a cheering crowd
and earn so much money
I won’t know how to spend it.
I’m not some princess
who is satisfied just singing.
Singing is my means to live.
So one day, I’ll definitely…
What the… Who the…
And how long does she intend
to stay on top of me?
Are you all right?
I’m fine. Sorry!
I’ll never forget that day.
March 5th, 2001.
My twentieth birthday.
That’s the day I met you.
That stupid Demon Lord!
It’s nothing to cry about.
But I was really looking forward
to the fireworks!
I even withdrew cash
from my savings to buy a yukata to wear!
So you finally dipped
into Natsuko’s 300,000 yen.
We met on the train to Tokyo.
I ended up moving in together
with Nana Komatsu.
Nickname Hachi or Hachiko.
Hachiko is selfish,
overly dependent and cries easily.
She is completely boy crazy,
and she’s quick to switch over.
She’s only been in Tokyo for six months,
and she’s already dating a third guy.
Nobu…
But she would remain uncorrupted.
She was a strange woman.
Typhoon Eleven, which has made
its way onto land in the Kanto region,
is getting stronger as it continues north
and is expected to reach…
-Are you that jealous of our happiness?
-the Tohoku area later tonight…
-Well, I do understand how you feel.
-and Hokkaido tomorrow morning.
-Are you talking to the Demon Lord again?
-Total rain accumulation is estimated…
-I worry about you, Nobu.
-at 200ml in the Kanto region,
-But I’ll let it go since Hachi’s cute.
-150ml in the Tohoku region,
-Wrong. I’m talking to the weather girl.
-and 100 to 150ml in Hokkaido.
-Now I’m even more worried.
-Now, tomorrow’s weather.
First, the Kyushu and Okinawa regions…
-Na…
-Nobu! What are you doing?
Come here right now!
You promised to pick up Hachiko
at seven o’clock, right?
But we can’t go anywhere in this typhoon.
The fireworks will be canceled anyway.
Don’t you wanna see Hachiko in her yukata?
It’s bound to give you a nosebleed.
Why are you coming too, Shin?
-I wanna see Hachi in a kimono, too!
-It’s not a kimono, it’s a yukata!
What’s the difference?
-She’s so cute!
We bought fireworks.
Let’s go to the river and light them
after the storm passes.
Really? Thanks!
YASU
Hachi was like a pet
that belonged to our band.
Well, a better term would be
our queen bee.
Just having Hachi there
smiling brightened the place up.
It gave everyone added energy
in the studio
as well as during live performances.
I felt it had more meaning to the band
than getting another member,
no matter how skilled
that band member may be.
Look at all the water from the rain.
The riverbed has disappeared.
I'm glad the barriers didn't collapse.
The fireworks won’t light up!
Damn! They’re damp because of the rain.
-Ow!
-Are you all right?
Oh, it’s better you don’t touch it.
Wanna go to the convenience store again?
I got one lit, Nana. Here.
Thank you!
Very impressive, Yasu.
Light one up for me, too.
-You want one too, Misato?
-Yes!
Hey, what about me?
-Here, Nobu. I’ll lend you my spark.
-Thank you.
Here.
Is it innocence or deceit?
Nana!
You probably don’t realize it, do you?
Every move you make…
stirs my heart around
with the strength of a typhoon.
I feel like a teenage boy
falling in love for the first time.
It feels like my heart is about to burst.
-Do you wanna do it with Hachiko?
-It’s not like that!
That head of yours really does
only think about doing it!
But a young man in love for the first time
is totally battling
against his sexual desire.
Yes, it is a battle.
But it’s not about sexual desire.
Then more like an appetite?
Yeah, she does look delicious.
Like rice cake.
Rice cake?
AND CUTE
When I talk with you,
I feel like a total idiot
for seriously worrying about stuff.
I’m glad about that.
Because you’ve always had the tendency
to take things
too negatively and seriously.
Hachi seems to be really
affectionate with you,
so you should be glad that
someone cares about you so much.
Treat her as well as your heart desires.
There’s nothing wrong with that.
Yeah, but…
Edamame!
Well, now that you mention it,
that does make sense.
But I hate feeling persuaded like that!
Why am I always influenced
by what Ren says or does?
I can understand that
being the case in the past,
but why is it still like that?
I haven’t matured a bit.
First of all, I had no intention
of getting back together with him.
So why am I seeing him
like a part-time wife?
Why am I making miso soup?
And at this time of the night?
-Because it’s my favorite, right?
-Well, yeah, but…
Hey, where’s your on-off switch?
I don’t have one.
If there is one, install it in me.
Someone… please adjust me.
Why does my heart still burn
so hot?
Hello?
Oh, Take. Good morning.
No, it’s okay. I’ll take my car.
I’ll leave in thirty minutes.
He’s hardly had any sleep.
He’s gonna make himself sick.
But…
I do envy him for having so much work.
In fact, it’s frustrating.
You could stay in bed longer.
If you try living like me,
you’ll die young.
But I have to go to work.
The moving company Nobu works at
is short of staff,
so he introduced me
and got me a job there.
A moving company? That’s a manly job.
I can no longer work in the evenings
with our band practicing every night,
so I need to make my earnings
during the day.
What's going on with your debut?
Any progress?
Not really.
Back then, I stayed at Ren’s place
for about half of the week,
but we missed each other often
and would only see each other
for short periods.
When we were together,
we couldn’t control our passion
for each other,
so we hardly spent any time
talking about ourselves.
But I thought it was better that way
because that way we could avoid
unnecessary subjects
that would only make us feel awkward.
What? Still there?
So annoying, aren’t they?
Maybe I should move.
But maybe that won’t make any difference.
Huh? What? Those papa-rakkyos?
Not the rakkyos!
I’m talking about that woman!
I told you to have her go home!
Rakkyo makes me wanna eat curry and rice.
Yeah? I prefer Fukujinzuke
on my curry rice.
What? Curry rice wouldn’t be complete
without a raw egg.
Right, Takumi?
I don’t eat the common folk’s food!
BEEF CURRY
Open a pack of curry,
and heat it in a pot.
When you find you’re running short,
add a pack at a time.
Be careful so that it doesn’t burn
and stick to the pot.
The rice is already cooked,
so place a little on each plate…
Ms. Komatsu?
SERVICE AND GOODS ENTRANCE
I’m very sorry.
It can’t be helped.
You’re not feeling well.
Thank goodness it happened
before we let the customers in.
I am really sorry.
You mustn’t take
summer heat fatigue lightly.
You’d better go see a doctor.
Yes.
PHARMACY
You’re eating it.
And at an employees’ cafeteria.
THE COMMON FOLK’S CURRY RICE
These things are usually
the furthest from my mind,
so why is it that
when I suddenly remember it,
I suddenly crave it?
Bottom line is, you love the stuff?
-I wish it would end already.
-What?
Summer vacation.
Only three more days.
Summer vacation seems like
a long break, but it goes by so fast.
If at least discussions
about your debut were more concrete,
I could go home feeling relieved.
WORLD HISTORY, JAPANESE HISTORY,
BIOLOGY, SCIENCE, MATH
It’s been a month already
since you signed that contract,
but you don't even have an agency yet.
It’s only a temporary contract after all.
I’m not quite clear on the meaning
of that temporary contract.
How is it different
from the official contract?
I’d say it’s something like
an engagement before a wedding?
Mr. Kawano is presently working hard
to collect funds and personnel
to organize a big reception for us.
The contract is there
so we remain faithful to them,
even if others approach us.
In turn, we’re free to use
Gaia’s music studios as much as we want
while we prepare to be beautiful brides.
I get it!
I finally understand now. Thank you.
Hey, Misato. You’re older than me,
so why do you talk so politely to me?
Well, you’re younger than me, Shin,
so how come you’re able to help me
with my 12th grade homework?
I can only help you with your English.
Have Yasu or someone help you
with the other stuff.
-I knew it!
-You knew it?
You have that pretty and luminous face
because you’re only half-Japanese, right?
Pretty and luminous?
You can hide it all you want,
but I can tell.
That’s why your English is so good, right?
My English is good
because I was raised abroad.
My parents are both Japanese.
What? Raised abroad? Where?
I mean, so you're not half-Japanese
with that face?
Don’t you believe me?
I don’t.
I don’t either.
They shouldn’t have given birth to me.
SPEEDY RESULTS INSTRUCTIONS
All right! All right! Okay, stop!
SEAGULL DELIVERY SERVICE
Wow, such a huge mansion!
It’s small! Too small!
It’s nothing compared to the future house
of Nana from BLAST.
I’ll show you, Demon Lord!
I see you’ve also become
a believer of the Demon Lord.
No way! The Demon Lord is my underling.
Back then, I had a dream
that I couldn’t give up.
Thanks to that,
I was able to obtain so much,
and at the same time,
lose something so precious.
But I lived life to the fullest,
so I have no regrets.
Just…
there’s one thing that
weighs heavy on my heart.
Hey, Hachi…
Right now… Are you smiling?