They say that the closer you are,
the more you fight,
but fighting is nothing
but a clash of egos.
Revealing your true feelings
doesn’t necessarily make people
understand each other better.
I think it’s probably impossible
to live your life without getting hurt,
but I also think an effort
should be made not to hurt others.
I just felt so strongly about that.
FROM NANA
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
HACHI - SEPTEMBER 11TH 08:56 A.M.
GOOD MORNING
THANKS FOR CALLING ME LAST NIGHT.
I WAS REALLY HAPPY TO HEAR FROM YOU,
SO I’M SORRY FOR HANGING UP ON YOU
SO ABRUPTLY.
I THOUGHT LONG AND HARD AFTER THAT
AND REALIZED THERE’S SOMETHING
I MUST TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
Good morning, Reira. Did you sleep well?
Yes. My head is clear, perhaps
because I didn’t take any medication.
Is that so? That’s good, since you have
to talk to a lot of people today.
-A lot?
-Yes.
In the morning, you have an interview with
a women’s magazine here in this hotel.
In the afternoon, we change locations,
and all band members will give interviews
to three music magazines
and two information magazines.
In the evening, you have
two radio show recordings.
I’m so sorry for scheduling
all this for one day.
No, the recording got delayed
all because of me.
-I’m really sorry.
-It’s okay.
Can I take a shower?
Do we still have time?
Yes. The hair and make-up people
are scheduled to be here
in thirty minutes.
What do you wish to do about breakfast?
Just order something from room service.
Yes.
You forgot it on purpose, didn’t you?
I had a day off from work that day,
so I spent the day sleeping peacefully
in Ren’s arms for the first time in days.
I woke up feeling that
my troubles had disappeared.
Damn, I left my umbrella at Ren’s place.
Tell him that I won’t be seeing him
for a while.
Knowing Nobu, he probably never told him.
That guy’s really useless.
Is your pride that important to you?
Here, here.
I doubt I’ll be able to erase
the complicated feelings I have
towards Trapnest’s Ren unless
I make it big with my singing career.
But the reason
I always end up letting things
like this happen when we meet
is because I love him.
It’s as simple as that.
The strawberry glasses weren’t
in the kitchen cupboard.
I couldn’t imagine Hachi taking
my glass too,
so I figured
the glass must’ve broken after all,
which made me feel uneasy.
-Actually, both glasses were broken.
-Huh?
Takumi told me.
He said, "Your woman is terribly brutal.
You’ve gotta discipline her."
Discipline me?
When Hachiko saw them broken,
she was so shocked she started crying.
Takumi apparently had a tough time
trying to calm her down.
Given the situation, it’s normal to think
that you broke them out of anger.
In reality, it’s not likely that
both would break by accident.
It’s natural that Hachi would wanna
move out without saying anything.
All the more if those glasses
were precious to her.
It’s more than enough
to give her the message
that you’re ending your relationship.
What am I gonna do?
That wasn’t my intention at all.
-Then what was your intention?
-I don’t know.
You really don’t remember?
And you don’t remember putting
your phone in the water.
Sorry. And after you went to the trouble
of getting that phone for me.
-Something was wrong with me.
-It’s all right.
If you need a cell phone,
we can buy another one.
But I lost all the phone numbers
and email addresses I had.
I should’ve kept a list.
Well, the few friends you have
are mostly my friends too, so…
wanna copy the numbers?
That’s right.
It needs to be recharged.
Charge it right now!
No, I have to get going.
You’re practicing again
at the studio tonight too, right?
Ask the guys directly when you’re there.
But I’ve gotta call her right away.
Rather than calling her, go see her.
Hachi’s struggling with morning sickness,
and it’s raining.
She‘s probably home.
SHIROGANE 7-CHOME, MINATO-KU
Shirogane… 302?
That’s the same number as Ren’s place.
Ren! Give me a ride to the station!
To Shirogane-dai station?
No, the station over there.
I’ve gotta buy those glasses.
No matter how many times I think it over,
I can’t get over how careless I was.
But with the rain getting stronger
and the restlessness of not
having an umbrella
added to the anxiety of wanting
to hurry and see Hachiko…
How lucky!
Is this the rain of good fortune?
The trigger that alters someone’s fate
can be pulled in an instant.
2:40 P.M.
Hello, Mrs. Ichinose.
Are you going out?
Yes. Can you please call a taxi for me?
Certainly. Where to?
To the Shirogane-dai station.
This isn’t good. I don’t have a clue.
It should be somewhere around here.
Twenty minutes from the station?
I feel like I’ve been walking for an hour.
Excuse me.
I need to get to this address.
Would you know the way?
CALL
I should just act normally,
as if nothing ever happened.
Hachi thinks that I’m taking Nobu’s side
and am therefore furious,
taking a stand for justice…
because she thinks of me as some hero.
So I must teach her that a true hero
always stands by the heroine,
no matter what happens.
&lrm;CALL
Sorry, Nobu.
I WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU
UNTIL SEVEN O’CLOCK
AT THE TICKET GATE
OF SHIROGANE-DAI STATION. NANA
Um, excuse me.
It seems that the person
I’ve come to see is not here.
Can you please give this to her
when she returns?
Of course.
Whom is it to, and which suite number?
Suite 302…
Suite 302 is presently vacant.
Could you have the wrong suite number?
302 is the same number as Ren’s place.
I definitely don’t have the wrong number.
Excuse me.
Smoking is not permitted
in the restaurant.
Nana Komatsu?
There’s no one by that name living here.
That’s impossible!
She just moved here recently!
Why, of course. It’s under Takumi’s name.
What’s Takumi’s surname?
Or is Takumi his real name to begin with?
I have no idea what Takumi’s real name is!
Takumi of Trapnest and his woman
live in suite 302, don’t they?
There’s no use hiding it. I already know.
There’s no one living here
who matches that description.
Excuse me, but could you please leave?
DO NOT ACCEPT MESSAGES FROM ANY VISITORS
WITHOUT AN APPOINTMENT.
Damn it!
I bet that guy mistook me
for a fan of Takumi.
Of all people, Takumi!
Suite 302 is presently vacant.
A peremptory measure.
Takumi would think of that kind
of method to get rid of someone.
Sure, if confronted in that way,
many would think they made a mistake.
People will believe it is a vacant room,
and Hachi, living her life here carefree,
would be like a ghost,
unaware that she is already dead.
She’d exist only for Takumi
and the child she’s having.
Hey, Hachi, are you really fine with that?
What? You’re getting married?
Yes.
Are you pregnant?
You’re really good
at figuring out such things.
That’s the only reason that comes to mind
that would lead Takumi to propose.
But is it really Takumi’s child?
Probably.
Have an abortion.
You should tell Takumi the truth
and break up with him.
The thought that you’ll earn happiness
just by getting married
is only an illusion.
Of course, Takumi knows everything.
He knows, and he’s still marrying you?
That sounds unbelievable!
Huh? But, well, I can go through with this
because we accept each other
even after knowing stuff about that.
Am I weird?
And Takumi is a weird person too.
No. I don’t really know what’s weird
and what’s not about anything,
so don’t worry about anything I say.
You think maybe your family situation
has some similarities
with the position I’m in now?
I think the reason people are keeping
my situation a secret from only you is,
of course partly because
they don’t wanna talk about me,
but I think it’s also
because they don’t wanna open up
any scars you have from the past.
I also intended to keep it
a secret from you,
because I knew you would be
against me keeping it.
But then I thought that’s all
the more reason why
I should tell you everything.
I’m sure your mother went
through a lot of agony like I did
but still wanted to have you, Shin.
I know that much.
Stop treating me like a child.
I’M SORRY
Then I want to hear from you
what made you feel that your mother
should never have given birth to you.
I don’t ever want my own child
saying something like that.
But if the child is not Takumi’s,
I’m sure that would be agonizing for him.
And the child
would eventually think it strange
if they don’t look alike
or their blood types are different.
But even so, I believe we can still be
a happy family if we try,
or at least I’d like to at least hope so.
-Am I being naive?
-I think so.
But really, don’t mind what I say.
Even if there are some similarities,
things will be different
if the people involved are different.
You’ve just gotta do what
you believe is right.
Yeah. I’m sorry.
I wish I’d been born as your child, Hachi.
Shinichi Okazaki’s mother took her life
shortly after Shin was born.
The truth about Shin’s biological father
may be lost forever.
I can investigate further if you wish,
but you’ve gotta realize
it’s a case about one individual,
and it happened overseas.
No, this is more than enough
for a great story.
I’d rather have you investigate
the whereabouts of Nana’s mother.
Thank you as usual.
But unless BLAST becomes big,
won’t this go to waste?
Just watch. There’s no doubt about it.
They’ll be big.
But it appears that Gaia has
no intention of letting them debut.
I’ll make it happen.
Even if they were to debut,
they won’t sell.
A visually attractive band
may attract fad followers,
but that will repel the real music lovers.
-And these songs aren’t what--
-Stop talking like some music critic!
What the people want never changes!
They want a stimulating topic!
And yet the young brats of today
just don’t get it.
They all believe they’re great artists.
It makes me sick.
A world where "honor student" bands
like Trapnest reign is as sleepy as hell!
I would just love to break that nose
of Takumi that he proudly sticks up high.
Anyway, I look forward
to tomorrow’s party.
We’ll open everyone’s eyes.
Huh? But Search isn’t on the shelves
until the day after tomorrow, right?
I sold half of the information
to TV networks.
They were really into my scenario
and practically handed over their wallets.
It wasn’t about getting a scoop, huh?
My objective is to increase
magazine sales!
Get the people excited with news
about their love affair,
and the people will jump
at the precious photo!
You got a picture of them together?
It looks great.
That day, I waited for Hachi
in front of her place until sunset,
but I couldn’t see her.
TRAIN TICKET MACHINE
210 YEN
I’ll come again tomorrow after work.
I have a little time
before I go to the studio.
I’ll get her phone number from Yasu,
so we don’t miss each other
like this again.
It’s not like I’ll never see her again.
There’s always tomorrow.
Sorry to keep you for so long.
I’m so glad we got the chance
to talk about all kinds of stuff.
Housewives are craving
for the chance to talk to people.
Don’t remain at home thinking only
about the baby in your tummy.
You need to get in touch
with the outside world.
But the only plans I have to go out
are for shopping and checkups.
Why don’t you take courses on something?
You’d also make housewife friends
that way.
Great idea.
Good luck with your practice, Shin.
Personally, I think some things
are impossible to achieve,
no matter how much you practice.
That’s not true!
I believe that BLAST will become
the best band in Japan someday!
Well then, madame, we’ll meet again
when your husband’s not around.
Yes.
Shin!
How is Nobu?
He keeps playing his guitar!
It’s so noisy I can’t get any sleep!
I can’t wait until dawn.
I hope it’ll be sunny tomorrow.
Ouch!
Oh, sorry. You’re home.
Seven o’clock?
He just got to bed. I’m amazed how
he can get up and go to work.
What are you watching a video
of yourself so early in the morning?
-No. We’re on TV.
-Oh, how nice.
Is this "Channel Nana"?
Wake up! There is no such channel!
MORNING 7
Good morning! It’s time for Morning 7!
We've learned
about the passionate love affair
of Trapnest’s guitarist, Ren!
She's a member of his former band
and the vocalist of the "Black Stones,"
a band on the brink
of a major debut with Gaia Records.
Her name is Nana!
Ever since that day
when the thick clouds passed
and I was suddenly in the spotlight…
The place we were standing was
not a stage but the center of a ring.
I can still hear the cheers
and jeers ringing in my head,
loud and annoying…