If I were to die now, I doubt Ren
would die with me anymore.
But that’s fine. That’s how it should be.
I must be crazy for thinking that’s sad.
WRITTEN BY AI YAZAWA
Excuse me, I’m from next door, and…
I think she’s hyperventilating.
D-- Do you have a plastic or paper bag?
You don’t have one?
A paper bag would be better.
If you don’t use it right,
plastic could make it worse.
Really?
Or rather, how should she use it?
Well… um… I’ve never been
in this situation before…
You seem like you know a lot.
Is it safe for someone
not in the medical profession to do it?
Sure. I always do it by myself.
Lay her on her back,
then cover her nose and mouth
with the paper bag
but make a little opening.
Like this…
Have her take deep breaths,
and it’ll stop before long.
It’s a living hell.
Th-- Thank you. I’ll give it a shot.
You don’t have to freak out.
She’s got that guy,
who is like a tranquilizer.
Tranquilizer?
I was jealous, so I said something mean.
Sorry.
As if being pulled up
from the depths of the ocean,
I was finally able to breathe.
Yasu’s chest had
the sweet scent of Black Stone.
I’m not going anywhere.
YOU'RE SURE TO FIND IT
-Ah, Ginpei. Keep up the good work.
-Where’s Nana?
How is she? Did you notify Dr. Azuma?
Calm down.
She was probably just hyperventilating.
The same symptoms as Myu’s.
That’s a problem.
The security guard apparently
phoned the agency
instead of getting an ambulance.
Ginpei rushed over,
and he drove me to see a doctor
he said he knew well.
By the time we arrived at the hospital,
which was past its hours of operation,
I was feeling completely back to normal.
But they insisted that
I get checked just to be sure,
and I got a thorough physical checkup.
AZUMA HOSPITAL
Hyperventilation syndrome.
Also known simply as hyperventilation.
-What’s that?
-It’s just as the words suggest.
It’s caused by excessive breathing.
The carbon dioxide levels
in your blood decrease,
causing the attack.
Carbon dioxide levels in my blood?
Be quiet and listen.
Your attack subsided
when you placed a paper bag
over your mouth
and breathed into it.
This is called
"the paper bag technique," and--
Doctor, I don’t need you to share
your knowledge with me.
What the hell’s wrong with me?
Is it my lungs?
-No.
-Then is it my blood?
No.
Then it must be because I smoke
even though I’m on the pill.
But I heard that when you’re young,
a little is all right.
"A little"?
That’s not good.
You risk getting thrombosis, you know.
I know that, but I can’t quit either.
What am I gonna do?
If you’d use protection instead,
then the problem’s solved.
Huh? Me?
Come on, Doctor! You’re misunderstanding!
Yasu belongs to me!
My apologies. But in any case,
the examination shows
there is nothing wrong with you,
so you can relax.
Huh?
I was in so much pain I thought I’d die!
Did you examine me properly?
You rogue doctor!
Nana…
Ms. Osaki, calm down.
Hyperventilation can occur
after strenuous exercise,
but it can also easily happen
if you’re overly nervous or excited.
But she’s always like this, Doctor.
How can it be cured?
Well, there’s no guarantee
it’ll even happen again.
The best thing to do is
to not worry about it.
Of course I’ll be worried!
I’m a singer, Doctor!
Performing live is a tough workout,
and I do get really excited
when performing.
I can’t risk having
another attack onstage!
Please do something!
Hmm… But this is stress-related,
which isn’t my area of expertise.
If you’re worried,
I suggest you see a psychiatrist.
If you’d like, I’ll write you a referral.
-A psychiatrist?
-Thank you very much, Doctor!
I always appreciate your help greatly!
Nana!
Oh, you were here?
Oh, you look perfectly fine.
Nana!
Are you feeling all right?
What did the doctor say?
He says I’m nuts, like I thought.
BAM
That hurt!
Wow, that stone head full
of prejudices won’t even crack!
Don’t crack it!
In this modern age,
everyone has to deal
with varying degrees of stress.
It’s truly a difficult world to live in.
You just happen to be
a little more sensitive than others.
There’s nothing wrong with that.
But I hate myself for being so weak.
I can’t stand being who I am anymore…
So why do these guys
continue being with me?
They've got guts.
FROM NOBU
MESSAGE FROM NANA
I’M REALLY BUSY SO I CAN’T CALL YOU,
BUT I’M DOING REALLY WELL, DARLING!
LET’S BOTH DO OUR BEST.
Why is there so much work to do
immediately after returning?
It can’t be helped.
Going to England wasn’t part
of the original schedule.
-So stop whining!
-Sorry about that.
It’s not your fault, Ren.
I don’t think it was necessary
to go all the way to England
in the first place.
What are you doing?
Don’t touch it with your filthy hands!
Filthy? I’m out of lighter fluid.
That’s a lighter, right?
Huh? So that’s a lighter? Wow, it’s huge!
You know, you said the same thing
when you saw the one
Shin was using at the after-party.
Have you forgotten already?
Huh? You mean Shin from BLAST?
He said it was a limited edition.
It’s a rare item.
Is that right?
That one you have isn’t Shin’s, is it?
It isn’t!
Why are you carrying a lighter
in the first place
when you don’t even smoke?
It’s from a fan, and I like it!
Must be nice to get cool stuff like that.
All I get are stuffed animals.
My room’s full of stuffed animals.
You’re actually displaying them?
Ren, hand me your lighter.
FROM SHIN
WELCOME BACK
I’VE BEEN THROWN
INTO THIS JAIL THEY CALL A DORM.
I’M THINKING OF A WAY
THAT I CAN MEET YOU
WITHOUT ANYONE NOTICING
BUT HAVEN’T COME UP WITH ANY IDEAS.
I’D LOVE TO SEE YOU SOON.
Saying I was busy was just an excuse.
I’m sure Ren realized that.
But if I heard Ren’s voice,
I thought I’d have trouble
breathing again. I was scared.
So now, I’m announcing today’s schedule!
There’s a photoshoot for promo material
at the Harajuku studio.
-Promo material?
-Promotional material.
In the afternoon,
there will be three interviews
for music magazines.
We’re introducing ourselves,
so we’ll be visiting them.
Please make sure
you’re very polite to the people
during these work-related visits.
We want to leave a good impression.
Remember, your rebellious image
is only an act.
Also, if they ask you any questions
about your private lives,
do not answer.
Then, at 7:00 p.m.,
we will meet with event organizers
to discuss the guerrilla live performance.
That will be at the Gaia main office.
A rehearsal at the Kagurazaka
studios at 9:00 p.m.
Finishing time depends on Matsuo’s mood.
Well, there you have it.
It’s not as packed as I thought.
That’s plenty packed!
Nana’s still recovering, you know!
-Not a problem at all.
-Well then, we’re leaving now!
-We’ll have breakfast in the car.
-All right! I’m starving!
The busier I was, the better I felt.
This is Masaru, the stylist.
Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you, too.
-If the work was fulfilling,
I felt refreshed, so I didn’t think
I had to go to the hospital.
I don’t intend to change much.
Your styles are already
pretty well established.
I agree! Let’s bring bondage
back into style!
SIGH
There were so many people involved
with BLAST’s debut project
that I couldn’t remember everyone’s names.
I can’t ask about your private lives?
At least tell me what your hobbies are.
-Mahjong.
-That was fast!
Interacting with people
was never my forte,
but I had no problem with it.
Teacher, I’m so hungry
I can’t reach the high notes!
Don’t blame it on your stomach.
One more time!
Yo, Old Fox! How are ya doing?
What dirty tricks do you have
up your sleeve this time?
Nana!
Looking good. Okay, don’t move.
Think we should tell Misato
about the live performance?
But it’s on a weekday.
Midterms are coming up, right?
If we tell her,
it could be a disaster for her.
I wonder if she’ll be able to graduate.
Hey guys! You can’t tell anyone about it!
I felt that if I saw Hachi now,
I could laugh and talk with her.
I felt I could even listen to her
talk about Takumi and the baby.
But there just wasn’t any time.
I’m sleepy.
But if I don’t do the laundry today,
I’ll run out of clothes to wear.
I’ve gotta hurry and move my stuff
from the old apartment
and cancel the lease.
It’s a waste of money.
Won’t anyone do it for me?
The laundry too?
But everything won’t fit here.
Should I just send it
to my parents’ place for now?
But I’ll bet Dad’s still angry with me.
But when BLAST’s debut
is officially confirmed,
I’ll bet they’ll be so thrilled.
G-- Good evening.
LAUNDRY
-Um… Can I ask you something?
-Huh?
Ah, well, about hyperventilation.
You probably wouldn’t wanna talk
about it, huh? I’m sorry.
It’s all right. What is it?
One of our staff members told me
that if Nana has another attack,
we should stay calm and act
as if it’s no big deal,
that if the people around her
start to panic,
it would only make her more anxious.
I do think he has a point,
and I hear that’s what the doctor’s said,
so that may be the right thing to do.
But wouldn’t you feel lonely
if you were in great pain
and those around you acted
like it’s no big deal?
Like, I wonder if I could remain calm.
I doubt I could.
GIGGLE
Huh?
Whether you’re surrounded
by people who are calm or upset,
you wouldn’t be lonely
if you could feel their compassion.
I don’t know about other people,
but that’s how I’d feel.
I feel like I just asked
something totally obvious.
-Hey, is that a script for a movie?
-Yeah.
-You’re an actress?
-More or less.
I’m sorry. I didn’t know.
It’s okay. I’m not at all well-known.
This is a small part
for a straight-to-video.
What’s the title?
I’ll be sure to watch it
when it goes on sale!
-Tanki na Onna.
-A mahjong movie?
I love mahjong!
Though I’m really bad at it!
-Um, can I ask you one more thing?
-What?
What’s your name?
I wonder how many people
in this city know my name right now.
Hey, what’s that? Is someone coming?
Who knows?
It’s probably some unknown singer.
It would be nice if they could
get Trapnest to perform.
I can never get a ticket.
That’ll never happen.
Anyway, Yuji and the guys are
at the karaoke room and told us to join.
Wanna go?
-Sure. Will they be paying?
-Mr. Kawano? We’re all set here.
LETTERS
Okay, go! Play as hard as you want!
Hi, Yuji? Yeah. We’re on our way now.
-Nana!
-Huh?
-Hey, that’s BLAST! BLAST!
-No way.
-No way! Nana?
-What? Who?
-She’s the worst! Get lost!
-Don't you know them?
I can’t tell which ones are
the hired applauders.
Looks like we’re more famous
than I thought.
I guess Ren’s pretty popular
with the people.
That means we don’t have
to spend time on introductions.
I appreciate it, paparazzi.
October 10, 2001. 7:00 p.m. in Shinjuku.
You guys all better be thankful
for the fate of just happening
to be here right now by coincidence.
FROM YASU
MESSAGE FROM NANA
I’LL BE WAITING AT 7:00
IN FRONT OF ALTA IN SHINJUKU. NANA
Hey, Hachi.
It’s a little far,
but that’s the safest VIP seat.
I wonder if the baby in your belly
can hear me singing, too.
&lrm;SHIBUYA 109
Good morning, everyone!
It’s Friday, October 26th.
Time for Music J.
The first video clip today is
of the new Trapnest single,
"Shadow of Love."
-I wanna wear the same dress as Reira!
-Huh?
You know, the wedding dress
she wears in the promo video!
It’s so beautiful!
I totally wanna wear it!
Can they make another of the same?
We already ordered a dress.
You can’t change it now.
-You’ll make the dressmaker cry.
-But I wanna wear it.
Then I’ll change twice
during the reception.
That’s too many times.
Besides, it’s not the dress that’s pretty.
It’s Reira.
It wouldn’t look good on you. Give it up.
I knew it! You’re involved with Reira!
No, I’m not!
And what do you mean "I knew it"?
Oh, Myu! Good morning!
Calcium? Can I have some?
Hey, Nobu. Will you stop calling me Myu?
-My name’s not Myu. It’s Miu.
-But it’s too hard to pronounce.
Why not? It’s a cute nickname.
Everyone says so,
and no one pronounces my name properly.
Though I really like my name.
No one does?
Then I will be
the only one to call you Miu.
Are you off today?
Nope, we’ll be on a music show tonight,
so we’ve got a rehearsal in the afternoon.
You’re really busy, huh?
It’s already been one month
since we moved into the dorm,
and Nobu is getting cozy
with the girl next door.
There was no point in us changing rooms!
I would’ve preferred to have
him fool around with Yuri.
Why do people easily drift
from one relationship to the next?
Until recently, all he’d say was,
"Hachi, Hachi, Hachi, Hachi."
They’re all such fools, Hachi included.
But it would be too cruel
to force Nobu into a relationship
that has no future.
I have no right to do that.
Hey, this isn’t good.
I’m having… trouble breathing…
Good morning. Are you going somewhere?
Like, to have your hair cut?
No, I have a meeting with Mr. Kawano,
so I’ll be leaving ahead of you.
You’re looking pale. Are you feeling okay?
I’m perfectly fine.
I can’t keep Yasu
in an unrequited love limbo.
On top of that,
why did I unwittingly move in
next door to him?
That’s pretty cruel.
One reason I didn’t wanna get back
with Ren is because
I was feeling
Yasu’s extraordinary love for me.
But in the end, I got swept away.
I’m just one of the fools.
I’ll breathe into this just to be safe.
After all, I have
important work to do today.
I’ve managed to keep on living
even when Ren wasn’t around,
but without Yasu, I’d probably fall apart.
I’ve gotta end it.
The next time I see Ren,
I won’t get swept away.
It’s been a while
since we performed live
for a music show on TV!
I’m sure
the fans are looking forward to it.
I bet the ratings are gonna be great!
I’m sure of it.
They’re throwing us in the pit together.
But even if they pick a fight,
I’m not gonna fight back.
-What are you talking about?
-Here, say "Aaah…"
-Do not resort to violence, Takumi.
-BLAST will be performing, too!
Hey, Hachi.
I always thought life was
about standing your ground,
no matter how strong the current is.
But going with the flow isn’t
such a foolish thing after all,
as long as you’re moving forward.